We're back for day three, and today we're shipping our company, and so if this is the first time
you're tuning in, we are building a company in 72 hours at the Grok Bot Galaxy event in
San Francisco.
Just a quick round of intros if this is the first time you're joining us.
I'm Matt.
I work in Developer Experience at SpaceX AI.
Hello, I'm Potato, also known as Lauren, and I work on Grok Bot at SpaceX AI.
I'm Roshan.
I work on product at SpaceX AI and Grok Bot, some other stuff too.
Yeah, and so if you're joining us from yesterday, we've done actually quite a bit overnight
because Lauren set up a bit of a software factory, but before we jump into that software
factory, I think we have an announcement for you all, and that is if you sign up, if you're
new users, you haven't used Grok Bot before, you don't have an account, you sign up in
the next 10 minutes, you can get a month for free.
So new users get one month free of Grok Bot, and that kind of starts right now,
so you'll see a clock below.
So go online, registered, and then you also have to create, what is the, we have to
create a bot?
You have to download Grok Bot, you have to create an account, and you have to set up
a recurring task, and Potato is going to tweet about some examples for how you could
do this, like searching through your emails, any other routines that we love, keeping an
eye on GitHub issues.
Yeah, like looking at Slack, you know, things that take up a lot of your time are
great to automate, and you can just tell your Grok Bot to, like, hey, check my emails
every day, and I'll set it up for you, so very, very easy.
Yeah, we have a QR code here if we want to get my screen up on the stream that we're
showing. It's one free month of Grok Bot, valid for new accounts only, so you've
been watching these past two days, but for some reason, haven't signed up on your
own, eight minutes and 20 seconds left from that timer down there for you to
claim a free month of Grok Bot.
I think this includes a lot of credits, too, right?
It's like a pretty good free month.
Like, yeah, 200 bucks, like, of usage in the first month, so.
Awesome. Okay, $200 in value, free month of our highest tier.
That's a lot of usage.
Yeah, we'll have to see how much usage we used over the last few days.
Awesome. So, yeah, you got nine minutes to take care of it, and I feel like we can
maybe spend, actually, seven minutes. Time goes by pretty quickly, and I feel like
we can maybe spend some of that time talking through what we built last night
and where things are at.
Yeah, Ocean, do you want to maybe show us some of the, I think we made a lot of
changes for our game, but maybe to start, like, maybe we should talk about,
like, what our game is for the people who are just tuning in?
Yeah, I think it's a great idea.
So, for those who are just tuning in, we are building a game studio and
launching our first game today, imminently, in the next few hours.
I think we have a little bit of Paula, if we want to get in before we get it
all out, out there to the world.
But we are building a game, and we have a team of, really, an army of Grok
Bots that we've been using to build this game with.
Towards the tail end of the afternoon yesterday, we put together a team of
bots that are basically helping create a software factory here.
And so you're looking at my copy of this factory that was inspired by some
of the bot templates that Lauren shared with me.
And I don't know, Lauren, do you want to maybe talk through some of the ways
the factory works?
I can show some of this while you're doing that.
Yeah, so for a start, like, I think the factory is pretty interesting,
where what Roshan and I did was, basically, we did a lot of brainstorming
last night about game mechanics, and just thinking through polish,
and how we want the game to actually be fun.
So we initially started with a game that kind of felt like a 1v1 rock
paper scissor game, with Elo, and a scoring system, and a leaderboard.
And then when we played it, we found that it was not really that fun.
So we got inspired by some of the other games that we enjoy,
and we kind of got inspired by some of those mechanics.
And we crafted some plans together with Grokbot and Cloud Agents,
and then we used Pstack, which is my personal set of skills.
It's a cursor plug-in and a Grokbot plug-in.
And in that plug-in, there is a skill called Potato Mode.
And Potato Mode is a skill that essentially
teaches your bots to be much more rigorous and much more basically
much better at orchestrating other bots and agents.
And yeah, that's it right there on the screen.
And one of the cool things about Pstack
is if you type slash Potato Mode, and you say full autopilot this plan,
it will actually go off and break down
that plan into lots of different small phases.
And then basically set up a mini factory
where you have agents that implement the PR, the small PRs.
You have agents that go off and verify.
They'll run your application.
They'll fuzz it where they just actually click around and test it,
find bugs, and basically give you a ton of trust
so you can actually just merge.
The PRs will just auto merge themselves in full autopilot mode
because of that rigorous verification and checks being done.
So overnight, I think we landed more than 100 PRs.
I think we're at 150 now?
145.
You should look at what's closed.
We're at 170.
Really?
OK.
160, 170, something like that.
Let's see.
Yeah, 160 out.
Yeah, we have our back.
Cranking over here too.
Yeah, yeah.
We did all sorts of redamping the UI, upgrading our back end,
and making sure it was good security
and it can handle the load, I hope, fingers crossed.
Well, we'll find out.
Yeah, we'll find out soon.
I wanted to show a little bit of that in action.
So this is my, I just merged 124,
which was a UI rewrite that we were working on
and remacing a few times over the last few hours.
And you can see how the bots communicate
with each other in action.
You have a bot here whose name is Play,
whose job is to basically be a play tester.
So you can imagine any good game needs a QA team.
Well, we don't have a QA team.
We had an intern yesterday,
but that intern is not with us today.
And so we have a QA bot whose job it is
to basically look at each PR.
And this is using one of those subscriptions we talked about
where you can create a recurring task
or respond to an event and looks at each PR.
And anytime it sees a PR that looks like it's green
on our CI suite, we'll just jump in and play test it
and go through the UI, drive the entire game end-to-end,
knows how the game engine works
and will provide any feedback
on what might need to be changed
before we merge that PR.
And you can see, have all of our bots coordinating here
to get all that work done.
It's pretty cool.
Yeah, I really love routines in Graphbot
because again, like going back to this factory concept,
well, first of all,
I actually don't really even like the term factory,
but I guess it's like the closest analogy
of something that's very automated.
And I think a lot of us,
even if you don't do engineering work,
there's so many tasks that we do that are so repetitive.
Like I, for example,
I'm very bad at checking my emails.
I just get so lazy at doing that.
It's almost like I'm consciously avoiding it
because I'm dreading how much time and effort it takes
to like go through and like, oh, this one's spam.
You know, like, oh, I have to reply to this one.
And I don't even know what I need to reply.
So Graphbot can kind of,
you can teach it how to like go through your inbox.
It can go through Slack.
It can go through GitHub PRs.
Basically anything you can imagine,
you can automate with Graphbot.
So definitely check out, you know,
check out Graphbot and ask your bot
to help you out with those.
So we got, by the way,
two minutes and 20 seconds on the promo here.
So if you're a new user, you sign up for Graphbot.
And then, you know, you perform,
you set up a recurring task.
So create an account, set up a recurring task.
You get a month free of Graphbot.
And if I was just, you know,
if I was just to summarize maybe what I'm hearing
is that it sounds like essentially what we're trying to do
with this like software factory concept,
which might be kind of ambiguous,
is like set up really good feedback loops
for agents to be able to do work themselves.
And that means removing the manual steps
that we would normally have to do.
Clicking through UIs, validating that things work,
looking at logs.
If you pass all the right information,
the right context to an agent,
you might be able to automate those things.
And the same way we can do that
for software development,
we can do that for things like email
or other, you know, business operations functions.
And that's kind of what it means, right,
to build a company with AI.
It's like break down all these human workflows,
isolate them, and then figure out
how you can have an agent that does all this stuff
that an agent should do, right?
Maybe an agent shouldn't be sending emails for you,
but it can get rid of all the spam,
it can unsubscribe you from lists,
and then it can send you an email
that you need to look at,
help you come up with a draft,
and make that process a bit more smooth, right?
Yeah, you put it perfectly.
Okay, cool.
It's, because when I hear factory,
I'm like, I don't know.
I know, I don't like that term either,
but I think, yeah, it's a term that I think,
a lot of people use.
We have about a minute left for the one month free,
so definitely download it.
Yeah, and while you guys are talking,
I'm firing off a few bots to do some additional UI polish
on what we've built.
Should we show off the UI for a little bit?
Are we ready?
There's still some scrolling issues.
I feel like if we're not embarrassed by it,
then we've launched to,
yeah, there's definitely some.
We may want to hide the bar to put it in full screen.
Yeah, there's some work that we've done to,
yeah, let me do that now.
Okay, let's take a look.
Can we see Roshan's screen?
Let's take a look.
We have a sponsorship form on the main page
that I think we'll need to move out,
or refactor, but.
You've been zooming in as well.
Yes, there we go.
Yeah, zooming in a little bit.
Here's our game.
We have a, we are a code name calling it Cupcake,
a real name drop coming soon.
So if you wanna see what it's called
when we launch this,
stay tuned.
We have a signing with Twitter support working,
which is really cool.
We have a global leaderboards.
Right now it's just Potato and I
who've been play testing the game,
but hopefully you all will be able to jump in soon.
We actually added a guest mode last night,
which lets us, lets anyone kind of jump in
and try the game before signing in.
So we're gonna see if we can get that live,
and hopefully our database can handle the load.
And let's see here.
Yeah, so we have basically like a card-based
little battler game that we ended up with,
with little cute art styles
that are inspired by our bots.
Actually the PR I was just kicking off
while we were talking is to adjust
some of the art styles here.
So this looks a little bit more like a card
with the art filling up more of the page.
But you can see these bots have sort of stats
that they get assigned.
And so we have a pool of these bots.
And the concept of the game is basically
that you choose your lineup
and then over the course of a couple of rounds
are pitted head to head against another player,
all sort of, you know,
with a matchmaking system and all that as well.
And so you're catching me mid game here.
Clearly some polished stuff here
that our factory is cranking on,
but I think this is pretty fun.
I think there's some really cool strategy elements to it
where you're sort of like trying to make a lineup
that you think is going to win.
It looks like I won that round.
At the start of every round as well,
you get like some gold.
I think we might want to rename that to like a token
or something.
Oh yeah, that's a good idea, we should do that, yeah.
But the idea is like you have this shop
where you can buy bots,
you can buy power-ups for your lineup.
You only have 10 gold to start,
but you know, you can add a new bot,
you can sell bots that you don't want.
They each have a different ability and skill
that does something different.
And then that's how you kind of play the game
and put some strategy in it
and go on until you win all three rounds.
And actually fun fact is that all of the bots here
are real bots from the bot marketplace,
the Groff bot marketplace.
So we got, I think there's like at least 70 of them
that we found.
And we generated avatars for all of them, unique ones.
And so it's kind of small right now,
but you have a lot of UI polish to do as you can see.
I think our boss will be able to take care of it though.
I think we know exactly what we need to change.
There's some CSS issues here, some clipping issues,
but hey, I just won that one.
So that's good, the Elo bump.
Yeah, there we go.
Number one for the leaderboard first time.
I've been in second place on the leaderboard the entire day.
We've been testing this out.
I got to catch up.
Yeah, we have some tiers here too.
So yeah, hopefully we'll give you a chance to compete
to make it to the platinum tier, which would be really fun.
And if you're just joining us,
you might've missed the first 10 minutes
where we gave away free Groff bot ultra.
But I think I'm going to try to convince the team
that maybe when we launched the game,
if we have a leaderboard, it'd be really cool
if we gave away more ultra plans
for like people on the top of the leaderboard.
See what we can do.
So let me see what I can do.
I'll try to convince our team whether we can do that.
But yeah, very excited to get that done.
Yeah, I guess maybe before.
So we're gonna, just to give you guys a bit of a,
what's going to happen in the next few minutes here.
So at 9 a.m. Pacific in about six minutes here,
we're going to cut over to the main stage.
So for those of you who have not been following along
for the three days, we're doing a bunch of stuff.
It's all happening live in person.
We are here in San Francisco,
just like a half block away from all
of the Dreamforce festivities.
And so we have a streaming studio upstairs in this space
where we've been building and cranking away.
We also have a main stage downstairs
where we've been doing talks about how you can use
Grokbot for like every part of your business.
And so we've been cutting out to those streams
and actually bringing that content
into building our own business.
So we're gonna cut over to one of those talks
in just a few minutes and give you all a chance to hear
about how you can use Grokbot for marketing
and marketing operations.
And then we'll bring marketing operations up here
to chat with our colleague to go into how we do that
for our launch.
So hopefully we can kind of tie in some of that knowledge.
But what are we gonna do off camera?
So I think we should maybe give the viewers a bit
of a plan for what we'll do in the next hour
or so before we're back on stream.
I know I wanna take care of some UI polish.
I feel like that's gonna be my focus.
Well, so my factory spent, I guess my team of bots
spent a lot of time last night working on the backend
and making sure we are secure and hopefully
performant enough to handle a lot of players at the same time.
So I think I will do some more testing of that,
make sure we can actually launch.
Load tests, hopefully lots and lots of load tests.
I might help off the UI polish too
because actually I'm a very like,
I do a lot of like client and UI work.
So I always get like nerds sniped by UI things
because I think, yeah, like the feel of the game
is like so important to make it fun.
So I wanna definitely do that.
Sweet, then I have some user feedback loops.
So ideally we'll have a way for you guys
to submit feature requests,
submit what you like, what you don't like.
And then we'll show how we can collect that information,
store it safely, service it to the team
and then implement kind of what we think is important,
which I think is, you know,
collecting user feedback and understanding
what people are saying is essential to product development.
Well, one thing that I think we wanna do
over the course of the day is actually continue
to update the app.
And so we're not gonna just launch this and walk away.
We're gonna, I think we have a really long roadmap already.
Last night, actually, before we cut out,
we spent some time doing audio design
and we have a bot, had a bot whose job it was
to help us with audio engineering.
And so we can revisit that bot.
We haven't had a chance to prioritize music yet,
but I think we can end up with some really cool tracks
that we generated with Suno.
And so maybe we work some of that in,
maybe a stretch goal for our launch,
but hopefully afterwards we can add some music.
We promise we won't make it annoying.
Nice, nice, great music.
He has a ton of stuff there.
We had a bot who was off doing some 3D prototyping
for how we might make the whole animation system more 3D
and make our characters more 3D.
And so I think it'd be great to revisit that idea if we can.
So yeah, a bunch of ideas that we can kind of cook with
over the course of the day.
And I think we'll have a lot to do, so.
Yeah.
I'd love to see, you know, ideas in the chat as well.
Like if you, I guess, caught a glimpse of our game
and you have suggestions on UI polish
or questions about mechanics or, I don't know,
any cool suggestions would be fun to read.
And then also, I think I want to actually shout out
production team, because today we have a very special,
I guess, livestream, because we have like a live agenda
and our bots up on the screen, which is super cool.
So Steve right there, oh, you just missed it.
Steve is my chief of staff bot
who is running the show.
Who's bot is Cupcake and?
That's my bot.
Oh, that's your bot.
And I also renamed my chief of staff bot to Steve.
Oh, really?
Because I was giving Mermin Flack yesterday
for having his name chief of staff
and then my bot was named chief of staff.
And I was like, too many thieves of staff.
Okay, I can change mine.
You need something else.
What's a good name for chief of staff bot?
If not Steve.
I don't know.
What about Steven?
Steven?
What about?
It's Steven now.
Yeah, I don't know.
I think I guess it's Roshan.
And now look, we have notes from productions
coming through on this screen.
Love it.
Yeah, I think every day we're building a business,
a production team building a production company.
There's a lot of like cool building
and evolution happening here.
Amazing, amazing.
Well, I think we're three minutes away
from our first talk of the day.
That's gonna be Grokbot for marketing operations.
If you're just joining us,
this is day three launch day of building a business.
In three days, we're building a gaming studio
and launching our first game really, really soon.
And we'll have a little more to share on that
very, very quickly here.
We're excited to open this up
and give everyone a chance to start playing
and helping us improve it.
So we can put your feedback
into our automated feature factory that we've built.
So really excited to get into that.
Yeah, I think we have some plans
for the next few hours.
Is that an error we need to fix?
This is an error on my side that we need to fix.
So it looks like,
I don't know if it works for your account.
I'm down on login with X.
So we got some work to do in the next hour here
and we're gonna get on it.
Pieces are there.
I feel good.
The pieces are there.
Awesome.
Cool.
I guess we're going downstairs.
We got a minute.
So I'm gonna, basically what I'm doing
is when I see an error like this,
I'm sure Lauren has a way of
that's automated this already.
I'm kind of like looking to see
what's going on on the server side
and then maybe passing that off to Grokbot
and letting it know.
Yeah, I mean, you can even
tell Grokbot to open that and it's...
Yeah.
And so there's really no limitation to the work that you can hand off to it, and I think this will only become more true over time as the models improve.
And so, as I mentioned, there's really that ease of use that you get with Grok Bot.
You have these always-on agents where you no longer have to worry for any of you who are out there who are maybe doing work at an inconvenient time, but you can't close your laptop because if you do, then the agent is going to stop working.
You don't have that concern here.
And really, when you combine all these primitives together, you get to a place where, in this really natural way, you talk to your bots, you know the access that they have.
They're really intelligent. They can keep working around the clock and produce some really high-value outputs for you.
So I'm really excited, particularly for this audience, to share a few use cases that I have personally that the RevOps and MarOps team internally at SpaceX AI has for using Grok Bot to do our work more effectively.
So first, a quick show of hands for people here in person.
How many of you are on your RevOps or MarOps team at your company?
Anyone working on GTM engineering, GTM systems?
Okay, workflows, processes, automations. I'm sort of speaking the same language as all of you, seeing some nods in the audience.
Well, what's really exciting about Grok Bot for RevOps and MarOps is I can sort of go through all of these.
Some of these I'm going to demo in just a second, but if I had to call out just one to really highlight about how a tool like Grok Bot changes the nature of our work,
is we can finally build tools and not just rules.
So oftentimes, when you're in these roles that are inherently about cross-functional collaboration and aligning stakeholders, so much of the job is just communicating information out,
hoping that people follow guidelines for the right way to set up a campaign, the right way to get something tracked.
But finally, with a tool like Grok Bot, we can all think of ourselves as much more technical to the point where we're not just setting out the guidelines for,
hey, if someone at the company wants to get XYZ campaign done, they have to follow this checklist.
And instead, we can set up the infrastructure, the internal apps where those teams can do the work.
And the apps are just set up to respect those rules in the first place.
And so you can sort of think of the marketing and sales teams as playing a game that you are designing as that sort of back office ops team.
But really, across all of these use cases that we're highlighting here, there's really so much to do that really fundamentally changes the nature of the work.
And so I want to walk all of you through a demo of some specific ways that I use Grok Bot to highlight a couple of those use cases from the prior slide.
And before we do that, I just want to introduce you to my team of bots.
So there are some obscure references here with the names of my bots.
I don't know if by any chance there are any Radiohead fans out there in the audience.
Amazing. So maybe you would understand the reference to owned over there. It's a beloved instrument.
But all of these are sort of references to music devices in another life.
I might have pursued that passion a bit more, but now I can do that with my bots.
And so we've got OP1, my sort of synthesizer chief of staff, who drives a lot of my work.
We've got Fisher, which is sort of the receiver of all the information from across my inboxes, email, calendar, text messages, Slack.
Juno is my product manager bot that sort of helps me think through corner cases, product requirements when I'm going out and thinking of tools that I want to build for our marketing and sales teams.
It helps me really think through all the implications and build the right thing in the first place.
And then owned is my engineer bot.
So it has a really clear sense of our systems, how they interact with each other, things like the CRM and our data warehouse and our existing code base and how we build internal tools at SpaceX AI.
And so what you'll see in a second here in our demo is, first, I want to show you what I call the self-completing task list.
So this, to me, I'm sort of a productivity nerd.
For over half a decade, I've been building my own internal systems for getting work done more efficiently because especially in a role like RevOps or MarOps.
As I said earlier, so much of it is just stakeholder management.
You're getting so many messages from so many different places, trying to make sense of it, trying to understand what is truly high priority.
And finally, with a tool like RockBot, what you can do is you can set up these bots to monitor all your inboxes and help you distill, okay, of all these messages you've received, things that showed up on your calendar, which of these are actual tasks versus which of these are just FYIs
or things that we can safely ignore.
And so what we'll do here is we can see my bots have already been active in the background.
So Fisher, the sort of executive assistant or receiver agent that's tapped in to all my inboxes, we can see today at 904 a.m., it completed this ongoing routine that it has.
You can see over here it has this regular routine that it runs on a schedule where it checks all my inboxes and picks out whatever's new.
And then it proactively, actually like while I was giving this talk, messaged OP1, again, that's my chief staff agent, and it gave it the rundown of across email, calendar, work chat, all the information that came my way.
And so this alone is such an unlock in terms of knowing, like I can, even if I wanted to, I could turn notifications off on Slack, on email, and I would just know that in the background, my bots are monitoring those channels for me and surfacing to me the things that are most important that should really take away my attention.
And that alone really cuts down on the context switching for me and really helps me get into much more of a focus mode in my work and just be a lot happier in my work.
So really, really cool, right? That alone changes the game. And then what you see here is Fisher is receiving this information. It's proactively telling my chief of staff, hey, here's what's new.
And then my chief of staff is distilling that down into the actual tasks and subtasks that I was able to identify from that input.
So, right, sometimes you get messages and you don't actually have to act on them. Sometimes you get messages and you have to act on them, but you can't really tell just by reading the message alone, like what's really going on here.
And so with bot, what you can do is it reads the message, it reads the entire Slack exchange, and it sort of distills for you like, hey, I think here's what that person is asking for.
And so it just makes your life so much easier.
Now here's the really cool thing is this is where we get to the self completing part of the of the self completing task list is my two bots Fisher and OP one are working together to identify tasks.
And then OP one identifies one of those tasks looks like there's a territory dispute, a couple AEs have some disagreements about who should work a given account.
And what OP one can do is relay that task to another bot that I have, which is a territory planning bot.
It can give it context on what's going on. And then that territory planner bot who has full information on our rules of engagement, how we set out different territories, all the context from our CRM, that bot is able to complete a pretty good first draft of that task of what deliverable is needed to complete that task.
And so I didn't even have to think about, you know, what, what we should do about this territory dispute. Of course, I can always come in and validate the work and make sure that it actually makes sense.
But it's really amazing to think that, like, I have a team, I truly have a team, a team that is monitoring my inboxes distilling the tasks relaying those tasks to the right other teammates who can get them done for me.
And then I just come in and sort of oversee the whole process and finalize things.
So that's demo one.
Demo two is really how I was able to build what, to put it in a pithy way, is a dating app for leads that we use internally at SpaceX AI, where, you know, often, for those of you in the audience who know what I'm talking about, marketing sales handoff is like such a classic
group in companies where marketing is producing all these leads. Salespeople are like, I don't really love these leads. I don't want to have to work them. So they're just sitting there getting stale.
You don't really have a feedback loop where marketing can refine their targeting to give sales more of the kind of leads that they want. And the whole process is just broken.
And so I sort of identified a better way to handle the marketing sales handoff, which is what if every AE could log into an app and they would just see the leads that they own?
They can swipe left to end those leads. When they end those leads, they have to give a specific ended reason. When they hit submit, it actually writes back to the CRM in all the correct ways.
When they swipe right, they can add that prospect. They can add that lead directly into a follow-up sequence. And so this is what I mean when earlier on I said this really transforms what we can do as someone on RevOps or MarOps,
where all of a sudden we're not just talking about SLAs and making sure that the sales teams abide by the SLAs and, hey, why aren't you working these leads?
And, okay, let me relay that anecdotal information about these leads back to the marketing team. Instead, we just set up the game for the teams to play.
They play that game, and we get a lot of really valuable information on, okay, why are these leads being ended?
How can we sort of programmatically feed that back into the marketing teams to improve the targeting and give sales more of the leads they like?
How can we make it as easy as possible for salespeople so that this is something fun that they want to get to inbox zero with their leads every day?
So the way that we did this was I basically told my product manager bot, I want to build an internal app for sales reps to review their leads.
I gave it a rough idea of the mechanics for the app, some extra things that I want.
And most importantly, from the start, we really want to get this off flow with our CRM right, because that's sort of the most critical thing.
We want salespeople to be able to log in and see the leads they own and make sure that we're writing information back into the CRM properly.
So what happens when I send this message is Juno is a really good thought partner for me.
So I have this rough idea for an app.
And with prior AI tools, what might have happened is the AI really wants to please me.
It really wants to do a good job.
And so right away, it jumps into, okay, I'm starting the coding process.
Here it is, and maybe it doesn't look like what you envisioned.
Maybe it doesn't work like what you envisioned.
Maybe it anchored too much on what you had in that first prompt.
And so in a way, you're sort of scared to use the AI and overthinking, like, did I get that prompt right?
Did I need to give it more detail in the first place?
Oh, no, now it's running away and building the wrong thing.
What Grokbot does is it takes a second.
It asks you follow-up questions, really good follow-up questions, things that I didn't necessarily think about when I first had the idea for this app.
And so we can answer these questions.
We'll see it.
It'll ask a few more.
We can go through this process.
Let's see.
I want to show people only their new leads, no additional filters.
We want to make sure, okay, so this is a really good question.
When a lead is accepted, what should change in the CRM?
Now, what I want to tell Bot is, actually, we shouldn't change any fields in the CRM when a lead is accepted because the real moment that the lead status changes is when the rep reaches out.
We already have an automation for tracking that activity and updating the lead status.
So we're really getting in the weeds here, and the AI, the Grokbot, is really prompting me to think more deeply about my idea and to say, hey, you know what?
That's a good point.
I'm not just answering questions mindlessly, but I'm really thinking through some of the implications here.
Let's do reason and optional notes.
And there will probably be just one or two more questions that it'll ask.
Let's see.
Offline actions.
Great question.
Let's queue and confirm before done.
So then we'll see that this product manager bot will come up with a spec for our product.
And not only that, but let's do local only here.
Not only will it come up with the spec, but what we'll see in just a second is, well, I won't spoil anything.
So we can see it's drafting the product spec.
And actually, it's sort of giving it away.
So what Juno is going to do for me is it's going to write the spec and then proactively hand it off to own our engineering bot to actually get the build started.
And again, I think the really magical thing here is I didn't have to prompt Juno to do that.
Often when you're using AI tools, if you even get to this point of thought partnership and producing really good quality outputs, you have to take those outputs and send them into the right new system.
If you even have a consistent bot that you go to that just does your engineering work.
And here you can, again, really think of it as a team that's working on your behalf to get things done end to end.
So it messaged, owned, it has this product spec ready for the engineering to begin.
And now we can see that our engineers off to work.
And now sort of cooking demo style, I'll show you what the finished product looks like, since I won't bore you with all the details of on doing the build.
But what we've got here, this is all fake data. So no worries here.
This is just a mock up of the real interface that I was able to build with Grokbot and that many of our reps now use on a daily basis to get their reviewed leads down to zero.
And so we've got all this information available at a glance about the lead.
We can simply put the card to the left to end that lead.
We can swipe to the right and we can put that lead in a sequence.
We can see more information about how the lead came in in the first place.
And it just works already since introducing this new app to our sales reps, which, by the way, went from idea to implementation in just two weeks.
The live build time was really 10 hours and then a lot of the other time was spent just introducing people to this tool, getting them familiar with it, gathering more feedback and feature requests.
In the two weeks since we've adopted this on the team, we've seen our leads reviewed rate shoot up.
The AEs love it. Marketing teams love it because they're finally getting high quality feedback from sellers on how they can improve targeting.
And we can see how working with Grokbot really elevates what we can do.
Show of hands out there in the audience, how many of you feel like without AI you would be able to build a product like this?
Amazing. Okay. Right. We got one hand.
Now I would say with AI, and especially after seeing this demo, how many of you feel like you could pretty confidently go into a chat with AI and build this or any other internal tool that you need?
Amazing. Amazing. I'm seeing a lot of hands now. And that was exactly neat.
I really joined this team with a lot of ideas for how we could improve processes, with a lot of specialized knowledge around specific tools where I just knew the menus and buttons to use.
But I'm at a point now where what I'm using more than anything is just my brain to really think critically about what do we need as a team and how we can be more efficient.
So now I really want to distill what we learn from that demo.
And really, some of the big lessons are if you were able to hire a full team, if someone came to you and said you have headcount to hire a full team of people reporting to you, who would be on it?
Really what Grokbot does is it democratizes in a way that CEO life.
Anyone can hire an unlimited set of specialists with the right context and access.
I think this is really powerful for our day-to-day in terms of just dreaming bigger about what we can each do for the teams that we're on.
The next lesson is really to trust your bots, give them agency, and at the same time give them guardrails.
So there's something really powerful about knowing really confidently all the access that your bots have, all the things that they can do for you, because that helps you entrust them with bigger and bigger tasks.
But at the same time, knowing that things aren't going to go too far off the rails, because they'll always come back to you before they ship anything.
Messages writing back to the CRM, pushing PRs, and I think Grokbot really helps you achieve that balance between pushing AI tools to the limit and then running into issues, or feeling like, I don't really know what access it has, I don't know how helpful it can really be.
So I haven't really started using it yet.
The final thing, and this is really, I think, more of a call to action than anything for those of you out in the audience whose role is similar to mine, is think of yourselves not as just the people setting rules, processes, but really you are a product manager and your product is revenue growth.
I am extremely excited about where the RevOps, MarOps, GTM engineering, GTM systems, whatever you want to call it, where this profession is headed, and I think that's particularly relevant with Dreamforce going on this week, is all of us are thinking about the systems that our GTM efforts are built on.
And I think in this new world, where all of us have access to tools like Grokbot, it means we can think of ourselves as identifying any bottlenecks to growth and getting rid of them.
That's our job day in and day out, is just talking to teams, doing the human thing, forming relationships, building trust, distilling what needs to be built to help the teams grow more effectively, operate more effectively, and then going and building those things.
So that's it for the main presentation.
We're going to have some time for questions next.
Thank you so much for joining. All right, so we have some people with microphones.
So WhatsApp is a nice tool for marketing, right? WhatsApp.
And I'm able to get WhatsApp working on Grokbot by connecting with my own personal one. Is there a connector that makes it easier to do in some way? What's your suggestion for working with WhatsApp with Grokbot?
Yeah, I'm not sure if we have a connector on the way that's native to WhatsApp.
There are other tools I use. This is not to particularly promote one over others, but sort of speaking personally, there's a tool called Beeper that I'm not sure if you're familiar with, but it's basically like a mega chat app that you can log into all your separate messaging apps.
And you can actually install that on your bots computer. So again, this is a really magical thing about Grokbot is you don't need to have native connections to anything.
You can just go into Grokbot's computer, install whatever app you want, and then it can use those apps just like you would.
I presume the same might be true for the WhatsApp app.
We're connectors to like meta or something like, you know, we spend a lot on meta and Google, but having those just natively like, you know, easy authenticate connect, I think is like a massive unlock because it keeps just logging out, right?
But do you have an idea on like the kind of roadmap for when those will come online or? Yeah.
Yeah, so there are certain things that I'm not able to go into, just in terms of what's on the way. But one thing that we did announce just yesterday is a one password integration.
So you're able to share your password vault with your bot. And what you could do if you're really open to it is you could set up a routine for a given bot to, like, sort of track whether the token is still active, whether the login is still active on a tool.
And if you need to re-auth, then you can have it re-auth for you using what's in the one password vault.
Okay, because I think like, yeah, the key insight, at least for like us too, is like we want like, let's say, meta or its search ads.
We wanted to monitor how the ads doing, increase, decrease spend, and then potentially create a new ad, you know, because it can like it's actually like I haven't building ads that I have to manually post.
But then if it could start running in that circle, that's like our dream state.
Yeah, exactly. Yeah, and I think it's really about breaking down into, you know, the other really appealing thing to me about this particular perch in looking at all these developments in AI is like, fundamentally, what our role is about is understanding systems and processes and workflows to begin with.
I think that's true even before the world of AI is we're sort of always bringing that systems approach to how does this get done and how can it get done even better.
And I think by leaning into that tendency that we already have, we can help the AI tools codify those processes into these like actual automations that are running on our behalf.
So, when I think about automating complex jobs and I spend a lot of time thinking about like, okay, what are the fundamental
So why don't we open up the portal and see what's going on?
So yeah, so it's really important to look at all of the data that we have in the
portal, like blocks of doing this task.
So maybe the first chunk is, like, being able to log into that platform and look
at the analytics and then the second chunk is, and download a report, and then
the second chunk is, OK, now look at that data in the context of all the other
detailed instructions for how to do things,
the better off you'll be building bots around them
because you can give it clarity,
you can sort of have separate specialized bots
for each portion of the job
and then have them all work in tandem like you saw before.
Yeah, I have a question.
So if the bot just keep evolving,
what do you think would be the market stack
that's gonna disappear first?
And how do you think about the relationship
between bots and human?
Yeah, I think of it,
I really think of it a lot as a mirror.
Oftentimes when I'm talking to bots,
especially in one of those thought partnership sessions
like you saw with the Q&A,
I think of the bot as, of course in some ways,
it's influencing how I think about what I'm trying to do.
So like it might bring up certain aspects
of the build for that app that I didn't think of myself,
but ultimately it's then prompting me to do that thinking.
And I'm like, huh, okay, yeah, good point.
And now I'm thinking about it,
now I'm really engaged with it.
And now my engagement with that thought
breeds more thoughts and more ideas.
And then I just share that with the bot
and then it has more context to work off of.
And so you can think of it as like,
if nothing else, you're sort of like thinking out loud
with these bots and they're giving you,
they're, you know, in some ways we prompt AI,
in some ways AI is prompting us to think more deeply
about what we're trying to accomplish with it.
So that's what I think about,
like the relationship between me and the bot
or any one who uses GrokBot.
In terms of the stack that I think will go away,
it's sort of hard to say.
I think there will probably still be many instances
of like, it's really good to just understand
the right buttons to click and menus to navigate
to use certain complex tools.
But I think something that's sort of happened,
especially with coding,
is like the barrier to entry is so much lower.
I think the engineering profession
have this sort of reckoning over the past few years
that more and more professions are gonna start to have
with the introductions of these kinds of tools
around like, okay, what do I do
if my role is no longer just being the gatekeeper
of this like really complicated looking code
that no one else understands?
Like now all of a sudden anyone can produce that code.
And so what's the value add of an engineer?
There is a value add, there definitely is,
but that value add is more about that higher level thinking,
that intuitive feel for the systems.
And so I think it's helpful to really get
to know the tools deeply because of similar to before,
like what it prompts you to think about.
Like no one really wants to be a master
at navigating menus,
but there's something about that tedious work
that really makes you slow down
and think about what you're trying to do
in those complex tools,
just like AI also prompts you to slow down and think.
So I think that is what's gonna remain.
I think using complex tools to the extent
that it gives you deep familiarity with your profession
and expertise and taste, I think that will persist.
But I also think that in many ways
there'll be a lot less button clicking
wiring things up properly and setting up the integrations.
So a little bit vague,
but hopefully you sort of understand
philosophically what I mean.
Yeah, thank you.
I'll throw one from an enterprise solutions,
large organization type idea,
but I've got my Grokbot, he's got his,
we're both working on a similar project,
whatever it might be.
How best should we approach or think about
having the agents work in harmony
so we don't have to do as much?
And then on top of that,
I'm using Grok myself and it's learning how I think
and how I'm doing things and how I'm approaching things
at a brilliant level, it's fantastic.
But it's individual to me,
so how I approach a project may be very different
how he approaches it.
So how should we think about synergies between the two?
Yeah, on this front,
there's something that I can't quite get ahead of
anything at the company and announce,
but I think we'll have something really exciting
to address this pretty shortly.
It's all good, I'll say it,
we're just waiting for multiplayer, we want cod, you know.
The team is working hard to build a lot more cool stuff.
You probably also can't answer as well,
where are you gonna get Grokbot on Tesla?
Oh, on Tesla?
I can't answer that, unfortunately.
But I appreciate the excitement.
My parents have Teslas,
so believe me, they're asking me that question too.
Yeah.
Any other questions?
One question for Max,
how can we get the Juno template?
The Juno template?
I can definitely provide any of these bots
that you saw here today as templates afterwards.
We can figure out the logistics
and get that to the right people after the stream.
One last question.
What has been the feedback from the sales team
on the lead dating app that you created?
So they love it.
They really do.
Everyone was like, this is crazy.
Just the idea of being on the subway on the way to work
and I'm swiping left and right
and someone's looking over my shoulder
and has no clue what I'm using,
but I'm working through my leads.
I'm building pipeline.
Come on, guys.
So people really love the concept.
I think it's reflected in the numbers.
We, like I mentioned earlier,
within a couple weeks of introducing this,
hit record highs in terms of lead review rates.
So I think that sort of shows it all.
Sales reps are working through their backlogs,
getting to inbox zero,
and the tool really helps them do it way, way better
than clicking through five different menus,
opening up five tabs to look into this lead
and what ad do they even see when they became a lead
and all these different things,
only to then have to click through three more menus
and end the lead properly.
Clearly, that was not something they were a fan of.
So they really love it.
One really funny thing that I heard from a rep was,
yeah, I'm pretty sure I don't need
another dating app in my life.
And my reaction was, well, at least this is a dating app
where if you get the date,
it could actually earn you money.
You don't have to spend money on this date.
So they really love it,
and I can see many ways that it could expand
and really be one command center from Signal to SQL.
So this is really just the beginning,
and it's really exciting to have that
ability to keep building more and more and more
thanks to a tool like RockBot.
Awesome.
Well, I think that is our time.
Now, one last, oh, one more question.
Yeah, last question.
Thank you for the presentation.
What tasks should remain human-owned,
even if it's capable bots?
One, what tasks should remain human-owned
is the question, yeah.
You know, more and more over time,
it becomes clear how much relationships matter.
I mean, we've always known this as human beings.
We are social creatures.
We want to form relationships.
I think, you know, how many of you in the room
like knew what RevOps or MarOps was
when you were four years old?
Okay, no hands.
How many of you would you say you like a thousand percent
today, a thousand percent know what RevOps and MarOps is?
No hands, okay?
These are concepts that we created as human beings
to solve certain problems.
And those concepts that we created
were around being really specialized
in certain tools or processes.
I think what it always comes back to
is forming relationships, building trust,
and solving problems no matter what it takes,
whether that's having a certain title,
using certain tools,
or whether that's just like figuring it out on the fly.
I think those things will always remain our job.
So we should just keep doing that thing,
leaning into our instincts.
I think there will always be plenty
of human work to do in that vein.
So you're all seeing this on the screen.
I'm really excited to announce to all of you,
we just launched this challenge.
It's live on X.
And the way this challenge works
is you can share a Grokbot
that you simply cannot live without.
And then you and a guest could be headed
to Starbase in Texas for the rare chance
to watch a Starship launch in person.
This is really exciting.
When we came up with this challenge internally,
we were all like, can we enter also?
Oh my God, how does this work?
And so all you have to do to enter
is just go on X, follow at Grok,
and at bot,
and then quote our challenge post.
I think that's what you'll reach
if you scan that QR code.
So quote the post,
give a description of your Grokbot
and a link to your shared bot template.
And basically, good luck,
and see what happens,
and hope to see you all
at many more events like this in the future.
It's been really fun talking to you all today.
Thanks.
🎵 Just like your electric eyes are everywhere 🎵
🎵 Honey, do it like that, be a superhero 🎵
🎵 Do it like that, baby 🎵
🎵 Life like limit 🎵
🎵 I've lost the moment 🎵
🎵 Lost USA 🎵
🎵 Plucked her eyebrows on the way 🎵
🎵 Shaved her legs 🎵
🎵 And then he was a sheesh 🎵
🎵 She says, hey, babe 🎵
🎵 Take a walk on the wild side 🎵
🎵 Said, hey, honey 🎵
Okay, we're back.
Welcome back, everyone.
Hope you've enjoyed the morning so far.
We are cranking away at deploying our game.
And so for those who are just joining us,
got a team of SpaceX AI folks here.
We are on day three of our three-day mission
to launch a game studio in our very first game.
The idea here is that we were using Grokbot
to power and build a game from,
or build a business from scratch.
And kind of going through the last few days of ideation
have settled on a game studio and a game.
So I'm pretty excited for those of you
who have deployed production apps,
web apps into production with a tight timeline.
You might understand some of the things
that we're working through right now.
So Lauren and Matt are cranking away at all kinds of stuff.
I figured we'd hop back on and kind of tell you
a little bit about where we are in the process
and kind of just walk you through what's going on.
So you get a feel for what's happening behind the scenes.
We are currently managing a bunch of client secrets
and web secrets.
And so we probably won't show our screens
a little for at least a little bit, you know,
just we're not, we're not gonna deploy
live production secrets on stream.
So sorry for anyone who was hoping to get that out of us,
but basically what we've built
is a sort of card battler style game.
We showed this a little bit earlier as a preview.
We're actually doing a really great UI polish pass
that we're really excited about.
So hopefully I'm gonna give everything
a fresh coat of paint, make our cards look super slick.
Lower your expectation.
Okay, okay, okay.
It looks a little bit better,
but I mean, still a lot of improvement.
And so maybe that brings me to the plan for the day,
which is, you know, we're here in San Francisco
live at Grockbach Galaxy.
We're in this beautiful space.
It's a bunch of stuff happening in person.
We have a bunch of talks happening downstairs.
We have our little studio space set up upstairs
in this space.
And we're gonna be cutting back and forth
through a bunch of content throughout the day.
We might have some guests on today.
For those of you who've been tuned in for the three days,
you know, we've been kind of mixing it up as we go,
bringing in some experts in the industry
on how to build a business,
bringing in some folks around, you know,
from SpaceX AI who are experts in working with Grockbach
and kind of showing you some of their presentations as well.
And so we'll keep cutting over to stuff as we go.
And, you know, what we really wanna do
is get this app live and get all of your feedback.
So Matt earlier this morning
was working on some feedback channels.
We're gonna make a way so we can get your feedback
that you're experiencing while you're playing the game
and using the product into the app.
I'm gonna talk a little bit more
about monetization this afternoon
and bring in some SpaceX AI folks
who can help us with the marketing plan and revenue plan.
So I'm pretty excited about that if we get the chance.
But then really just wanna get the app live
and be able to iterate based on your feedback.
And so we're hoping we'll do is ship
a little bit of a play test in the next little while.
Get the play test live
and then kind of once we have that live,
go and really just ship and iterate.
So, you know, I think there's the classic startup line
where if you're not embarrassed by it,
it's not ready for prime time.
So definitely some stuff we're embarrassed by, I think,
but that's a good thing.
We're gonna turn that into a good thing.
Get it live and be able to just iterate throughout the day.
So lots of opportunities to add polish,
lots of opportunities to add new features.
Really just wanna make sure we can make something really fun
that folks are excited to play with
and building something that people want.
And that's where we are right now.
Just to give you a sense of what's happening
in the actual deployment process.
So we're using a bunch of different tools
to make this come to life.
So we've been using GrokBox,
obviously is our core driver for the business.
We have a team of GrokBox doing everything
from managing our software factory
where we have automatic bug fixes,
automatic play tests, automatic reviews.
And we have, let's maybe not show screens
if that's okay while we're working.
Thank you, thank you.
Automatic bug fixes, automatic PR reviews happening.
We have any good game, we need some play testing.
And so we have play testing happening
and we have bots that are kind of doing
all these various things,
kind of put together in a little bit of an engine.
And so anytime we catch a bug in production,
a bot can notice that and can go ahead
and prompt a cloud agent to go and fix it
and make a PR for it.
And we have a play tester bot
who will pick up that change,
run it through the game engine,
make sure that everything is working well
and then kind of approve the PR
in addition to the other approval steps
and our continuous integration suite.
So all that is powered by a combination
of Brock bots and GitHub working together.
But we're obviously gluing together
a bunch of other stuff to make this work too.
But math's working on right now
is getting authentication working with clerk.
And so we had a clerk developer account
that we set up in order to get login with X to work.
So we're gonna support login with X on the product
where folks can log in and participate in a leaderboard.
So hopefully you guys get a chance to sign in.
You'll be able to play the game.
Each player will get an ELO score.
So depending on how it goes over time,
you'll hopefully be able to increase your rank in the game.
We're pretty excited about that.
And so we'll be able to make that leaderboard available
to folks who sign in with Twitter.
We also have a practice mode in the app.
And so what Matt's working on right now
is getting our clerk configuration cleaned up,
making sure that we have all the domains
pointing in all the right ways,
all the DNS records set up in all the right ways.
We were joking off camera, it's always DNS.
And so we were just debugging a DNS issue
right before this.
And it's sometimes always cores.
And so we're also debugging a cross-origin issue as well.
And so again, for those of you
who have deployed apps into prod, managed large web apps,
I think you can probably commiserate
with some of these issues.
So yeah, we have clerk
that's helping handle our authentication.
We're using Vercel as our hosting provider here.
And so that's been really great.
We have a bunch of Vercel settings
that obviously when you flip
from development to production mode,
we've been kind of testing each PR.
That's how our play tester bot handles testing
is by kind of accessing those Vercel preview links.
But going to production obviously involves
hardening the app a little bit,
making sure we have great database control,
great ingress control, egress control,
security ratcheted down the way we need.
And then obviously off working with clerk,
DNS setup and all that good stuff.
And so all those things are in progress.
We do have a domain name, which we're pretty excited about,
but we're gonna hold off on sharing that for now
until we get the product live.
And so coming soon, we'll reveal the name.
And yeah, other than that,
we have kind of like all the infra getting ready to go.
So we've also been running a bunch of load tests
against our database.
We're using PlanetScale as a database provider here.
We have a series of databases we've set up
to handle the core games store.
And we're basically, look,
I think last night actually ran a bunch of load tests
against the database.
We're doing some production hardening this morning
to make sure things are in a good spot there as well.
Trying to think of what else we have in our stack.
For those who weren't around yesterday,
we've also have an entire operation stack
around the business.
So we have a Slack channel or actually a Slack team
where we have a Bug Reports channel.
I'm actually seeing some Bug Reports filter in right now,
which is pretty great.
What's really nice about these systems
when you get bots talking to your other tools
is that they can use those tools just like humans would,
but they're often a lot faster at using them than humans are.
And so one common workflow that we use a ton internally
at SpaceX AI is we have feedback channels
and issues channels for our products.
Anytime someone posts an issue,
we have triage bots whose job it is to go in,
take a look at the issue, see if it's reproducible,
look at some logs in our internal logging systems,
kind of come back with, well,
is this something that needs a fix?
Do I need to tag the right person
who might be able to help advise on this?
And those are really cool systems
because it can sort of shorten the time period
between something being reported
and then getting to a fix.
And very often saves a lot of engineering work
where someone has to go manually look
through a bunch of logs.
So I'm trying to replicate some of those behaviors
for this app, basically creating a Slack space,
making it so that anytime we see an issue
or anytime one of you reports an issue,
we can just automatically fire a bot
to take a look at that,
see if it's a real issue, reproducible,
look at logs and then kind of come back with a PR
versus just coming back with an investigation
or a dashboard that someone else has to go
and write some code for.
So that, earlier today,
you heard us talking about the software factory.
And I think that's really what that is in practice.
It's sort of this automated software development loop,
you know, and really for production apps,
apps that are out in the field.
So it's so important, right?
Because, you know, no software is perfect, you know,
but we don't intentionally put bugs in software,
but bugs exist.
And so a large part of the work of an engineering team
is kind of looking at issues that exist,
kind of making sure that we're seeing those issues come in,
being able to triage them, fix them,
and then continue to do that while evolving the product.
And so you'll see another set of issues,
well, hopefully not too many, but we're going to...
We're trying to minimize issues.
We're also doing a UI rewrite.
So I don't know.
We rewrote the UI.
We just revamped our authentication stuff.
So when...
You flip from a development to production authentication.
There's a bunch of OAuth and callback stuff
you have to reconfigure.
And I don't know, it's an interesting lesson
because a big part of not just building a business,
but building software is connecting things together
and figuring out production environments
and what production is, how that's different from a development
environment.
And yeah, it's not always fun and just making stuff happen.
Sometimes it's literally figuring out the glue.
But agents are quite good for that
because previously, you would have
had to diagnose these issues manually,
which if anybody's tried to do this before,
it takes a lot of time.
And so having an agent understanding,
I think a larger point is all of the same skills
that apply in software engineering or running
a business still apply.
So if you think about what it means to be
able to debug something, previously, that was like,
OK, I'm going to understand all of the steps in a process.
And then I'm going to go through those manually one
by one until I kind of identify an error point.
And now we can lean on agents to help us do that.
But all the principles are kind of still the same,
which is between point A and point B,
there are x number of things that can go wrong.
And how do I think about where we are, where we're going,
and then where all of those sort of points are?
And I often describe this like fixing a lamp.
If a lamp is not working, the first question you should ask
is, is the light bulb working or is the bulb burnt out
and is it plugged in?
And if you can diagnose those two issues
and they're both working, then the issue
is somewhere in between those two.
And then your job as an engineer or someone
trying to fix this lamp, someone who's
trying to do it themselves, is to figure out
what point in that chain can go wrong.
And this is exactly the same with software.
So we have a lot of API keys and things floating around,
which is why we're kind of talking through this.
But these are good lessons.
And it's the same thing in business.
While you were talking, I know you've
been working on getting the clerk app working
in production.
I just signed in and I'm looking at the clerk dashboard.
Let's not show this on screen, please.
But we're looking at the clerk dashboard
and I see one active user.
So we have our first production app.
I'm the active user of production.
I'm playing a game right now, too.
OK, cool.
OK, maybe clerk dashboard is lagging behind.
I just lost that.
So essentially what we did was flip from dev to prod.
And now our prod instance has active users
and we're starting to get things working.
I see three active users.
OK, so we have user authentication.
We have a game engine.
I think that works, yeah.
I think that's working.
I think it just started working.
Yeah, what else is on our launch checklist?
So we were talking a little bit off stream
about all the things we need to do
to feel good to get this launch out to the world.
And so what are the things that are on our launch checklist?
And maybe what I can do is why don't I just
make a notion dock and we can just put together
this checklist right now.
I'm going to bug you guys a little bit.
I know your head's down, but let me see what I can do.
I'm going to pull up my screen.
And so now let's go ahead and cut to my screen if we can.
Actually, give me one second.
Let me just close some tabs.
There we go.
We're good.
OK.
And so for those who are not familiar,
we have a notion dock that we have been working on.
And yep, got it, got it, got it.
And we basically, yesterday, just to catch you guys up
on how we thought about managing the context for the company,
is that we ended up creating, well, it
looks like we have our agents have really done.
I think they need to be cleaned up.
Our agents have gone hard in here.
We also have a, here we go.
So yeah, we did create a sort of task board
that we've been using with our agents.
They've been logging data into a notion database.
This is a little messy, it looks like.
Where's my checklist that I'm looking for?
OK, we'll see if I can find it.
We have a working to-do list here.
We have a bunch of other company contacts
that we've been putting in, things
like our canonical database schema,
things like the source of truth for our game mechanics.
And these are just really helpful ways for bots
to be able to interact with other bots,
and to be able to interact with company context.
I think Lauren had a really great point on Tuesday
when we kicked off, which is like,
very often for coding agents, the code base
is the best source of context and memory.
And so that's obviously a huge part
of the actual software engineering loop.
But for many of the operational things,
it helps to be able to write docs.
And so we have a bunch of these docs that we've created.
What I want to do, though, now is make a launch checklist.
So let's just work through this live.
I think we need a few things.
We have to get authentication working.
I think that works now.
Authentication is working.
I just wanted to put something on the list I could check.
You can check that out.
Check completed.
Cool, cool, cool.
Do we want to land the UI rewrite before we?
I don't think we need to.
I think we should just check.
I mean, I feel like, should we launch it right now?
You're saying the checklist is that's it?
There's nothing else?
I mean, I think we could maybe set expectations.
This is like a first play test.
The UI is not very polished.
And we're not sure if things will break.
I'm actually pretty sure things will break.
Things were going to break.
Yeah, but I feel like we could probably, I don't know.
What do you think?
Should we polish it more?
What does chat think?
If do you want to play it right now?
Just as long as you understand that it's pretty,
it's not very polished at the moment.
I don't know.
I haven't clicked through it in a while.
So if you guys think it's ready, then.
How about this?
Why don't you go to your browser, hide the URL.
OK.
Maybe hide the URL.
Maybe turn off the screen for a second.
Yeah, why don't we turn off my screen share for a second?
Then you go to our app, our game, hide the URL,
and then see if you can play it.
Then we can show off playing it.
And if we feel good about it, let's just
share the URL with everyone in the chat
and do our first play test.
Cool.
We haven't renamed.
We'll do it live.
We've got to finish the rename.
OK, so if we want to go back to my screen, moment of truth,
let's see if things work.
We can put my screen back up.
Can you zoom in?
I think if I zoom in, it's going to cause some formatting
issues.
So let's try running it with default views right now.
These are the kinds of things that I think we need to clean up.
So if I hit Practice, we added a practice mode.
Maybe explain the game, because I
feel like we made so many changes, it's not clear.
Yeah, well, we need to add a tutorial.
I think that would be really cool.
Yeah, so essentially what we've built here
is sort of an auto battler style game,
where we have a set of preloaded cards.
These cards are all generated from RockBot templates.
And so we seeded a set of cards or a deck of cards
with abilities from the RockBot marketplace.
And this is really fun, where we have our office ops desk,
or a writing bot, or a dial bot.
Each of these cards have stats.
They have two key stats.
They have an attack stat and a health stat, like an HP stat.
And they all have an ability.
And so each card has a separate ability
that's been minted for that card.
And what's really cool about these
is that these abilities really modify the game place.
The way the game works is it takes place over three rounds.
In each round, you set your lineup of bots.
And so you kind of line your bots up.
And you're matched against another person
who's also set a lineup of bots.
And what the way this works is you basically spend,
you have a pool of gold that you use
that you're sort of spending over the course of the round.
So why don't I just show you the first round.
I'm going to just go ahead and buy three bots.
So I'll buy my office ops desk.
I guess that's a pretty small, by the way.
So you might want to just read out stuff.
Yeah, well, why don't I pinch and zoom?
That might be the lead.
Oh, yeah, perfect.
So we have our office ops desk card.
You can see that attack there.
You can see the health there.
And you can see up here that it's in the first spot
in our lineup.
It has this ability called hold the line.
It's pretty cool.
So when it gets hurt from the front of the line,
it'll restore one HP.
So it just basically can be a little damage tank for us.
And I don't know if I love these help techs,
but we can always do that.
That's what our card looks like.
We actually have a cool way we're going to modify that.
And so basically what I do here is I set my lineup.
So I got the office ops desk.
Earlier, if you saw the base cards cost three gold.
And so I start with 10 gold.
I'm down to seven now.
I see a bug.
And so you found a bug.
OK.
The names suddenly changed to unknown bot.
I don't know what happened there.
Oh, yeah, good point.
OK, that's a good catch.
That might be one we should fix.
We should probably fix that.
But you can still show the card.
Oh, 100%.
So here's an unknown bot that previously had a name.
Definitely has a cute image.
This bot is a 3-3 and is unknown and apparently had
an ability before.
Let me see if I buy it.
Make sure refresh and see.
OK, well, when I pick a bot, we get a bug.
Yeah, that's a bug.
I'll fix that.
There's Dialbot.
Dialbot is a 3-3 bot that has poke.
So any time the game starts, this bot
deals one damage to the enemy in the front lines.
And so what's cool about this game
is that basically you're setting a lineup.
And then the cards, the bots, all
have abilities that make it so that you can basically
modify the behavior of other bots in the other team's
lineup.
So the idea here is that it's sort of lineup
versus lineup with a bunch of cool abilities.
So this is our second bot, Dialbot.
And then we're going to buy our third bot here.
Writing bot.
That spends almost all my gold.
You'll see them down to one.
And you'll see that we have our writing bot here
whose ability is to give the frontmost friend to attack.
So what ends up being really fun about this
is that because of the way these cards all
have different things they can do
and because they all modify the lineup,
you can kind of compose this together.
So for example, I know that my strongest attack bot here
is this office ops desk and actually
is pretty able to withstand a lot of damage too.
So what I can do is drag my writing bot to the second slot
and what the writing bot does is give the frontmost friend
to attack, but it also has a ton of defense of its own.
I think what this will do is set me up for a really strong
start in spot one and then be able to have
two sort of characters who can tank a little bit of damage
for me, which I think will be great.
And then you'll see this guy, yeah, gets a heal to attack.
I think I like this setup.
Yeah, and then we'll get Dialbot
at the very beginning of the match.
We'll just deal one damage to the enemy front.
So I really like this combo because I
think this will give me a four attack
to start against a potentially weaker opponent, which
I think is going to be really, really cool.
So I like this lineup.
And then the way the game works is
if I had a little more money, I could buy these upgrades.
And so every round, between rounds,
and again, it's the best of three rounds,
you basically go in and can get an upgrade.
In this case, I had to get a plus one plus one.
I don't have three gold.
Just go ahead and fight round one.
So you're seeing here, I'm getting paired against another
team of bots.
And it looks like my strategy worked out pretty well.
Let's see, there we go.
And so what you've seen happening
over the course of the game is that the bots are duking it out.
Those abilities fire.
It's a bit of an event stream here.
One idea I'm thinking is, I wonder if we should show the event
stream.
Yeah, we should show the history.
Because as you were playing, I was just noticing
that it happened so fast that I didn't actually
know what was going on.
So it'd be cool if you could maybe even
step through the thing even if you wanted to play
or just let it auto play.
Actually, you know what?
For an MVP, why don't we just make it click through?
I feel like it could be.
Sure.
And then an auto play button.
Yeah.
OK, cool.
So we're going to continue.
So now that's round one.
And then, of course, you can continue through two more
rounds.
But what's really cool now is we have a few new bots
that have entered the fray.
And so you got an uncommon card if you can see the green bar.
Yeah.
So I got an uncommon card, which is super strong.
Looks like this card gets stronger
when the card in front of it faints.
And so this might be a really cool one
to pair with one of my other bots.
But I have some choices to make.
I know that what I'm fighting against,
so I can see my opponents line up, at least
from what I saw last time.
I have 10 gold.
And these bots are pretty expensive.
But I have some room to work with.
So I think what I could do here is sell one of these cards.
Do you want to pinch to zoom so we can see some of the text
as well?
Yeah, I think.
What bots do you have in your shop now?
So I have the SEO and AEO deal one damage
to the enemy in the same seat.
I feel like we should definitely buy the Knightly Audit
Engineer, since it's uncommon, and maybe sell the dial bot.
I don't think that's that good.
So that gave me a gold.
We should probably say how much they sell four on here.
Oh, yeah, you get one gold for selling them.
But I'm going to buy my Knightly Audit Engineer.
And this gives plus two attack when the friend ahead faints.
I actually really like this combo.
So what this is going to do is my office ops desk
is going to get this hype benefit, which
will give it plus two attack.
So it'll be a five, five.
And then when it faints, this will turn into a five, six.
That's a pretty good combo.
You have enough gold to buy the power up to the apple.
Oh, right.
OK.
Where do you think we should put that?
What does that do?
Can you zoom in?
Yeah, so the apple just gives us plus one, plus one.
Just stack the front line.
Sure.
And that's like our main damage dealer.
Yeah, that's right.
OK, so this is now a four, six.
It's pretty beefy.
And then we have four gold left.
I guess we could swap another bot.
We could sell and buy.
But I kind of like this lineup.
Yeah, I think this is really good.
Let's go with that.
OK, let's go with that.
So here we go.
We're going to fight round two.
This is where maybe the sound effects and the music you had
could be kind of a, yeah, we did so well here.
And again, this is just practice.
So this is just fighting our AI, which is not very smart.
But as we start, yeah, but when we start actually releasing
it, we'll have players will be able to compete with each other
and we'll start tracking scores and the leaderboard
will start getting active.
So yeah.
And we'll keep iterating on it, too.
So a lot of polished things that we're seeing.
So one of the things that we do internally
is we have this tradition where
any time we're going to launch a product, we fuzz it,
or we kind of walk through literally
step by step of the entire experience.
We could literally just do this.
We all get into a room together, sit on our laptops,
and test the feature.
Obviously, this should we share this with the chat now?
Yeah, well, do you think we're ready?
Only one way to find out.
OK, OK, OK.
Well, here's the home page.
There's a bot menu.
See all the bots.
Oh, yeah, this is actually a bug.
We don't need to show this.
I don't know why my bot added this.
Oh, we have some epic cards in here.
But actually, I guess this could be cool to show.
So like we were saying earlier, we looked at the XAI.
If you go to x.ai.bot.marketplace,
you'll see all of the bot templates
that we have that are featured.
And basically, what we did is we turned all of these
into bots in our game.
And we also generated a custom profile picture for them,
like a cute little avatar.
We're going to make this UI look a lot nicer.
But yeah, there's a lot of cards to choose from.
And they have different rarity as well.
So like there's the common cards.
You have uncommon cards, rare cards.
These are really good.
Yeah, so these ones are like better stats
or more interesting abilities.
And then we have epic cards.
I agree, Link, she is epic.
And oh, yes, Dr. Eggbot.
We have Dr. Eggbot right there.
I feel like Lauren might have.
I might have cheated a little bit and favored my own bot.
As an epic bot.
Well, I didn't make Dr. Eggbot legendary.
I feel like as game creators, we should each get
one legendary bot of our own.
Maybe, maybe.
Yeah, or maybe we can feature somebody's bot, right?
Someone in the chat bot as a legendary bot.
That could be cool, actually.
If you create a bot template and we like it, we'll add it.
Yeah, yeah.
You can do that just from Grokbot.
Create a bot in Grokbot.
Hit the Share button.
You can export it as a template.
Share your bot templates with us.
And maybe we'll pick a few of our favorites
and bring them into the chat.
I like that, or bring them into the game.
All right, so I think it's really important for our game
studio that we actually get real feedback.
Yeah.
So let's do a really quick five-second huddle.
Cool.
Should we launch it right now?
You have the Twitter account or the X account ready, right?
I have the X account, yeah.
I mean, the X account is not, there's no details on it.
But we have the URL.
The URL is good.
All is good.
We can do a play test.
We can just say, this is a play test, right?
We'll set expectations.
You know, it's going to probably, we'll have bugs and errors.
But hopefully you'll get to play it with us
and give us feedback.
Let's ship it.
Yeah.
I'm down.
All right.
I feel like Matt should do the honors
and make our first X post.
Our first X post.
Okay, okay.
I didn't say I was logged in the X account.
So, Matt's going to get the post up.
And then once that's up, we'll put it on your screen maybe.
Sounds good.
Yeah, I can pull it up.
And then we'll share your URL.
And then we'll just start watching our logs, I guess,
and make sure everything's working.
I think I'm logged in on my phone.
Yeah.
And one thing we'll, so a couple of things for folks
who are just catching up, just tuning in while Matt gets us set up.
We are, you are watching us, joining us mid-launch.
We are launching our game studio that we've been working on
for the last day and changed.
We're on day three of our 72-hour livestream to build a product,
build a company entirely with RockBox.
We spent some time early on ideating.
We settled on an idea early, late day one, early day two
that we've been running with, and we're building a game studio
and we're launching our first game.
And, well, we know it has a lot of polish that it needs,
but we're really excited to get it out there
and get it into people's hands.
So, we're imminently here going to reveal our domain
and reveal our X account.
And one thing I'll call out is like, you know,
those will be the only real accounts
and domains associated with this,
and so I want to make sure that, you know,
you're coming to the source
and that any other associations you see
are not going to be by us.
So, we'll reveal the two official sources of truth
for this app and be able to share those out.
Did you hear the post-up?
We are posting now, yeah.
Very exciting.
I'm literally updating.
Like, the X account was default and blank.
Yeah, this is like...
And I guess if you've ever worked at a startup
or built a startup if you're on or thinking about one,
you know, this is what it's like.
It's super scrappy.
Things don't work, but there's a real...
I think it's really fun when, you know,
you're working with a team of founders.
There's a lot of energy.
I see Roshan, your screen.
Oh, no, that's your screen.
That's my screen.
We're just watching.
We'll watch.
I've logged into my account.
I have it up when you're ready.
As soon as you tweet,
we can cut to my screen if you're ready.
All right, okay.
We're live.
Thursday Arena is live.
With our default profile picture
because I literally didn't have 100.
I love it.
And, yeah, I'm reminded to everyone that
Thursday Arena, this is the only official X account
for our game studio.
And ThursdayArena.com is our only official game.
So, if you're seeing anything related to this project,
that it's not coming from the ThursdayArena X account
or it's not being shown to you on ThursdayArena.com,
it's not us.
These are the two spots, source of truth.
And, yeah, let me actually just retweet your post and follow.
Wow, we're getting followers.
Yeah, there's a side quest of our game,
which is how many followers can we get on this Twitter account?
So, one little tool that I built, like I like emojis.
So, I have this, I have my own site, emoji.mattballmar,
that actually allows you to download any Apple emoji
as a PNG.
Nice.
A little tool that I have for myself
so I can get a little cupcake emoji here.
Maybe that's our first X profile image.
Oh, Matt, emoji is so cute.
Kid name?
Yeah, we're working on some, in the background,
I'm working on some of the, like,
favicon and styling things as well as OG images.
A little quick tip for you,
any time you make a website, any time you have a business,
you probably want it to show up nice.
Like, if I went to Thursday Arena and, like,
searched for it on Google or something, right?
Meta information is the things you see here.
So, like, clearly we're not doing our SEO or AEO yet.
We're going to work on that.
But you want the information shown to be, like,
number one, you want it to use best practices
and search engine optimization.
It also will look nice for users.
Sorry to interrupt you, but look at our leaderboard.
We have 96 people on the leaderboard.
I don't even know if we have pagination.
You want to bring up the leaderboard?
You may have to sign in.
So, we got our...
Sign in works, yes.
Sign in works, so that's good to hear.
Very nice that it works.
Before I should fix on this logo.
While they're doing that, I also have a bot
that's working on building us some dashboards.
And so we want to be able to track how the launch is going.
Roshan, you're number one right now.
Yeah, we need to work on this.
I was in second place all of the last 24 hours.
Let me enjoy my number one spot.
Oh, my gosh.
You're losing, Matt.
You're going to go to silver.
I'm going down on the leaderboard.
You need to think about your strategy.
One of the things I'm doing while Matt's playing here
is I love bots for routines for product launches.
I do this all the time.
So, anytime we launch something internally in SpaceX AI,
I put together, I ask a bot to say,
you're my data scientist bot.
You have all the context on how all of our data science works
and all the stuff in our dashboards
generate me a launch pulse.
And so that's what I'm doing on my screen right now
where I just asked my bot to, you know,
this is a lot more fun than dashboards.
I know, I know.
But put together a 15-minute pulse.
So, every 15 minutes, I'm going to get thrown some dashboards
to see how the launch is going,
can track some new sign-ups,
track the number of practice rounds we've had,
get a sense of if we maybe have a conversion funnel here
where we want to convert people from practice accounts
to real accounts.
All the cool sort of product metrics that you might love
for any new app.
But we're live. It's exciting.
So, shall we call people who are trying to climb the leaderboard?
Yeah, maybe we'll head over.
So, now we have second place Ben Jay Bush.
Wait, first, let's head over to Lauren's screen real quick.
She's going to shout some folks out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, so, well, now I'm in third place.
I've fallen down in the rankings
because I've been slacking off.
And we have Ben Jay Bush in second place.
Roshan's still holding strong on first place.
We might consider making this leaderboard update
every minute or something.
What does it do now?
It doesn't.
Oh, okay, it's a refresh, yeah.
Ben Jay Bush getting very close to beating you, Roshan.
He's at 1046 points and you're at 1047.
So, we're up to 225 followers on X.
Wow.
Very nice.
And are you working on the...
I think it'd be really cool to show how many users we have live.
I know you can bring that up.
Yeah, I'm working on it.
My bot is...
Don't share Roshan's screen yet.
But I think it'd be really cool to see how many people we have concurrently.
And to be honest, I am very impressed that the app hasn't crashed yet
because, oh, Ben Jay Bush is now in first place.
Congratulations.
We did mention that maybe we'll have some prizes
for people in the leaderboard.
We'll talk about that very soon.
But yeah, as I was saying,
the factory was really spinning up last night.
We were merging PRs automatically.
To be entirely honest, I didn't look at the code at all.
I just used potato mode and PStack
and told my bot to make this really performant
and make sure we can handle a giant swarm of people on X playing our game.
And so far, so good.
I'm dropping down the ranks now.
I'm only at 11th place.
I got to start playing some games.
But while Roshan's still working on the dashboard,
I can actually show you some of the commits, I guess.
To be honest, this is definitely the first time I'm looking at some of them.
But a lot of this was like...
I didn't tell my bots to put in a lot of effort in the commit titles.
You can see actually Roshan was landing a lot of commits in the last hour.
Let me just filter.
Sorry, I'm not just going to be working on dashboards,
but I'm also trying to get my rating back up.
That's important.
But yeah, I did a lot of things like fixing our migrations.
I had a bug.
But one thing for the techie people in our chat,
so one thing I was thinking about as we were building this was type safety.
And it's like a very...
When you start building a real game,
you start thinking about how to actually maintain.
And again, entirely honest, when we first started building this,
it was very, very scrappy, very loose.
Didn't look at the code at all,
so I didn't even know what we were going to expect.
Wow, we have almost 500 users.
Oh, wow, that's huge.
And yeah, so our backend is built with Go,
and it's actually a serverless backend built with Vercel functions.
So I think that's maybe part of the reason.
We also use PlanetScale for our database,
so that's probably why it's so...
It's actually working pretty well right now,
thanks to the...
We're standing on the shoulders of great engineers.
And so one thing I was trying to think about last night was,
how do I make sure that the backend and the frontend,
the client, stay in sync?
So when you're back and talk to your frontend,
it would be talking over some protocol.
So for us, we just use a REST protocol.
But so one thing I was trying to think about was type safety.
So type safety is this idea of, on the backend,
let's say you have a bot type,
and the bot has certain fields,
it has a display name, it has an avatar,
it has some stats associated with it.
And let's say, as Matt, Roshan, and myself
are contributing to the code base,
how do we ensure that if I make a backend change
and Roshan makes a frontend change that we don't conflict?
Like maybe Roshan redesigns the card
and I removed a field.
And now the field that the UI is reading from
is no longer able to get that data.
So one of the things that I started to look at was,
how do we ensure that type safety over the network?
And I honestly didn't really have a,
if I had spent more time,
I might have designed this differently.
But for now, it's kind of a basic approach
where we parse the responses we get from the backend
through ZOD.
ZOD is this really great library,
JavaScript library,
and it essentially lets you parse the response
and handle them and make sure
that it's all validated and correct.
Can someone also create a QR code
to our ThursdayRuna.com?
Oh, it's up there.
You got it, awesome, awesome.
Oh, it's up there?
Yeah, right there.
Oh, cool.
I have some dashboards.
Should we take a look at that?
Yeah, yeah, let's switch to Roshan's screen.
Yeah, let's switch to my screen, please.
What's a business without a dashboard on site?
I am a product person.
I need metrics.
I'm blind without them.
Let me zoom in a little bit here.
So, yeah, this is Grokbot.
You can kind of see some of the bots that we have set up.
It looks like my founding engineer here
is just still listening to all the PRs that are coming in.
So we're working away.
What I love to do, as I was saying a second ago,
is for new launches,
use Grokbot to drive my metrics and reporting.
I find that this is actually a really powerful way
to just get quick on-demand data
versus having to go to a dashboard website,
log in, kind of navigate through a bunch of clicks.
And honestly, what's even better about this
is I can just get my live cuts of data that I need now.
So I don't have to go and recreate a dashboard.
I just wanted to interrupt you to say,
I love hockey stick charts.
Oh, yes.
I'm squinting in the middle.
Let's take a look at the charts.
Okay.
So we already have over 600 practice sessions.
This is like as of, I don't know, two minutes ago.
I love funnel metrics.
So it looks like 38 of our users,
or 38 practice sessions converted to Sign In With X.
400 people signed in with X.
I know that number is already higher than it is,
just based on what we saw.
Oh, nice.
We have, wow, a hockey stick chart.
This is traffic spike.
Amazing.
It's time to get funding, guys.
Yeah.
Up and to the right.
Cool little funnel snapshot here.
These are really great.
We can kind of see where in the funnel we're losing people.
Obviously, like for games and SaaS products,
we care a lot about retention, recurring visits,
and obviously, if you want to monetize this,
those will be metrics that our monetization partners
will care a lot about.
Some cool signed in matches by phase.
I don't know why it's calling this SaaS matches,
but that's okay.
Shop, result, and battle, so we can kind of see
when people are signing in.
We have a Sign In With X button throughout the product,
so we can kind of see when we're capturing the sign in.
That's really cool.
Actually, something I'm curious about,
I've always wanted to know,
is like as a product manager,
when you're thinking about how to grow the product
and act on user feedback,
and prioritize what's most important,
what do you look at?
I guess for me, I want to see the,
obviously I want to see the user numbers go up
and engagement, but do you have any go-to things
that you see to like,
where are people falling off in the product or in the game?
Yeah, I think it actually really depends on
what type of product you're building.
And so for where we are, we're a zero-to-one company.
We just launched this.
We're like hopefully going to get a few hundred,
maybe a few thousand users today,
if you guys keep signing up.
And for a zero-to-one product,
we don't have monetization in the app right now.
So really, I think what we care about,
this is a classic sort of Bay Area growth machine, right?
It's like we really want to get as many people
into the product,
really liking what we've built as possible.
And so the things I care about most are,
are people playing?
Are they having a good time?
Can we get it?
It's a sense of, do people like what we've built?
And so some of that will be through feedback.
Some of that will be through the funnel.
So for example, being able to see if people are making it
all the way to a game, all the way to the end of a game,
playing another game, or are they kind of starting off
and then just falling off immediately
and kind of not coming back?
So funnel metrics are really great for that,
particularly for zero to one products
where you want to get a sense of how things are going.
And then obviously, for a scaled revenue product,
which hopefully we can get to as well,
revenue is a big metric.
We talked with some guests on Monday
that helped build small businesses
and helped empower small businesses to really grow
and kind of heard over and over again
that revenue is the main thing that businesses care about.
We're no different, right?
Any good company needs to make money,
needs to make money to keep the product growing
and to keep the product continuing to evolve
and fund all the engineers and help us buy coffee
and all those good things.
And so revenue ultimately at the end of the day
becomes a huge driver, but we're pre-revenue,
we're pre-revenue.
So while we're pre-revenue,
I like to focus more on product metrics.
I like to focus on engagement, retention,
some of those classic metrics,
but obviously tune to our product here.
So maybe we're happy with a bunch of people
just practicing and not signing up for X,
but maybe for the people who sign in,
we could give them even better experiences.
We could really make the leaderboard more competitive
or add more features for signed in users.
Maybe we give them all kinds of perks, things like this.
And so, yeah, I think that's kind of how I think about it.
The other thing that I also really like to think about,
because we're building a game,
the game mechanics are really important here.
And so, you know, we mentioned earlier,
we love playing games,
we haven't built a ton of games ourselves,
and so we've learned a lot throughout this process.
But one of the things we can do with these metrics
is we can also just get a sense
of how the game is operating.
And one of the things that I know
is really important from game design
is making sure that we don't sort of fall over
on the mechanics, meaning is there not variety,
is there enough replayability?
Is the game balanced in a good way
where it feels like you're not losing every time
or you're not winning every time?
Is there a truly competitive dynamic?
And so, while I was talking a minute ago,
I just asked my bot here to pull some examples
of, you know, win losses and how games are going.
It looks like we have, yeah, a little loss heavy right now.
We're at a 41.8% loss ratio.
And it looks like we have, yeah, you know,
I wonder if our AI matchmaking is working okay,
because when I was playing,
most of my games seem like they're playing against AI.
So maybe we should try and-
I think that was because we didn't,
so the way it works is that you get matched
with another player's snapshot.
And I think at the time we were playtesting it,
there wasn't nobody else.
So once you played my snapshot, for example,
it's gone from the pool.
And so then you just matched with an AI player.
But now we have players who are actually getting ranked.
If you look at the computer board,
the scores are continually updating.
Now Nicholas Chek is in first place.
Congratulations at 1084.
I'm very curious who's going to be the first player
to break out of gold if you open the leaderboard
and zoom in a little bit.
I actually forgot what the next tier is.
I think it's diamond after this.
I think so.
We might need to add more tiers, but we'll see.
Elo should be balanced, yeah, yeah.
So the way Elo works as a rough example,
it's like it gets harder to get points
as you ascend the ladder.
And if you're, yeah, and there's also some math behind,
if you get matched up with a much higher rated player
and you beat them, then you gain more points.
Yeah, what I'm wondering is, we might have a,
yeah, I would zoom out because it's hard to pick cards.
Did you match or you can just pinch?
Yeah.
Did you match against a real person?
I think I'm AI.
That might be a good bug for us to look into.
Yeah, but then I guess, I mean,
other people, I see other people's scores changing.
But they have to be matching with players.
Let me try and play a game as well and see.
Okay, so while Lauren's looking at that,
I'll bring us back to Grokbot.
And we were talking a little bit about game mechanics.
So this can be really helpful too.
It looks like we can see some really quick charts
on our win-loss.
And then also just like opponent difficulties.
So we have ghost players, AI players, and unknown.
We should probably come up with some better naming
for those, so these charts are really useful.
If we look at the win-loss,
there are more losses than wins,
which means that AI is just beating people.
Yes, that's exactly what that means.
So this is actually interesting
from my game's studio perspective,
because I actually, I mean, I don't know,
I've never really built a competitive game before.
But I think, I believe the idea is to try to strive
for more or less like a 50%.
Yeah, because you need to feel like you can win,
but also-
Right, right.
In other words, like right now,
it might feel like it's too unbalanced
where you just keep losing and it's not that fun.
I think, I feel like it'd be a good,
this is something we need to iterate on.
It's like, how do we actually get it more,
up to 50%, maybe we can kick off a bot here and there
to kind of analyze the data.
And this, I think, is also another example
of how Grokbot is powerful
when you hook up all of the things.
So, Roshan's Grokbot is connected to,
like, Vercel, to PlanetScale, to GitHub,
to all the metrics here.
And so, it can pull all of this information together
and start thinking, you know,
like, send it to your game designer bot and say,
you know, help us look at this data and understand-
We'll do that right now.
Yeah, help us look at this data and understand,
you know, where, you know, maybe the game is not as fun
because people are, like, losing more than they are winning.
You know, and it doesn't feel like you have
a good chance of winning.
And it can get you so many good insights
just because of the fact that it has all this context
pulled across all of your different sources.
So, I often tell people, like,
the most important thing about Grokbot, actually,
is not even setting up your bots.
It's actually connecting all of your different tools
and plugins.
You know, you can actually get very far,
even with just one bot,
if you don't want to set up a team.
Yeah, here's what I have right now.
Yeah, Pstack, of course, Slack, Vercel,
X, PlanetScale, Notion, Clerk, Excaladraw,
we were doing some whiteboarding earlier.
But yeah, really, anything you need.
We did some sound design,
so my bots were creating their own skills,
which is really cool, so they can do that.
Yeah, anything you need, if you want Dr. Eggbot,
you have some featured bots here,
but also a bunch of apps.
What's cool about this, too, since we're on the same team,
I can see, oh, Matt, it's all remotion,
so maybe I could also get remotion.
Yeah, anything you need, a plugin exists for it,
or you can just also point your agent at the,
point Grokbot, add an MCP URL,
it'll install it for you itself.
We added one password yesterday,
which is really cool, too,
so a lot more of these coming online every single day,
like AgentMail for email, Canva for design,
Clay for go-to-market, which you heard about earlier today.
Lots of cool stuff here.
Cool, well, I have Krit, who's my game design bot.
I asked my data bot to kind of share
the live launch with Krit.
Krit's been helping us on game design,
kind of walking through the mechanics
that we might want to build.
Are they good, are they bad?
I think production has an update for us,
actually, we have some cappuccinos coming in on set.
We're doing a live delivery.
Thank you, production.
Thank you, it's all that.
Thank you.
Need fuel for the launch?
But yeah, Roshan, I think you're right.
I assume to be getting only AI matches for some reason.
Maybe, I don't know if it's just us,
but other players are getting,
have you gotten a real player match?
No, I haven't.
We need to work on it, so that's all nice.
So I don't know what happened to our,
we definitely have bugs,
but I see people climbing the leaderboard,
so I assume-
I think we're just letting you get ELO
even if you play AI.
No, no, I don't think so.
My ELO didn't change after I won or lost my games.
Oh, interesting.
So maybe we're stuck in some kind of-
Dang, how'd I get to 27th place?
Or maybe we're just stuck in some weird-
Well, I'm going to ask my bot.
What's going on?
Maybe you can show us how you would do a bug fix.
Yeah, so in this case, this is a bug I noticed, right?
If it was a bug that was reported through some system
where we'd find it ourselves,
I would probably ask the engine to take care of it.
But in this case,
I'm just going to go to my founding engineer bot
and say, hey, I think our ELO, our match-making,
I'm going to narrate for a second.
Hey, so I think our ELO and our matchmaking are messed up.
What is happening right now is
every time I play a game on thursdayareno.com,
I get paired with an AI player
instead of another player's set or lineup.
But for some reason, as a leaderboard,
the ELO scores are changing a bunch.
And so not quite sure,
are some people getting paired
and just like the matchmaking is off?
Can you dig into that to figure out what's going on?
Use potato mode
and use a cursor cloud agent for the investigation.
Don't open a PR yet.
Just come back to me with what you think is going on
and then we can try and apply a fix.
Want to share that?
Wait, let me, I want to see one thing.
You can just mention,
like you don't have to open it on,
you don't have to open Slack.
Oh yeah, sure, sure.
Or you can at least say like that button now works.
So we can cut over to my screen,
which I can show you what I've been cooking on
for a little bit.
So one thing that I'm big on
and Lauren talked about these like feedback loops
and we're working on basically getting feedback from users
and then integrating that into the project.
So now you can send feedback.
And so if I say, hey, what's up?
And send that,
we're gonna be able to have that user feedback
flow through into our Slack channel
when I can see that I'm getting feedback.
Now, obviously, because we're submitting
user generated content,
there's a lot of moderation that's going on
behind the scenes, rate limiting, profanity,
all of the things that you need to be very careful of.
Sanitization, if you're logging something to a database,
all the things you need to be careful of
if you're accepting user input.
And then also this is behind an authenticated route, right?
So you have to authenticate with X.
We know that we're not just accepting
submissions from anybody.
But this is the first step, right,
to being able to then take that feedback
and action upon it.
So maybe we could have Grokbot summarize
the feedback that we're getting,
categorize that into features
to then improve our application.
And then we as a product team could decide,
oh, hey, this is actually a really good feedback.
We need to incorporate it.
It's also a way,
Lauren talked a lot about fuzzing
or like testing our own application.
To start doing that at scale
where we could have people reporting bugs
and then we could start running like automated bug reports
on some of the user submitted feedback.
So this is one step.
I'm also working on some other more creative ways
and fun ways for you all to engage with the product
which should be coming soon.
And then we're also kind of working on some like
ads sponsorship stuff.
But I think we're desperately in need of a redesign as well
and CUI is like making me cringe.
There's a lot of good feedback coming in on the X post.
So if you cut over to my screen real quick.
So we'll go to Lauren's screen.
So what I would love to do,
I'm not gonna show the feedback live, of course,
as Matt said,
but I do wanna talk about like,
as an engineer,
how do you actually make use of feedback?
We can get over to Lauren's screen
so she can show off some of the feedback flows, please.
Yes, I'll show you how I use Graphbot
to set up like a factory.
But while we get my screen on the screen,
I'll just talk.
There we go, thanks.
Yeah, so what I'll usually do,
so again, if you're looking at my Graphbot
for the first time,
Steve is my chief bot
and I talk to Steve
and he delegates to all my other bots.
And the point I wanted to make here is that,
so I copied the link to our Slack channel
and I'm gonna tell it something like,
oh yeah, I'm gonna use dictation.
All right, Steve,
the link above is our Slack channel
that is receiving user feedback
that players of our game are leaving for us.
So I wanna set up a factory workflow
where we look at the feedback,
we triage it,
we try to reproduce the issue
and then file a ticket in our Notion database.
And this is gonna be our first step for now.
I'll eventually wanna hook it up to bots
that can automatically fix those issues and open PRs.
But we'll save that step for later.
And then another thing that's really important
about receiving user feedback,
user generated content is that we wanna filter
for anything that isn't about the game
or it contains profanity
or like weird links.
And very importantly,
if we're using AI to review feedback,
you wanna tell your AI to,
what do you call it,
watch out for prompt injections as well.
So yeah, that's what I wanted to show.
And then as always,
I will just say,
restate this in your own words.
And then I'll click that.
Do we have anything else interesting we wanna show?
I might have something shortly,
not yet, but shortly.
Yeah, I think I really know.
Okay, let's see,
I can talk about it.
Have you looked at the leaderboard?
I just looked at it recently.
We can cut to my screen for a second,
if you'd like.
We have our first Platinum's.
Oh, dang.
Wow.
There's Platinum players.
They're grinding, this is crazy.
To be fair, it's only ELO 1100,
I'm just kidding, okay.
Platinum's a great achievement.
Congratulations to the six players,
five players who have fought through our UI bugs
to ascend the Platinum ranks.
I'm impressed.
We will make this better,
but this is awesome.
We have to get these players some prizes.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Well, hey, the day is young.
It's only 1043 Pacific.
And I feel like there could be a lot of
leaderboard shakeups happening really soon.
I feel like I'm commentating an esports game.
I know it's like...
Yeah, I want to say,
maybe we can figure out a set of prizes.
Maybe we can give out some Grokbot Ultra plans
for people on the leaderboard.
We'll need to talk through the details,
but maybe we can do something like the top 10 players.
Yeah, yeah.
We'll obviously need to get approval for that,
but we'll give our best shot
and really appreciate everyone on the chat
playing our game.
You can start sending feedback to us on Slack,
or no, it's not on Slack.
I mean, through the in-game feedback.
And we'll start looking at them and start fixing them.
We know that there are a lot of bugs
and a lot of things to polish.
So we really appreciate the time you're taking
to play our game and play test it.
One mechanics thing I'm thinking is every round,
you always get after the first round,
you reset to the same gold.
And so what you do mechanically
is you always sell one bot,
you buy a new bot,
and you apply an upgrade.
I wonder if we should try to rethink that mechanic a bit,
because I think right now what happens is
you kind of do the same actions.
There's still a bit of strategy
for how you move the cards around,
but you kind of do the same actions.
And so it feels like a little bit repetitive
in terms of the shop mechanic.
That might be a thing for us to think about
is how we improve the shop mechanic.
I'm also gonna, while you do that,
I'm gonna tell the bot that I just made
to look at the feedback that we've gotten on Slack
and then categorize them
and maybe make some charts so that we can actually
start seeing like, maybe we have a majority of issues
that are gameplay related or actual bugs.
So I'll try to get that out soon.
I was gonna say, if you can cut over to my screen,
Matt's screen real quick,
we can show some of the feedback that's coming in.
It's actually pretty great.
Very brave.
I mean, I've audited the feedback
and we are moderating it.
Oh my goodness, this is wild.
So this was me doing a play test
that we hadn't tried before.
I actually tried to spend all my gold
and then realized, if you do that,
you end up stuck because you cannot buy new bugs.
That's only a bug.
Yeah, we should, actually,
I'm gonna report that as an issue too.
Sorry, but can we go to Matt's screen
and pull up the feedback channels
that we're seeing come in?
Pending.
Pending, pending.
In the meantime, I'm just enjoying my cappuccino.
I'm just stuck.
Okay, I'll log out.
There's no log out.
Does it sign up in that word?
Classic.
Okay, classic.
Okay, cool.
We got a lot of bug fixes.
Are we logging these anywhere?
Are we putting them into Slack?
Yeah, the feedback's all going to Slack.
If you have the Slack open version,
you can also take a look at it.
So where's that?
I don't wanna put that on the spot.
Don't do that.
I think let Matt do it because you scroll to a good part.
Yeah, I mean, it's very heavily moderated
just to be clear.
There's a lot of filtering going on.
Thanks everybody in our chat for being so nice.
Well, actually, we're just not seeing the people
that aren't being nice because, you know,
I'll actually take a step back, right?
When you receive like freeform text over the internet,
like you have to be very careful.
So what we're doing is both filtering on the client side
for, you know, length and a few other things.
But then on the server side,
we're filtering for, again, I mentioned profanity.
We're sanitizing all the user inputs
so that we're not getting some sort of like
injection attacks or anything like that.
And then we're running it through XAI models
to prevent other, basically catch all guards.
And so that way you can make sure
that user submissions are safe.
We also have rate limiting in place
and some other things to make sure that
we're getting, again, good user feedback.
And some people are getting 429 too many request errors
on the actual API side.
So you might be starting to overload the server
a little bit.
But yeah, if we can take a look at my screen
or I guess if Roshan can check out Slack,
it should be, we should be good
to take a look at the feedback.
Action team, can we get Matt's screen on?
Yeah, so here we go, Cupcake Feed.
You're gonna have to zoom in way, way much more here.
But this is a good example here
of what it means to like have users play test
and then collect this feedback.
And so, you know, when you're using AI,
context or data can really take any form.
And this is data about our game.
Data about what's broken, what people want.
Let people buy extra gold so you can earn money
even if that makes it a bit play to win.
We'll have to think about that one.
That's more of a product direction.
It needs a theme, yellow points.
Okay, so we have some mix of bug reports, requests,
and you know, just feedback generally.
So what we might wanna do is start to categorize this,
which it looks like you're already doing, Lauren.
Yeah, I'm actually getting my graph bot
to post some charts to this channel.
Oh, great.
So in like a few seconds, we'll see the charts show up.
And I guess some fun trivia is that
we actually have a very similar process set up.
I guess you can see the charts on my screen.
So I just got us to do one quick pass
to look through all the feedback and categorize them.
And I like doing this because it gives me
a high level overview of the main things
we have to fix.
So obviously, like a lot of people have reported
issues with the mobile layout.
So we definitely need to fix that first.
Only AI, no ranked matchmaking is another one
that we've seen ourselves.
So we should fix that.
Evo as well, very important.
Yeah, that's really a lot of good feedback here
that we definitely need to go and get the factory loose
on fixing.
Exactly, yeah, I think that'd be really great.
But I guess this is, you know, classic first launch
that we really scrappily put together
is 71% of our issues are bugs, right?
And so as a game studio,
and I think like a fledgling game studio,
I feel like it's really important for us
to think about like prioritization.
I'm curious how you think about it, Urshin,
but I always, for me as a gamer myself,
I always feel that when a game studio launches their game,
the most important thing actually is to prioritize
bug fixes and stability and reliability
or performance issues.
You have to make the core loop great.
Right, and I often see sometimes
that game studios might rush into,
oh, you know, we need to add all these features.
We have such a big roadmap of cool ideas we want to ship.
And it's always very exciting to work
on the next shiny thing.
But I think that, like personally,
the best games I've played are the ones
that are just relentless about
crafting a beautiful experience,
like a really, really fun game.
And, you know, I think that's really important.
And I can see, you know, like,
this is clearly something we need to prioritize.
We have 71% of our feedback are bugs.
We have 16% praise, which is actually pretty good.
You know, I feel like I-
Oh, they're being really nice.
Yeah, our chat, you guys are being so nice.
I'm literally moderating out all the mean comments.
Hey, there's one here that says,
gift potato arrays, but I think it's pretty cool.
Gift me arrays, yeah, I wouldn't mind.
I heard, oh, actually, speaking of,
so I heard someone, you have a new subscriber on X,
that might- Oh, no.
I heard Elon might be a subscriber.
Yeah, thank you, thank you, boss,
for the $2 a month, very appreciated.
Sick, cool.
So we're also, I'm also working on some other ways
to submit feedback, maybe a little bit more fun ways
that might be worth a demo in a few minutes.
So we might have something fun for you there.
And then I'm also just merged in a bunch of favicon
and like- Oh, nice, should we go to your screen?
Yeah, we can cut over here now.
I think I had some HDMI issues previously.
Let's go to the math screen, there we go.
Cool, so it actually updated the text
a little bit as well, which I wasn't expecting.
But now we have like a proper favicon.
So like on the site, you can see the favicon there.
And if you ever want to take a look at your developer console,
you can see in the actual elements,
if I start searching for OG, meta, I believe, meta, meta.
You'll start to see like OG tags come through.
So like, this is a bit more developer focused, right?
A bit more developer centric.
And there are other ways to take a look at this.
You can install like Chrome extensions, essentially.
But like having proper OG titles,
OG descriptions, site names and images.
So like, here's a V1 OG image.
This is like when you post a link to Twitter,
this is what it'll come through.
And so it's kind of like basics of like social media stuff.
You can see I updated our Twitter as well,
that if you post a link, you kind of want it to look nice.
I won't post this here, but you'd want a preview.
So what you can do is go like SEO preview website,
open graph, this is a good one.
And then you can paste your URL and just make sure like,
okay, when people post about my site,
does it have a nice preview?
Do we have like the right meta tags?
And like, we currently don't.
So these are things that typically if you have a business
or if you're trying to make yourself visible online
to people, and then eventually to agents,
which we can talk about as well,
you want to make sure that all of these properties
are populated and optimized to tell people
what you are trying to do and why they should use it,
whether that's a game of business or any of these things.
So step one to having proper,
to having people be aware of your product
is accurately communicating what your product is.
And so that's what we're trying to do.
Cool, maybe it's time for a quick roundup
of what we're working on,
just to kind of check in with each other.
So we have a bunch of great feedback coming in.
We showed some of the feedback.
We have a Slack channel,
gonna work on automating some of that feedback
and trying to get that into our coding engine
that we built.
So for those who are just joining,
earlier this morning,
we talked about a coding engine that we built.
We're watching Matt do some live prompting, I think.
All this stuff is flying around basically.
We have a whole engine where we can take the feedback
that's coming in from you all,
post-moderated feedback,
also the feedback that we're noticing ourselves,
feed it to our bots,
have our bots build PRs and then kind of come back with PRs,
play test bots will play test those changes for us.
We have some UI refresh work that's going on.
Thank you for all the feedback on that so far.
Yeah, lots of great stuff.
And so really, I think what sounds like our next,
maybe a few minutes here
should just be trying to get as much stuff,
as many bugs fixed as possible, right?
Sounds good to me.
We're at 476 followers on Twitter.
So that's great.
Amazing.
With our one tweet, we're live.
Also we'll follow,
you know, we got to follow a big man.
So we follow you on.
Yes.
We are also not, we're not verified.
So what is the UI?
Yo, CL, we're working on it, dude.
Yeah, yeah.
This was a very, very scrappily put together.
800 plus.
We do have a UI redesign coming.
Okay.
It's just not finished yet.
But I didn't want to say that.
I think this is very common.
Like when you're first starting a project,
it's not going to be perfect.
Especially when you have three people working together
and different agents, different prompting,
different art direction, different things like that.
It's very easy to fall into like a low quality,
I guess, product.
And so we, you know, if this was a real game,
I mean, or a real, I guess it is a real game.
If this was like more serious, like a legit venture,
I think we'd actually spend more time polishing.
We did want to launch it to extremely early
because we wanted to get it, you know what?
Our chat, playing with us and interacting with us
and, you know, getting like feedback
and showing what you can do with Grotbot in just three days.
And we also wanted to show you a lot about
the behind the scenes work of setting up a game studio
or a company where you want to think about
not just a product development,
but all of the other parts, the supporting pieces, right?
So right now I have a bot that I'm spinning up
that is going to-
Hey, we can take a look at Lauren's screen.
Yeah, I can show you what I'm doing.
So I just told Dr. Eggbot.
So Dr. Eggbot is again, like our, my bot template
that is responsible for creating bots for me.
And-
Lauren's screen on the production side
when we get a chance, please.
Thank you.
Yes.
I told Dr. Eggbot, let's get,
I'm telling Steve, my chief,
let's get Dr. Eggbot to create a bot to triage feedback
and work with Crumb, who is my play tester bot,
to reproduce the bug and then file the issue in Notion
if it's confirmed.
And you can start to see the factory
starting to go into place.
Unblock edge 403.
Maybe let's do, I think we'll leave that.
But yeah, so the new bot is Crumble
and it's starting to look,
it's going through all the feedback.
It's found some P0s, blank screens,
definitely not a good thing.
Can select empty board spots.
The rank and elo UI goes stale.
So we definitely want to get those fixed ASAP.
Do you want me to go ahead and invite Cursor
to the Slack channel while you're doing that?
Yes, please, please do.
Let me take care of that.
I saw that was a bot suggestion, so.
Yeah, and then I want to say,
I'm going to do some voice dictation.
The voice dictation button, it's not working.
Okay, I'll just type and narrate.
So I'm going to say, okay,
so now that we have triage workflow,
we have a triage workflow
for the confirmed bugs and issues,
the new Crumble triage agent
should work with Tater
to start fixing those issues
and using potato mode for,
maybe not full autopilot,
but do we dare to autopilot?
I mean, let's try that, right?
We've been on full autopilot this whole time.
Yeah, I mean, let's try it as well.
But one really important thing about full autopilot is,
but since we are now live in production,
it's very critical that we do not break
the game for everyone.
So we need to always rigorously
verify our work with the slash verify cupcake,
that's just the name of the skill we have,
skill and swarms.
So what this will do is we're going to tell our bots
to work together using some of the skills
that we have in PSAP.
And very importantly, we need them
to reproduce the issue first,
and then only if they can actually reproduce the bug
can we trust that the agent understands
like the problem in the first place.
And that actually is a good question.
I think we need to have another bot
that will be responsible for checking the work.
I'll say also work with hash brown
to, let's say validate
that the triage was done correctly
and that the triage agent or triage bot
actually understood the user's feedback.
So once we confirm all of these things,
we can do the full autopilot fixes.
And the verification swarms.
So verification swarms are essentially,
so the swarm skill in pthac is a skill that teaches your bot
how to spawn many cloud agents in cursor.
And so these cloud agents will have their own computer,
they're kind of separate from the Grok Bot computer,
and they will be able to run the game on their own machines
and actually click around and test things and fuzz it.
So this is like a thing we love to say at space.x.ai,
like we're fuzzing.
And when we say fuzzing, we just mean like,
you're actually using the application like a real power
user, you know, clicking every little button,
you're trying every little edge case,
you're really trying to stress test and break the game.
And so the idea here is that if we have a swarm of bots
or agents that can actually do that for us,
it takes us humans out of the loop there,
because I don't have to just sit here and click and play the game
and test it and find the bugs.
I can have my bots do that for me.
Of course, we're going to continue to do that ourselves,
and we'll find a lot of issues that way as well
with human fuzzing.
But when you start getting feedback like this,
this is something that you can try to set up.
So I'm going to kick that off, hit Enter,
and cross my fingers that everything's
going to work really well.
But again, going back to why I think
it's so important to disconnect all the data you
can to Groppbot, this is exactly why.
We have our Groppbots all hooked up to our tech stack.
We have Vercel connection, PlanetScale.
We have data coming in from Slack, user feedback.
This gives us this really nice way
to set up a loop where we're getting data from the outside,
external data, and bringing it all together,
making sense of it, and then feeding our inner loop,
our inner looping, the loop that powers all of the engineering
work that we do.
And when these two loops work together,
and of course, it's going to need a lot of fine tuning.
I'm going to ask Dr. Eggbot to help me design this really
well.
But when it works, it's beautiful.
What is automation, complete automation, where in theory,
if I had set it up right, bugs will just get fixed automatically.
The game just gets better constantly
without me having to babysit the whole process.
And that frees me out to actually go work on features
or polish, other things that maybe the bugs don't catch.
Well, what I love about that, too,
is it just speaks to the importance of building
your agent system.
To put it in a way that I think about it,
it's take the time to set up your systems,
take the time to set up how your bots talk to each other,
how your agents talk to each other.
And I think that gives you a lot of leverage later on.
So when I'm building something quickly,
I find this is actually the hardest part,
is I never want to sit down and just take the step back
and build the system's work.
But it really does pay a ton of dividends.
And I think you're seeing examples here,
where we have all these bots that Lauren has set up,
and they're able to talk to each other.
You know what each one's working on,
and your product just starts cranking.
Maybe just to do a quick programming update.
So I think we're at about a little past 11 AM Pacific time.
If you're just joining us, we are hanging out here
on day three of our 72-hour live stream, where
we are building a business from scratch.
We are building a game studio and just
launched our first game, ThursdayArena.com,
if you want to check it out.
Just for folks who are watching, the only official sources
of content, ThursdayArena.com and
at ThursdayArena on X. If you see anything
from any other account, that is not us.
We are just at ThursdayArena on X and ThursdayArena.com.
Those are official.
So yeah, get your news from the source.
We have been showing off a bunch of features
that we've added, like a feedback channel that's
coming into Slack, and getting our bots to start reading
all those Slack messages.
We are going to have a guest joining us at 11.15.
Now that we have a product, we should probably
figure out how we make money.
So Vincent's going to join us in about 15 minutes.
Before that, I think we might have a video we want to show,
looking at production.
Yes, we do.
So why don't we do this?
We're going to keep working.
We've got a bunch of things that we're going to go fix.
Obviously, the bug fixes will keep coming throughout the day,
so please keep the feedback coming.
Let's cut to a quick video in about a few minutes.
You'll see us back on for a second,
and then we'll transition into chatting with Vincent.
Cool.
Yeah, I think it's a good time to actually start thinking
about how do we actually turn this game into not just
a toy, but a real business.
So I think it'd be really cool to see what ideas Vincent has.
Yeah, I'm excited, too, and Vincent's great.
So yeah, let's kick to that video whenever we're ready,
and we'll be right back.
My name is Cal Day.
I am the SVP of product and engineering
for one of our product development divisions
at Nokia.
We are trying to leverage Cursor as an agentic platform
to introduce specialized agents that are persona-specific
for every aspect of work that we do,
that can partner with the human in-seat
that does that work today.
Those things become much more possible
if we are able to iterate in much, much faster loops.
That directly impacts customer economics,
lowers unit cost, improves customer satisfaction,
and then finally, there's an entire class of things
that I think we're now going to be able to do faster
that are to do with increasing resilience,
reliability, and security in the network.
Cursor and Cursor's agents, that increasingly,
many of them are out of the box,
is a massive step up in accelerating analysis,
getting insights that otherwise would not be possible.
So we're at the beginning of a very critical journey.
We've burnt the boats.
Our plans, our goals for this year,
not next year, for this year, hinge on this work.
We have a product line,
easily 50 plus million lines of code.
We are, I would say, in an intermediate stage
of decomposing what is fundamentally
a monolith-oriented architecture.
It would be a very daunting task
for us to attempt a manual inspection of that code base.
We have undertaken that with Cursor.
Our early results of that analysis have been remarkable.
We have been able to do precisely what I just described,
which would have required bespoke tooling,
would have taken far longer,
probably several months of effort
across probably a dozen or more expert people.
We performed the initial analysis as one example,
within a matter of, I think, a couple of weeks by two people.
We've seen evidence of Cursor being deployed
very successfully in situations
that involve a need to move very quickly,
where we have run into a customer-impacting defect
that might be having a subscriber impact.
And now we're able to do that
against an extremely large corpus of service requests
and radically accelerate something
like a root cause analysis.
These examples have not been one or two.
There have been quite a few and growing in number.
That's where we're seeing, I'd say, the early success.
And where we would love to take it next
is leveraging Cursor as a platform
for multi-agent deployment and orchestration,
where really the role of the engineer,
where the architect becomes the supervision of agents
that are calling out to tools,
that are performing work at scale,
collaborating with one another.
We are literally redesigning
our entire software development lifecycle,
from inception through product delivery
and everything that comes in between.
Welcome back.
For those of you joining us,
well, we have the new face.
We'll get to that in just a moment.
But welcome back to our livestream here
at Grokbot Galaxy.
My name's Roshan, Roshan underscore S on X.
We have been streaming for three days.
Well, this is day three,
so we're two days and change in at this point.
Building a business live on X.
And just to give you a quick recap
of how the week's gone so far,
we started out on Tuesday
with an idea for a physical pop-up.
We pivoted our business, like every business does,
into building a game studio.
And so just this morning, just a little while ago,
we launched our very first game,
ThursdayArena.com,
and have the at ThursdayArena handle on X.
So those are our official sources,
ThursdayArena.com, at ThursdayArena on X.
And we've had a team of folks,
a bunch of fun folks we've brought in,
guests, internal SpaceX AI,
also folks who are out there in the community
helping other people build great businesses.
And so with that,
we'd love to introduce Vincent.
Vincent, you wanna introduce yourself
and share a little bit about what you do,
and yeah, yeah.
Yeah, excited to be here.
I am on the growth team at SpaceX AI.
So that's just how we think about,
there's a lot of interest for our awesome products.
How do we make sure we tell more people
who wanna find out more about them,
and figure out how they wanna use them,
and really speak to them.
Yeah, so what is growth?
Yeah, this is a great question.
It kinda really depends on the company
that you're working at.
Like at a PLG kind of business like our own,
you wanna really appeal to users,
and really figure out what they're doing.
That's like a lot of life cycle maybe.
Like, hey, I saw you maybe struggling
in product on something,
we should put a nudge there,
and figure out how to help you out.
In a more sales-led kind of approach,
it's like mass email, outbounding, LinkedIn,
there's a whole, you know,
business is built around that even,
so it really just depends
on what your business kinda looks like.
Yeah, and so I guess you mentioned PLG,
so that's product-led growth, right?
So business is where people are signing up,
and that kinda feels like what we're doing.
So have you had a chance to look at our stream,
or see what we've built it all,
or would it help you keep your bit of recap?
Yeah, let's see, let's see what the recap is.
Okay, cool, if we can pull up my screen, please.
So this is our game.
We're working on the UI,
we've got a lot of stuff we gotta do,
so cut us a little bit of slack,
I'll actually show you the full experience,
cause I feel like whenever I've worked with folks
who think about growth,
they wanna see the end-to-end funnel.
So maybe we could look at this together,
I want you to just absorb as much as you can,
and so for everyone in the chat,
everyone on the stream, what we're gonna do,
Vincent is an expert on all of this business stuff,
we have a product, we haven't yet turned it
into a business, and so what I'm hoping we can do
in the next 15 or 20 minutes,
is get all the great insights
for how we can go and make this a business,
and figure out how we can grow more usage.
Obviously, we're in a really lucky position
to have a bunch of people watching,
so thank you all for everyone who's watching,
that's been a great way.
Yeah, growth versus dream, right?
Many eyebrows.
So yeah, here's our game, you go in,
you log in with X,
so it already may be something interesting there.
Love that.
You know, authorize the app, this is great,
and then here's what we see,
so we have our leaderboard,
and the leaderboard's kinda cool,
we have this sort of stack rank
where you can earn points
and improve your ELO score as you play more matches,
and let's see, oh man, I keep dropping,
I am down to 35.
I was in first place for an hour.
My growth hat, first thing I'm thinking is,
could be cool to put a little share or pop up
as soon as you go on leaderboard,
be like, this is my ranking, you know, on this game.
I'm gonna, if you don't mind,
I'm gonna make a growth bot called Vincent.
Let's do it.
Oh man, hold on, he didn't let me name him
before I started.
Vincent, growth.
And I'm gonna, hey, start logging
some great growth ideas in Notion,
make a growth playbook that all adds stuff to.
So, okay, first thing you said was,
we have a leaderboard in the app,
and we should have a share option,
so you can share, respond, leaderboard, is that right?
Like almost as soon as the game ends
and you're kind of like old arcade style,
you know, you're putting in your name,
or I guess these are X handles,
from where I can infer.
You can then like have a pop-in,
it's like, press this share button to, you know,
post on X and brag to your friends
that you've got this ranking out of whatever on the game.
Great, I just narrowed, I just captured that voice audio,
we're just gonna ship that to the agent.
I love voice audio.
We'll just keep doing this, this is great.
So anytime you see an opportunity,
just shout out what we'll capture.
We have almost a thousand users on our leaderboard,
so, I don't know, pretty good.
That's pretty good.
Right, decent.
That's insane.
Yeah, okay, okay, cool.
You heard it here, from a person
who works on this professionally?
Yeah.
So that's the leaderboard.
And then, you know, we have a few other things here,
so you can go into the actual game loop,
and this might be really fun.
So I'm gonna start over.
And here's, oh, let's start again.
Here's how the game works is, well, let's do this.
I'm gonna make this full screen,
and then I'll zoom a little bit,
because I know it's a little hard to see.
So you get these little bots,
and these are all bots from our marketplace.
Love it.
Gotta plug the marketplace.
Yeah.
A good growth area for us.
Yeah, definitely a good growth area for us, right?
And we actually were thinking, maybe over time,
we could make it so you could bring your own bots
into the chat, too, into the game.
That might be a really fun mechanic, right?
Yes, these bots have these stats.
They have like an attack stat and a health stat,
and you just basically start the game
with a shop and some gold,
and you can buy your little team.
Oh, that's cool.
And the way the game works is that you're setting a lineup.
And so, you know, they all have different abilities.
So for example, when this character faints,
it gives the two friends behind it, plus one, plus one.
So I'd probably wanna put them in the first slot
so that, you know, I can take advantage of that ability
for as many players as I can behind him.
This one, whenever the game starts,
it deals one damage to the last living enemy,
or wherever this player starts.
So I think I might wanna put him in the back, actually.
And then this gives 50% of its attack
to the friend ahead.
So it's a little bit of a strategy game.
You kinda set your lineup.
And then, you know, you just go through this fight,
so you can kinda see on the screen there,
you kinda get paired up with an opponent.
The opponents all have different abilities of their own,
and you kinda see what happens as the game plays itself.
Sort of like an auto-battler, if you've seen those.
And so that was round one.
The game is played over three rounds,
and so there's a bit of an in-between rounds mechanic
where you can do some more strategizing.
So in this case, I have some new bots I can buy.
Here's Critikito, one of my favorite bots.
The design critique bot that Manuel
and our design team has made, which is really wonderful.
So this deals two damage to the enemy front.
It's an uncommon card, which is kinda cool.
So I can, maybe in this case,
I'm going to, it's got a lot of health.
So there's different rankings or different cards right now.
So you have a different tiering of scarcity, essentially.
Yeah, there's scarcity to it,
and we can tune all the logic, right?
So we can really play with any of these things.
I also like these abilities.
It would also do a share online,
be like, I'm playing this game,
share, if you share one card,
you can get another card, maybe.
Oh, I like that, okay.
So let's try to capture that idea.
Yeah, yeah, of course, absolutely.
Yeah, so when you're in the game,
since there's a lot of scarcity
in terms of doing ranking for the cards,
it would be a cool growth mechanic
to maybe be able to have you share a card that you made,
and then in exchange for somebody else maybe downloading,
you then get a more rare version of that card.
Oh, I like that, okay.
So bringing rarity and sort of making that
a part of the game loop, okay, great.
I'll log that in.
Cool, I love it.
Okay, and let me finish up the game
so you can see the rest of the funnel, right?
So we have our continue, I won the second round.
It looks like I'm on round three now.
I had no doubts.
Thanks, I'm pied 1-1, so let's see if I can win.
We have a projects manager,
which gives the front most guy to attack.
Well, we're just showing you an example here.
So I'm going to, see, I have 10 gold, I think, right now.
I have 10 gold.
I'm gonna sell this guy.
Well, gold's important, too,
so it sounds like in this mechanic.
Yeah, gold's sort of how you change up your lineup
in between each round.
That'd be cool.
Yeah, so there might be something to play with there,
but yeah, I'm just powered up the spot.
Play a couple rounds in a row, for instance.
I don't take any breaks, get more gold,
kind of like a streaky.
Like skip the shop or something, yeah, I like that.
Okay, let's see what happens.
We're just going to speed this up
so we can get to the end of the loop.
There you go, and that's it.
And so in this one, I take the round, and boom, I win.
You definitely need to share a screen on this, right?
Okay, that's an easy one.
We probably need to add a share screen to the win screen,
share button to the win screen,
so that when you win, you can share your result
and be able to brag about that on X.
Can players challenge each other directly?
Like if I'm Vincent, I want to specifically challenge you.
Ooh, I really like that, okay.
Because that opens up a lot of invite your friends
and stuff like that.
It can be complicated for, it's like a definitely, maybe, yeah.
Yeah, how about another idea where we make it
so that players can call out or challenge
another player of their choosing?
Maybe the other player has to accept the challenge,
kind of like words with friends kind of thing going on.
Yeah, yeah, okay, let's add that too.
And for those of you who are watching
and kind of seeing what we're doing,
we're just literally riffing about growth ideas.
I'm just kind of feeding those into RockBot
with the voice transcription.
It's not perfect, there's a lot of like,
yeah, how about that in the bot?
But the bot's figured out, right?
The agents figure it out.
You can kind of just keep giving them things.
I'll pull up the Notion dock in a minute here,
but the spot is just logging all this feedback.
Vincent, our Vincent bot is logging all this feedback
into Notion for us.
And then earlier we talked about the software factory.
We're just gonna let the software factory
lose some of these ideas.
We'll just throw agents at them.
We'll try things out.
It'll give us PRs, it'll give us play tests,
and we'll be able to kind of experiment with all this.
So, all right, so that's the core loop.
We have this windscreen, obviously,
some cleanup we gotta do here.
And that's it, so you go back home.
In that case, I don't think I earned any ELO points,
but that's okay, we'll figure that out.
And yeah, you can see the leaderboard, and there we are.
So yeah, what are your thoughts?
That's awesome, I think this is great.
And I think it's also really cool
that you have your own surface area as like a website
and the next account.
Those are, I think,
I don't know if people think about things like that.
And I think, as I was watching this stream
and thinking about it, I was like,
wow, we have so many eyeballs,
concurrent viewers right now.
It's really important if they're following X maybe
for the first time, the Thursday Arena account,
to be able to capture some of that love.
So, I think it's sometimes important
where even though you have the eyeballs,
maybe you need to very target the action
that you want people to take.
And so, maybe something cool we could put on the account
is every time somebody follows.
Hold on, do my discount, go.
So now, every time somebody follows
the at Thursday Arena X handle,
maybe we could automatically DM them.
Being like, hey, thank you for following.
You should try out our game here.
Maybe get 10 free gold.
Oh, okay.
That could be kind of cool too.
I like that.
Okay, so some way to sort of take the,
and so if I'm thinking about the rights,
we have X as sort of our platform.
That's right, yeah.
And we kind of use the followers as a way
to drive traffic to the game.
Is that how you think about that?
Totally, totally.
Because right now, I mean, our sources
of how people are finding out are pretty narrow,
which is pretty much just a stream
or maybe a post on X.
Yeah.
Like the X API, you could probably use the X API,
scrape when he's talking about Thursday Arena.
What are their thoughts, critiques, reviews?
Yeah, we actually have an X connector in Grokbot.
And so I actually already have it connected, I think.
Amazing.
So maybe we should just do that right now, right?
Maybe we'll just say, hey, do a quick search
of all of the feedback to Thursday Arena X
and summarize it in a new section in your Notion doc.
Like with user handles, too.
Is that really important?
Yeah.
Yeah, on product feedback.
Cool.
That's right.
Yeah.
Yeah, so this is really great.
You can just use the XMTP and connect
to one of the best platforms.
So love it, love it.
OK, while you were talking, I was trying to multitask
as best I can.
Yeah, I saw.
I showed this beforehand.
We have a lot of feedback.
We have this bot whose job it is to make dashboards.
And so we've talked about this before, off camera.
But internally, when we launched products at SpaceX AI,
this is one of my favorite things,
is I just spin up a metric spot.
And I'm like, hey, your job is every 15 minutes,
so give me the launch pulse.
How many users are using it?
How's the feature going?
Are there bugs that we're hearing?
As a PM, it's incredible to be able to do this
because you can basically just get your live.
You get a live dash.
It's like you have a little data intern
that's just feeding you reports on a paper,
but it's happening in Grokbot.
And something else that I think a lot of us do
is definitely maybe monitoring Slack.
People have comments and they're like,
oh, we would love to see that data slice.
And so you can have it kind of work with us
or your Slack bot or something.
And so you can get it all on demand, right?
So I want this data.
I get that data.
Exactly.
It's like immediately plugging and playing into the dashboard.
So one thing I wanted to run by you
is I got some graphs earlier.
I just asked my data scientist here
to refresh with the latest.
So this is as of, what, 11.25 AM Pacific two minutes ago.
Looks like we have about 2,200 practice rounds,
1,000 X sign ins.
Started to measure this funnel
for like a practice to an X login.
I don't know.
Is there anything we could do with that funnel?
Like how do you think about a funnel for this product?
Yeah, from the, can we go back to the screens
for the X and the practice?
Yeah, so when you're in,
so basically let me log out here.
If I log out and I just hit practice,
we obviously could do some cleanup here,
but there's an option to log in with X.
Interesting.
So you can just play the game,
get a feel for how it works.
You know, we didn't want to create a barrier
so you don't have to sign in just to play.
Maybe it's like, well,
maybe you could definitely like do a few things.
I think one simple,
the simple version would maybe be like you practice,
you know, two, three times in a row
and then you get the pop-up to sign in with X.
So I continue into game.
That can be kind of cool.
And then if I were to really put on like my,
so my roommate's actually in gaming.
So I think he always talks about these like reward mechanisms.
And so something that could be kind of cool would be,
you know, when you,
maybe you let the user in practice rounds
win a little bit more favorably.
And then you kind of can let people get a good feel
and be like, oh, we really actually want to play this game.
I like that.
It's kind of cool.
Let practice users win more often.
Yeah.
It's actually fun.
You mentioned that more often.
One of the metrics that we were looking at earlier
is we had some game engine metrics
because we really, you know,
we haven't built a ton of games before.
We played a lot of games,
but essentially we were looking at the win-loss ratios.
This is early.
This is from like the first hour,
but it was about four pretty, pretty hard games so far.
So you might want to tweak that.
But, you know, I think that's exactly your point
is we should maybe look at that slice
across practice versus logged in.
Totally.
So we have a better idea of like what that looks like.
And that might be a funnel impact.
Totally.
Yeah.
Or you can, I don't know if we've introduced
difficulty modes of like the simulated components.
We haven't yet.
And that's also a great idea.
I think it's a great feature maybe.
Right now it's just an AI
and then the head-to-head version that we're cleaning up.
But yeah, I think we have a bot here
whose job is to be the game designer critique.
And so they came back with a critique here
that looks like we have,
the game is too hard for launch.
Yeah, we should fix that.
We should fix that.
I want to go back to some of the latest funnel stats.
So this is what we came in at 11, 25.
So a few minutes to go here.
And practice sessions, practice to X, anything else?
Let me pull up.
Well, we've had some tapering off on new signups.
Thank you for everyone who caused our launch spike.
We're going to start outbounding you now.
That's the only solution.
Well, tell us about outbound.
Yeah, like what are your thoughts on outbound marketing?
How does it work?
Like, should we do any outbound here?
Totally.
Outbound's really tricky.
I mean, we've all are like maybe victims
of outbound marketing.
It's not something that you kind of want to receive
most of the time.
And so I think I was actually talking about this
with somebody yesterday.
I think the thing about outbound to get right
is you just want to make sure people read your thing.
And I think if you really think
about how people read things today,
it's like, when you open your email,
you kind of look, if you were to open your email,
I guess I would ask you,
what is the first thing you look at, do you think?
Oh, man.
I think I always get overwhelmed by the spam.
Like all the random stuff there
that I'm like, man-
So, I think it's a good idea to go and subscribe from this.
Totally, totally.
For me, I'm guilty of, I just always look at the name of the person or the vendor.
Not the subject line, not the hook or crazy, like, you must open this or whatever.
And so, I think I always think about it, like, okay, how do we then figure out who we know?
And how do we make sure you remember the names?
That you've seen these names before.
They're friendly faces that you've seen on X or LinkedIn or maybe on promotional videos.
You're saying we should get Lauren Potato to send you now.
That's what I was going to say.
She has to start sending some emails or start sending some DMs to people who follow.
There's Vincent Bot here.
Potato should send emails from Potato so we can leverage her fan following to drive usage.
Something I'm experimenting with a lot now, even, is definitely the concept of giving your bot an email.
I think that stuff can get really cool.
I think we'll open up a new page.
We should definitely do that.
Give our bot an email address and send a bunch of stuff.
Manage our campaigns.
You could probably go scrape maybe, let's call it, developer ecosystem people.
Maybe at these large gaming studios on LinkedIn.
You can enrich their work email and be like, hey, just building this new game.
You can check out us building this on stream here.
If you want to check it out, download.
Build a mailing list and contact list to reach out to.
Yeah, exactly.
It's like gaming developer ecosystem type people.
Great. This is all amazing.
We didn't know any of this.
I want to go back to the funnel here.
What's interesting here is we don't really have a strong need to convert people to signed in, at least not yet.
One of the other things we're starting to think a little about is monetization.
I'm also just curious for your thoughts on that.
We have a product.
We have maybe some ideas for how we grow usage.
I know we've had a bunch of folks over the course of these few days talking about how do you make money.
We care a lot about that, too.
I shared earlier we're in the classic San Francisco startup pod where we're just trying to get users at all costs.
We'll figure out how to monetize it later.
But it might be good to have a little bit of an idea.
What are your thoughts?
Gaming is so interesting.
I'm not by no means a gaming expert.
I sometimes read some things that people do.
That's the extent that I know.
What's really interesting about games is I think about the games I've played before.
There's so many different versions.
There's match three, which is candy crush.
That's free.
The good part about it being free is you introduce the cool down mechanism.
That allows you to show ads or other things that people have to watch to then get past those things.
But then there's open world concepts like Clash of Clans or something.
It's like a resourcing thing where you have to wait six hours.
If you want to speed it up, watch the ad or monetize.
Maybe for something like this, I would encourage a team to think about what are the levers that you think players would want more of.
I think maybe unfortunately sometimes you're introducing some friction into the game for that to actually monetize.
I think that's a fine balance.
I'm on the Slack channel and Slack right now where we're seeing a bunch of product feedback in from the world.
I didn't show you this before.
I'm in a new game.
Let's see if I can just skip through here.
I know I'm tanking my score.
That's okay.
What I wanted to show you is we have a feedback form on the website.
I'd be curious if you have any ideas on that.
If I just hit play here, let me sign in.
Looks like we might have deployed some changes.
I'm getting prompted to sign in again.
It's hard at work.
Thank you, Lauren and Matt, if they can hear us.
Feedback form.
We have a feedback form here.
We have a phone number now apparently.
That's new.
I don't know what happens if you call this number.
Try calling it live on air.
I'm a little bit nervous.
I'm sure Matt has something fun planned for that.
You can say hello from the stream.
It gets moderated first.
It gets put into our Slack channel.
Is there anything you could do?
What could be cool is if you report even a bug
or if you report anything in feedback,
you automatically get some more gold.
It could be kind of cool.
What I'm hearing, the kind of cool idea you have
is how do you create some player or store of value.
You have to have people care about something
and they can invest and decide if they want to come back.
I like this.
Let me check off our launch checklist.
We did get authentication working.
We did launch.
That was our launch checklist.
I want to go to our marketing, our growth plans.
Let's see where it went.
There's our growth playbook.
Here's what we've come up with so far.
Maybe it would be cool.
We have a list.
I love using bots to format Notion docs.
This is so great.
Let's go through the idea list here.
It looks like we have some impact and effort scores.
What I want to do live on stream
is ask you to help me stack rank these growth things.
Everything we've talked about,
let's summarize them into a list of what we think is going to be
most leveraged to lowest leveraged
and then we'll go through some agents on them
and get them prioritized.
We might disagree with the bot that put this together.
What are your thoughts?
Sharing your wins, sharing your bot card
for the tier of stuff we talked about,
challenging a player,
a weekly clip or leaderboard screenshot.
That's a good one.
Avatar showcase, the welcome DMs.
I know you're a big fan of the welcome DMs.
I'm a big fan of welcome DMs.
I think we've seen this a lot.
Speed delete is so important.
You're following me right now.
That means you're interested.
I've got to somehow get in touch with you
as fast as possible to be able to capture your interest.
What are your other favorites?
Maybe you can pick our top three.
If we want to ultimately have X signups,
that feels pretty great.
Find a way to drive more X signups.
I like that.
You've got to love the high impact, low effort.
Upper right hand quadrant.
You should get a graph of that from our bots.
I like that.
Any others here that catch your eye?
Emails from Lauren's fan list,
building our mailing list.
I kind of like the share ideas.
I think it's easy to share the leaderboard status.
You want to feel rewarded.
Let's find where that one is.
It feels so hard.
It's a point of pride.
I think we have a good list of three here.
I'm going to feed this into our engineering.
There's a lot of good ideas here.
Anything you think we're missing that we haven't talked about?
No, I think definitely the danger is adding too many things.
We're hitting users every which way with some random thing that they don't want.
Awesome.
We are super excited about all of this.
I think this is a really great list.
Vincent, before we wrap up chatting with you,
any other final thoughts?
Any other thoughts on growth for the types of products you'd want to share?
Anything else you'd want to bring up?
I think definitely getting PMF for the game first.
I think a lot of people always think about how can we grow it immediately?
There's a bit of a trick in the egg,
but I think you should definitely break down what is more marketing versus what is more growth.
I think those two things are definitely more different.
Marketing is definitely more top of funneling.
Then once you get people in,
then how do you continue to maximize essentially what are the best parts of your product?
Yeah, I like that.
So establishing some baseline metrics,
figuring out how you kind of move people from that funnel and kind of going from there.
Yeah, exactly.
I'm curious too.
You're a crock-bob power user.
We've been talking a lot about the game.
We can maybe stop sharing my screen for a bit,
and just maybe chat a little bit.
Not about the game, but like,
what are some of the ways that you like to use RockBot?
I'm sure a lot of those ideas that are there,
you shared a lot of them with us.
Yeah.
But what are some of your ways that you use RockBot in your job every day?
Totally.
I think the unique part about growth sometimes
is you're asked to do a lot of things like zero to one by yourself, kind of,
because there's like no resourcing,
and you kind of have to prove that it deserves a bit more scope.
And so a lot of that means like,
you're kind of putting on one hand,
being a data scientist,
looking at the data,
maybe then you're looking into like,
what does that look like on the screen
if somebody were to see it for the first time,
and for emailing even,
it's like, what does it look like to the person receiving it?
And so I actually,
one of the new things I discovered even last night
about how I use bots,
when I spin up a new bot,
and yeah, you can name it like Data Scientist,
it doesn't necessarily mean that like the bot
knows how to be the best data scientist.
And so I actually told my bot yesterday
to go take a lot of one-on-one, two-on-one,
three-on-one courses on being the best data scientist.
Yeah, that's really cool.
I just found a bunch of classes.
And when I found a bunch,
basically downloaded these little parts
that were like personalities that I felt like
were very key traits to like a good data scientist,
and then was able to keep that as like a persistent scale,
essentially, within the bot, which is so cool.
Like I was like,
I basically also did it to a designer,
I was like asking him to scope some things,
and I was like, this looks kind of ugly.
And so I was like, go take a ton of courses,
basically, a better designer.
That's a great prompt actor, I never thought of that.
It's like, go teach yourself how to do X
and be an expert on the thing.
Yeah, because I think like there's so many things
like in a previous life, I was working at a bigger bank,
and you're told to build all these models,
and so there's some like core primitives,
like building things, like spreadsheets or slides
that are like just like these small things
that you know not to do,
but maybe sometimes that hasn't quite translated
to your bot, so it's like,
don't hardcode things themselves, maybe.
So it's like, okay, always try to use a formula.
Unless it's like an input.
Yeah, one of the ways I like to think about these bots
is that they often are sort of like interns
that you brought onto your team.
Exactly, I say it all the time.
And you have to sort of teach your intern,
or you know, maybe not an intern,
maybe like a full-fledged colleague,
but you have to teach that colleague
kind of onboard them to your work, right?
That's right.
If we're hiring someone into SpaceX AI,
we spend some time kind of teaching them
how everything works, what tools do we use,
how do you get things done at the company, right?
And I think this is true of many companies,
and so, you know, spending the time to onboard your bot
I think is a really important thing.
It's really important.
I think you just get a lot more value out of it, too.
Yeah.
And I think it's like, it's how you want it to be done.
Right.
We all talk in a certain way.
Yeah.
Like I have one bot that just looks at how I talk in Slack,
so like how I talk in Slack with, you know,
my teammates in a team group chat,
maybe it's a bit different than like a general announcement.
And so like, you know, learning the language
and how I think about it.
That's awesome.
Any other fun bots that you have
that you want to highlight?
Yeah.
I'll have to shout out, like I think,
the one that I really love is the bot
doing stand up with all the other bots.
To me, I'm like, that's such a good way to summarize
like what's been happening in my day.
And how do you use that?
Yeah.
Like we, so we have this like main bot, the grok bot now.
And so that grok bot is like my main grok bot
and kind of just talks to all the other bots.
And I'm like, hey, hold stand up at 9 a.m. every day.
Just get a quick pulse check.
What are everybody working on?
And I sometimes do like to go into specific bots
to like do more one-to-one chats.
And then so I'm like, then do a round up
at the end of the day.
Right.
And re-download and re-get context,
like which bots are working on what.
And so I kind of use a bit of a hybrid,
like one bot fits all versus like specific bots
for myself.
Yeah.
Love it.
And so that's really helpful to all that context.
That's awesome.
Amazing.
Awesome.
Well, I think we are going to cut over a little bit.
Yeah.
So we have maybe a couple of promos
we want to talk about.
Is that right?
Yeah.
I think we have two promos,
which hopefully is good top of funnel for our game
and for our stream here.
And so one of the different one of the offers
that we'd like to have is for every single
like if you were here earlier,
we did a promo for new users,
but we want to take care of all of our existing users too.
So now if you comment reset,
that's R-E-S-E-T in the chat
and your existing Grokbot user,
we'll be able to do a reset of your account
by the end of today.
If you pull up my screen,
I have this for folks who are on the stream.
So earlier today you said,
yeah, we gave away some free Grokbot.
That was for only for new users.
Chat, we heard you.
We know some of you are already using Grokbot.
And so do you want to share again?
Yeah, exactly.
Yeah.
So if you're just coming on the stream right now,
basically within the next 15 minutes,
if you're an existing Grokbot user
and you've been hitting your limits,
we're going to reset that.
So make sure to post in chat reset
and then by the end of the day,
in the next 15 minutes,
you will have a Grokbot reset in your account.
Cue the chat reset spam.
I don't have it up right now,
but I imagine the chat is going wild right now
with all these reset requests.
Amazing. This is really cool.
And I think we actually might have one more.
Okay.
And I think we're running it again.
So also if you are now a new user,
new users who sign up in the next 15 minutes.
Also, if you just go to the link,
x.ai slash bot,
new users who sign up in the next 15 minutes,
create an account set of recurring tasks,
we'll also get one free month of Grokbot.
Amazing.
We talked about growth earlier,
and I feel like one of the best growth hacks
is just give stuff away for free.
Yeah.
What would you say to that?
I think the thing that it's kind of like that curve
where you're kind of like, you know,
growth is like just about winning hearts and minds.
And then there's like the, oh my God,
you need to do all these different things.
And it's just about winning hearts and minds.
I do think growth is also just like,
how would I want to be treated as a user?
Yeah.
That's most of how I think.
Wow. I really like that sort of
how would I want to be treated as a user?
I'm using a product.
Yeah.
Put yourself in the shoes of someone
using something else and like figure out what you'd want.
I really, really love that.
So, okay.
Sounds like we have two promos.
We have a Grokbot reset.
So in the next probably 10 minutes now, 13 minutes now.
If you post in the chat reset,
you'll get a Grokbot reset by the end of the day,
the end of the day tomorrow maybe,
depending on how long it takes.
Cool.
End of day.
And then if you're new to Grokbot
in the next 15 minutes,
you can download Grokbot,
create an account, set up a recurring task,
and get a free month.
And these are valid only for the next 15 minutes.
Limited time offer.
Yeah.
I'll just show both of these again.
So here's that first QR code.
I think it's actually the same QR code.
Should be the same one.
Awesome.
Same QR code.
So you can see both of those.
And cool.
So just to give you guys a sense of what's going to happen next,
if you're just tuning in,
we are in the middle of a three-day livestream here
where we are building a game studio as our business
and building a game.
We just launched our first game this morning.
Lauren and Matt are working away at adding a level,
sort of fixing our next set of bugs
and continuing some of the engineering work
to polish up the game,
take into account all the feedback that we've gotten so far,
which has been really incredible.
So thanks, everyone, for coming and sharing all that.
The game is at ThursdayArena.com.
No, www.
Just ThursdayArena.com.
And we are at ThursdayArena on Slack.
And those are the only sources of official information
about this project.
So if you're seeing anything anywhere else
that is from anywhere else,
and it's not us,
we are just at ThursdayArena and ThursdayArena.com.
Please check out the game.
Give us some feedback in the game.
There's a little cool leaderboard there
where you can kind of see how you do
against your friends or other people.
Super excited about this
and to make it better throughout the day.
We are doing all of this live
right next to Dreamforce in San Francisco.
So we are just like a half block away
from the big outdoor park.
We are in a building here
where we're doing a bunch of stuff
all happening all at once.
There's a main stage downstairs
where we've been doing a bunch of talks
and letting people come in and build
and learn how to use Grokbot.
We have a studio space upstairs right here
where we've been putting together the stream
and bringing on a bunch of really great guests
to chat with us
just to give you a sense of what's going to happen
in the next few minutes.
So I think Vincent,
we're going to let you go
and get back to continuing to grow
the SpaceX AI business
and helping Grokbot grow.
I'll probably stick around for a bit.
We'll try to see if we can bring
the rest of our build team back on
and see how much progress they've made.
And then we're going to have another guest,
I believe, around noon-ish
in the next few minutes.
And so we'll maybe take a quick
two-minute break right now
to give us a chance to reset the studio
and then we'll be right back.
So, Vincent, thank you again.
We're going to go get all these growth ideas
implemented and hopefully we can see
some cool pipeline changes.
Amazing.
I hear people DMing me,
showing me their wins.
Amazing.
I'm on X.
Oh, I love it.
Okay, and then we did have your X
handle up on the screen a second ago
so if you just rewind a little bit
you could find Vincent where to follow him.
Yeah, Vincent ZHU.
So, just Vincent Jue.
Awesome.
Yeah.
Thank you so much, Vincent.
Good to see you.
Yeah, of course. Thanks, Rich.
We'll be right back.
Thank you.
All right, we are back.
We are building Thursday Arena.
So, for those of you who are just tuning in
or maybe you tuned in earlier
and you forgot for some reason,
we are building Thursday Arena.
This is a three-day live stream here
at Grokbot Galaxy, which is our event
right next to Dreamforce live in San Francisco.
My name is Roshan.
I work on product at SpaceX AI.
I'm joined by a guest here.
We'll introduce very, very soon.
But wanting to just catch everyone up
on what's going on.
So, we are spending three days here
building a business.
The business we're building is a game studio
and we just launched our first game earlier today,
ThursdayArena.com at ThursdayArena on X.
Please give it a try.
We have a bunch of UI polish that we're working on.
Lauren and Matt who are on the team here
are just right around the corner
working on building and incorporating
all the great feedback that's been coming in so far.
And our hope and goal here
is to make a bunch of improvements
over the course of the day.
So, excited that we'll be able to kind of
continue making things better.
What we've been doing kind of
while the build is going on
is bringing on a few guests.
So, in the last half hour,
we just had Vincent Jue join
who works on our growth team here at SpaceX AI.
Gave us a ton of great ideas
for how to grow this business.
So, we started the business.
We have a product, joking earlier,
that we're going with the classic San Francisco
startup vibe where we're going to just go get users
and we'll figure out how to monetize it later.
But, you know, my colleagues tell me
that this is later so you got to figure out
how to monetize since we have some users.
Yeah, so we're on day three.
We're kind of in the stretch,
home stretch here.
But anyways, we're super excited to have
on another guest.
And so, yeah, why don't you take a second
to introduce yourself,
share a little bit about what you work on.
Yeah, awesome.
So, I'm Matthew.
It's really great to join all of you.
I'm on the marketing ops team
here at SpaceX AI.
And what that means in practice
is I really build tools and automations
that help our marketing and sales teams
work more effectively.
And so, you can imagine there's a lot
that I do with Grokbot,
both internally in my work,
but also in terms of enabling the field
to work more effectively with Grokbot
and to do things in a lot more of an
automated and interesting way.
Love it.
We love automation here.
If you're just joining us,
we have been using Grokbots
to build this entire business.
And a lot of it is automation heavy.
We're trying to get as much stuff
to be sort of auto-building,
auto-improving as we can,
and kind of getting that whole engine
built around it all.
We've thus far been focused
on the development and code process
for that.
So, I'm really excited to be able
to spend some time,
chat about how we can use
some of those same techniques
to grow and build our business.
Yeah.
So, you know, I wanted to start out
with just kind of,
what are your overall thoughts
on how you use Grokbot in your role?
Yeah.
Maybe just walk us through
a couple of common workloads
that you've built.
And then I'd love to show you
the game that we've built,
and maybe we can walk through it together,
see if you see any opportunities
for us to either use some of those techniques
or maybe build some of our own.
Yeah, for sure.
So, there are two main use cases,
and for those who have been
watching our stream
for the past couple of hours,
I was able to highlight these on stage.
The two main use cases
are really keeping myself sane
and reducing the context switching.
And so I, like so many people,
have landed on this paradigm
of a Chief of Staff agent.
And for me,
I think the real unlock
that takes it past like the Chief of Staff
just being who I talk to
to try getting anything done
is the fact that I gave
my Chief of Staff agent access
to all my inboxes.
Yeah.
Like not just a couple,
but truly everything.
How many inboxes do you have?
More than you might think.
Okay, same work.
It's like all my email addresses,
my calendars,
even like different chat accounts.
And so really across personal
and professional use cases,
I have all this information
coming at me, and of course,
there's Slack.
And I think number one
in today's day and age
is distilling all of that,
figuring out, okay,
what are the tasks?
What are just the FYIs
of the things that are tasks?
How do I get stuck into them?
And so what my Chief of Staff does,
which I think is maybe
a bit differentiated
than the typical use case,
is it can handle the whole end-to-end.
I call it a self-completing task list.
And so it's tapped
into all my inboxes.
It receives what's coming
into those inboxes
on a regular basis.
It determines what subset
of that information is tasks.
And then it identifies
which of my other specialist bots
are best positioned
to take a first stab
at those tasks.
Cool, okay.
So what's an example?
So it sounds like,
oh yeah, maybe just an example
from something you do.
Yeah, so for example,
one thing is like
territory planning
or territory disputes.
So I'm on the MarOps team,
but it's really sort of
a combined RevOps
and MarOps team.
We work across marketing
and sales.
RevOps and marketing ops
for those who aren't familiar
with that.
Exactly, revenue operations,
marketing operations.
And when you're growing
a massive business,
you're hiring all these
salespeople.
They all have different
territories that they own.
And sometimes like you
are a salesperson,
you meet someone at an event,
they exchange contact info
with you and you're like,
great, I can bring this deal on board.
Super excited,
I'm going to follow up with them.
And then all of a sudden
you realize, wait,
I actually don't own that account
and my colleague does.
And so I met the person,
but really they should be
the one following up.
That's a territory dispute.
And so you might face
instances of this pretty often
where you're,
especially if you have
a large sales team,
you're getting tickets saying,
hey, I don't know if I should
work this or not.
And often, at least in the past,
it would take a lot of human judgment
to point out the rules
and the processes,
and this is the right way to do it,
and you should have clicked that button,
not this button.
But what we can do now
is in a much more automated way,
understand what's really going on here,
how does this align with our rules of engagement,
and what's the policy moving forward.
Awesome.
So it sounds like company
with a large sales team
need a way to manage
some of those things,
make that more automated,
less about having a bunch
of people in a room all the time.
Yeah.
What are your thoughts on sales ops
or marketing ops
for a three-person company
that has a single game on the website?
Yes.
So I've been thinking about this a lot,
and obviously...
Obviously a very different kind of business, right?
Very different.
But fundamentally,
every business is really,
it's a bit cheesy,
but every business exists
to connect with people
and do something valuable
or entertaining or memorable.
And I think when you come back
to that fundamental principle,
it sort of helps guide your decision.
So if you're thinking about
a consumer standpoint,
you want to get a game
out into the world,
to the people who are going to be
most entertained by it.
Yeah.
If you're thinking about from like,
how do we keep this ship running?
You're like, we got to pay the bill somehow.
Yep.
We can make people pay for it,
or we can make it an ad-driven
kind of experience.
Well, I'm glad you segued it
into the monetization part.
That was sort of the thing
I wanted to do live with you
if you're down.
So if we can pull up my screen on the stream, for those who were joining us earlier,
I'm going to walk through the game. So you might have seen some of this already,
but Matt has not. And so I'm going to show Matt the game.
Hopefully there's been some cool updates that are also been built in behind the scenes.
Maybe we'll see some quick bug fixes too. And so I'm going to walk through the game.
And what I'd love to do is figure out what opportunities you see in this process for
how we could build a business, monetize it. You have some ideas,
so you kind of see some of those ideas too. The core game is called Thursday Arena,
and it's ThursdayArena.com. Please hop in and play if you want to give it a shot.
We have an option to log in with x or just hop into practice mode. I'll just log in with
my account so we can try and have this count against my winnings.
If I go into the game, we have a leaderboard. I can see all the people on the leaderboard.
Looks like we now have nine players who have made it onto the Platinum list.
Platinum tier players, congrats to those nine.
There were some different names up there the last time I looked at this.
And so we definitely, I'm down to 37 now.
Oh, boy.
Not really doing as well.
Hey, you've been hard at work on other things.
Sorry.
Yeah, fair. I haven't had as much time to play.
Exactly.
And it looks like we have a nice visual bug here too,
but over a thousand users logged in, which is incredible.
So thank you to everyone who's playing the game and trying it out and giving us feedback.
So that's our leaderboard.
If I go back to the homepage, we obviously have a little bit of a sponsor form fill here.
I could probably move that around a little bit, but get a little way to reach out to us
if you're interested in sponsoring the stream or sponsoring the game.
So obviously, I think that could be a really fun avenue without some ads and stuff.
You can also see the core game loop.
So I hit play. Basically, we're drafting a team of bots here.
I can choose the bots I want to buy.
And I can go ahead and put them in an order and pair it up with another teammate.
The bots do their thing, some cute animations there.
Nice.
And we have NYC parents.
That's NYC parents.
These are all bots that are taken from our bot marketplace, by the way.
Do you have a bot in the marketplace?
I do have a couple.
Okay. Okay.
What are your bots called?
I have one called Inbot.
So that's the template that I made for managing my inboxes.
Okay. Okay.
Let's see if we can get that one in here.
Inbot.
It should come up.
In Inbot?
In I-N-B-O-T.
And it's not showing up there.
Maybe not.
We might have renamed someone before another one.
Yeah.
What was your other one?
I can't remember right now, but I sort of like some of the ones that I'm seeing.
Like, what's Cooper?
Cooper?
That's a good question. I don't know.
Yeah. Okay.
We took out the bot descriptions, but we could definitely go to-
Let's go with one of these.
Yeah.
Well, you know what? We could just pull this up live.
So we have x.ai.bot. marketplace.
What is Cooper?
Cooper.
Tommy Hansen has a bot called Cooper that is a news agent for AI, tech,
venture capital, and business.
It delivers a tight daily Slack briefing of top stories at 8 a.m.
Sounds pretty good to me.
Yeah.
Weekday, midday competitor alerts only when something truly clears the bar.
This is really cool.
So if you haven't seen this yet, x.ai.bot. marketplace is our bot marketplace.
And so you can go into this marketplace.
You can see bots that have been published by some of the people we've been working with,
some great examples we've seen out there for how people are using
these bots have memories, so they can come preloaded with a bunch of context
and sort of what they should do for their job.
They also come preloaded with routines.
So this bot knows that when you install it,
it should send you a briefing every morning at 8 a.m.
You can go in and tune in, of course, and make it your own.
And it also has some integration.
So bots can connect to all the tools and services that you're using.
Obviously, connecting to Slack is a really important one to be able to
understand what's going on in the business or understand what's going on in your company.
So yeah, that's Cooper.
Nice.
We actually took a lot of these bots,
and we had them sort of be the first versions of our little bot marketplace here.
It's fantastic.
And by the way, just something else that I want to call out about the marketplace
is there are certain tools that have marketplaces
where you really need to lean on that thing
because the tools themselves are really complicated.
And it's like, I'm not going to learn how to build this complex.
Let me just copy it.
This is a tool where the marketplace seeds amazing ideas.
You should go to that first, start there.
But then you sort of realize, wait, I could create a template this good
by just thinking deeply about what I'm trying to do
and what connectors there are.
It's such a simple tool to build your own bots from scratch if you need to.
Completely agree.
And for folks who haven't seen it,
so I'm just pulling up my Grokbot here.
We've had a bunch of bots running and building this whole business.
I got my chief of staff.
I got Dr. Eggbot that helps me make new bots.
I got my data scientist who I promoted up here
because we've been looking at a lot of data.
You can just share these.
You hit share, it shares the template.
The bot will pop itself up and make itself a template, right?
Exactly.
Before the call, you actually share a template with me, right?
Yeah.
And so is that this one?
Is that Cerebro?
Exactly.
Cool.
That's Cerebro here.
All right, tell us about Cerebro.
Yeah.
So to my point earlier about what you're really doing
when you're thinking about growth, I don't know if you've seen X-Men.
Yeah, of course.
OK.
It's a great name.
Yeah.
Have you heard of it?
So Professor X, he sits down in that chair.
He puts that helmet on.
Right.
And then you see that big screen in front of him.
And he's just sitting there thinking about all the mutants
out in the world that he's looking for trying to track down.
And you see them all appear on the screen.
Well, when I think about what we're really doing
when we're trying to get something out into the world,
it's sort of like Cerebro, right?
You're sort of sitting down and you're thinking, OK,
what did we build?
Who did we really build it for?
How can we find them out in the world?
And not just by saying, like, we sell to this industry,
companies with as much revenue for like a B2B business.
But instead, really thinking outside the box about,
like, who are the human beings who we think
would be really excited if they knew that this thing existed?
Yeah.
And so what Cerebro does, and maybe we can take it
for a spin if we have time, is it really helps you come up
with, like, who is your ideal customer profile?
OK.
I have sort of an idea for how we can adapt it here.
Once you determine who that is, you can think, OK,
what data do we need to find?
Let's just do it.
Let's not go.
Let's do it.
So I'm going to hit refresh.
And we just see that we can install the bot.
Here's Cerebro installing in my Grok bot.
It looks like it comes with a bunch of context.
So Clay MCP specialist, AmpliMarket MCP specialist.
Not sure if we can connect those live.
But we can hopefully work with, yeah, I got the concept.
Yeah.
And yeah, some cool plugins.
So let me add this bot.
Cerebro has joined the team.
OK.
I'm going to pin Cerebro so we can make it
a little bit easier to see him up here.
And yeah, so I guess the bot installs itself.
Yep.
Tells it just sets him up.
We need one of those.
We don't have a go-to-market bot yet.
So I'm going to go ahead and assign a label to this bot too
while we're in here.
Uh-huh.
GTM.
OK.
Perfect.
Maybe let's just skip the plugins for now.
Yeah.
And you said you had some ideas for how
we might use Cerebro with our game.
Yeah, exactly.
Tell me more.
OK.
So you're building this game.
And again, you probably don't want an experience
where people have to pay to play the game.
Like maybe there are-
No pay to win.
I think we decided we don't want to make it
so that you'd have to pay to get more powerful.
Those mechanics get a little bit more-
Yeah, exactly.
Then you sort of just-
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And so I think the experience that you want
is making it ad-supported.
But when we think about these ad slots that we want to sell,
we could go the easy route and be like,
hey, whoever will give us money,
let's put those ads on the screen.
But then you get a really bad experience
where people are playing the game
and these random unrelated ads are showing up.
And sure, you're getting money,
but it doesn't really feel good.
It doesn't feel cohesive.
And so what I was thinking about and what we could use-
Let me pause you.
I'm going to just turn on the voice notation here
and we can just capture what you're saying
and speed it into the bot.
Does that work?
Absolutely.
Okay, go ahead and keep going.
Yeah, perfect.
Okay, so Cerebro, what we would like to work on with you
is really finding our ICP
in terms of who we should put in these ad slots.
So you have a skill.
It's called Find My ICP.
I think you should be able to run it
just by me invoking it here.
And what you'll help us do is really brainstorm
like who do we want filling up these ad slots.
And some thoughts that come to mind are like,
if you're sitting and playing this game,
maybe you're thinking about what are some other fun games
that exist that I could discover.
Maybe it's some snacks.
I'm sitting and playing
and I want something while I pass the time.
And so essentially what Cerebro will help us do
is come up with those creative ideas.
Okay, so let's go ahead and send that off.
One thing I'm also going to do,
and I like to do this when I'm adding a new bot to my team,
is I have a Chief of Staff bot
or a Dr. Eggbot who's helping coordinate things.
Also, reach out to Chief to get a brief
of what we're actually building.
Yeah, perfect.
Like the game and stuff.
And this is also cool too.
I love just messaging with my bots
as if they're just colleagues
and just chatting with them on iMessage or Slack
or something like that.
And so, yeah, just fired up a couple of messages.
This way, Cerebro has some context
on what it is we're actually doing
so it knows what those ad slots are.
A hundred percent.
And you said there was a skill in here
that does some of that ICP work.
Yeah, so if we hit slash,
I wonder if it'll show up
if it got packaged up with...
Find, oops, maybe it didn't get packaged up.
Okay, no worries.
And I think this will be able to...
Make that a little bigger for everyone.
...give us some good ideas to start with.
Where really we're starting from first principles
of who do we think we would want to reach out to
and say, hey, we've got an ad slot here.
We've got this audience convened
of highly interested, highly engaged people.
You can get in front of them
with the type of product
that they'll be interested in.
Yep.
So maybe we could take a look.
So other games got indie studios, casual games.
Games like the Discovery Platform.
Yeah, snack brands and energy drinks.
Okay, this kind of thing makes sense, right?
And I think the next thing that we want to ask
is essentially like...
Oh, I like merch.
Oh, that's true.
It could make some Thursday Arena merch.
Oh, 100%.
That could be cool.
Yep.
There are lots of ways.
And what I would do is...
And maybe we can turn the dictation on.
Yeah, let's do it.
Perfect.
Okay, and we got signal recipes here.
Yeah, why don't we take a look at that
and then we'll transcribe.
So it looks like we got...
Okay, so walk me through what's happening here.
So it looks like there's an ICP,
there's personas, segments, scoring points.
A lot of stuff going on here.
Yes, yes, yes.
Maybe some of us or some folks watching
are not as familiar with all these terms.
And so just like, you know,
give us the 101 here.
On what just happened.
Yeah, and also the awesome thing is
it looks like it had that skill in its memory.
So it was able to invoke it for us.
Awesome, awesome.
And this is the kind of output we would expect.
Okay.
So ICP, ideal customer profile.
You know, so many of these terms
like RevOps and MarOps are the kind of things
like none of us knew what these were
when we were kids.
Right.
And we get into this business world.
Unless you are a very interesting child.
Right, maybe.
Who knows?
And then you get into this business world
and there are all these concepts you have to learn.
Fundamentally, you can think of your ICP
as like who are we trying to reach out in the world?
Who's on that screen
when we put the Cerebro helmet on?
And so then you think in a bit more detail
like, okay, who are the personas
that we're selling to?
So like if we had to have different avatars
for the different like main categories of people.
Right.
Who we want to reach.
How would we bucket them?
So it looks like, yeah, brands, sponsorships.
Partnerships and platforms.
Yeah, we want to probably like,
there's game platforms out there
that can drive traffic to us, right?
That could be really cool.
Exactly.
True segments.
Yeah, so then I would think of,
so basically you can think of the segments
as like just another grouping of those personas,
like the priority order
that you should go after these sets of people.
Okay.
What do you think about this?
I mean, just having been involved
in building the game past few days,
how does this land with you?
Yeah, it's interesting.
I mean, I think we, you know,
earlier, I guess yesterday or so,
we were thinking through a bunch
of different modernization ideas.
And so, you know, we knew we didn't want
to make this a pay to win game.
That's just not really fun for most folks.
And, you know, we don't like those kinds of games.
So we didn't want to build something we wouldn't like.
But we did know that we need to build a business here.
Like we're a brand new game studio.
It's a notoriously difficult industry to operate in.
And so we kind of immediately went to ads
as an idea where we could sell some screen estates
since we have, you know,
hopefully a bunch more folks
signing up and using the app.
Yeah.
You know, I think there's a lot more
we could go from there.
I hadn't even considered the partnerships angle.
Yeah.
How do we drive more traffic?
And that can be really interesting.
Like if we have an ad sort of served
and we can drive more traffic,
like that becomes an interesting flywheel
maybe that we go and try to put in place.
Exactly.
Obviously, the partnerships would take
a little more time to put together.
But maybe some of these things are self-serve.
So we could do like that.
We also have options to maybe explore social
and paid ads and some of that stuff.
And so that would also just be great
to drive traffic in.
But obviously, you know,
we need to make sure that there's something
on the other end, right?
We're not just spending a bunch of money.
Exactly.
And so that's something that will highlight
a bit less in the Cerebro demo,
but I just sort of want to talk through.
So when you think about growth,
there are really like two fronts,
two major buckets that I would put
types of growth in.
So there's obviously like
consumer-oriented growth, PLG,
and then there is more SLG,
like sales-led growth.
And I would say, in your case,
the PLG is, yeah,
how do you like get more people
to play the game?
Yeah.
The SLG is that's going to be partnerships.
It's going to be filling the ad slots.
Those kind of conversations are like,
it's going to be a smaller number
of people that you're going after
to like sell the ad slot
or set up the partnership.
But that's going to be a much more
concerted effort of like coming up
with a really good cold email to send.
And maybe in that cold email,
you'll cite some statistics
from that first bucket.
You'll say, hey,
we built a game that hit,
you know, x number of users
and y number of days.
Yeah.
And so those two worlds
sort of interact with each other.
And that's where the flywheel comes in.
Like the more you can build
these one-on-one partnerships
with advertisers,
with promoters,
with partners,
the more they can drive traffic,
the traffic increases,
and then you have something better
to offer to future advertisers
and partners.
I just took some of that
and just kind of fed it into the bot
so we could all lose that thought
because I really like that idea.
Yeah.
But it looks like you have this idea
in here of like signal recipes.
Can you talk a little bit more
about what those are?
Yeah.
So that's essentially like,
okay, so again,
to come back to this cerebral metaphor.
So like,
let's say you have that screen
in front of you,
you're trying to picture
who you're reaching out to.
But it's really fuzzy.
Like you can sort of see
people's silhouettes,
but you don't really know,
okay, well, like,
what do I know about them?
What could I even say in an email?
You're not just going to send
a cold email being like,
game to advertise on,
click here to...
We could try that.
I mean, you could,
but, you know,
you could and sometimes it works.
Especially if your numbers are good.
If you can say,
hey, we have this many eyeballs,
right now, you know,
you want to get your product.
But another thing you can do
is make that picture higher resolution
by gathering signals and data
on those people
that you're going after.
Yep.
So it's not just any advertiser.
It's not just any snack brand,
but maybe it's a snack brand
that only came into existence recently
that is putting out products
that are like unhealthy,
but made healthier.
Yep.
And they want to really
get out into the market
and reach an audience
that loves junk food,
but wants something healthier.
Yeah, so tapping into like...
Super niche.
Yeah, so sort of like,
kind of what I'm hearing there
is, you know,
part of this is finding partners,
growing your business,
having the stuff you can lead with,
but, you know,
part of it is also,
it sounds like finding
the right partner.
Yeah, exactly.
Maybe there's a specific kind
of partner that's the right one
for your business,
or a specific kind of advertiser
that feels really native
on your platform.
It sounds like that's kind of
what you're saying.
Exactly, exactly.
Because then the incentives
are all going to be right.
Like, they're going to want
to answer your email.
Yep.
Because it's not just any email.
Yeah, no, that makes a lot of sense.
While you were talking,
you reminded me we have a bot here
whose job it is to
keep an eye on our numbers.
And so, yeah,
it looks like we have over 3,000
matches with a few hours.
So I don't know how that compares
to other ad models
or platforms, or gaming, or games.
But I don't know,
seems like a cool number
to be at so far.
We had an early traffic spike
right when we launched the game.
There we go.
Around 600 signups.
It looks like we're still
filtering more people in.
So, yeah, it looks like
we still have folks signing up.
Our bot decided to change
the colors on these charts for us,
which is fun.
I'm getting a 15-minute pulse
of all the stats.
Yeah, that's right.
Let's just add
hourly active users.
total user account over time to this.
If you had to come up with a theory
as to who you're reaching so far.
I mean, obviously,
we've got the live stream going on.
Obviously, there were probably
a lot of fans of Grokbot,
of SpaceX AI out there
who want to try this out
because we're building it.
But do you have any other
early theories, especially around
the name of the game
and the concept of the game
is so particular?
Do you think there are
any patterns you might draw?
Is that like who's using
this game and why?
It's a great question.
Let me switch back to Cerebro here.
I don't think we have
a ton of thoughts beyond
we knew we needed
to build something today.
We thought we'd build a game.
So short answer, no.
But I don't know.
I feel like there's
a really interesting niche
of folks who really enjoy
sort of like the downtime games.
You have a few minutes
in the middle of your day.
You want to do something
that makes you think a little bit.
I think our niche is
sort of the puzzle gamers
or the folks who are
playing words with friends
and taking a quick turn.
Maybe the folks who are, you know,
I feel like we should record this.
We should like feed
this into Cerebro.
Let's try it.
Okay.
Hey, Cerebro.
So we're thinking a little bit
more about our segments
based on what you shared
with us earlier.
And thinking about this out loud,
I think, you know,
what's great about
Thursday Arena is that
it's really quick
and easy to play.
And so maybe some of the segments
we should think about
are customers or users
who are more casual gamers, right?
They want to hop in,
maybe play for a little bit
during a five minute break
or spend a little bit of time
doing something with their brain.
In between meetings
or something like that at work.
But wondering if we can think
a little bit more
about our segments
given all that.
Yeah.
And I think the thing to highlight
is like especially
if you're thinking about
advertisers and partners
and maybe we can feed this
in as well,
is you sort of start with
like who's in your.
I'm going to record you.
Yeah.
And essentially,
we want to give you
that context, Cerebro,
because that's who uses our game.
And so we want to think about,
okay, those people,
what other products and services
are those people interested in?
Like maybe those people
are also the people
who between meetings
want to like read the news
and get smart on the news.
Like that sort of feeds
into who we should think about
with partnerships and advertisers.
Cool. Okay.
So it looks like
Cerebro is going to take this.
There's a lot of really good stuff.
I think you already
sort of understood
the concept by the way.
Yeah.
Extrapolating it to.
I love this.
I want to actually go up to this
because reading this a second ago.
And I love how
we basically have now
sort of some really good stats.
What I love about the bot team,
Cerebro can like reach out
to the other box and be like,
hey, I need to write an email.
Like give me the data for the email.
And it actually makes it so easy.
So like everything just like
your team just working for you.
Don't lead with beacon current.
Don't lead with these certain things.
Here's the revised openers, right?
Like we shipped it this morning
and we have a thousand players
and 440 matches in the last hour.
Yeah, it's really cool
having this really cool.
We didn't have any of this yesterday.
So and also imagine
like the old way of doing things.
These are completely
different teams.
Yeah, like the person
executing these outbound campaigns
or like on the partnerships team
might have to be like,
hey, can we pull the latest data?
And okay, let me talk
to the data team.
Like there's so much.
Yeah, so many steps
you have to go through.
This is just a bunch of bots.
Yeah, and they all share in the context.
Yeah, I think that when the context
is on the agent team,
I feel like it adds this level of they all
they can just hang out
and chat with each other.
You're talking about standups earlier.
I think same same idea.
Oh yeah, totally.
Cool.
Well, then we talked a little bit
about our segments.
Looks like we got some updates here.
So we're great casuals,
scroll substitutes.
There you go.
I might put myself in this category.
It's like forget the Instagram reels
just like play a quick game
of Thursday Arena.
Yeah, that should be kind of cool.
I could I could see that.
Yeah, that feeds into messaging, right?
Like these are fundamentally
these are stories
that we're trying to tell
about why our game
exists out in the world.
Totally.
And when we can share that story
with the right people out there.
Yeah, they're like,
yeah, I get that.
I want to be part of that.
Yeah, cool.
Well, I love this.
This is all great.
And then it looks like
the bot is asking us
if we want to kind of lock
in a mark segment.
And then we gave it some more context
and here you go.
Like some actual personas, right?
So this is awesome
because I feel like we can kind of
what I always appreciate
when it comes to product
is thinking about your customer
putting yourself
in your user's shoes.
Exactly.
Thinking about user stories,
like when am I going to engage
with the product?
When am I going to engage
with the app?
How am I going to engage with it?
Like what am I seeking from it?
Like these types of questions
sound kind of esoteric
and philosophical,
but I think they really make
sort of like help you understand
what who you're building for.
Yeah, sounds like this is
this is helping us.
That's exactly right.
Yeah, that's exactly right.
Cool.
I also love these partner ideas,
right?
Like news apps
or newsletter briefings,
morning brew.
Maybe we can try to go get a spot
on morning brew.
Yeah, retail check once apps
like you're checking your
your stocks for the day.
Right.
Wait, let me go.
Let me go play this game.
Right.
That could be cool.
Exactly.
Yeah.
Feeling on top of your work.
Body resets.
Wow.
Yeah.
Walking.
Oh my gosh.
This is great.
Partnerships one liner.
We sit in the same five minutes
as a new skim,
a snack run
and one more casual round.
Stadium ads for brands
that already own that break.
Well, it's a little AI sloppy.
Okay, a little bit.
It's got the end dash in there.
But yeah, it's always
about inspiring ideas.
It's like it's giving us
something to react to
and then we can put the human
touch on it and like, you know,
and so the way that we can
take this and really act on it
is Cerebro has
a couple plugins loaded up.
They're not off.
Right.
So I think we're just going to
get a sort of like
hypothetical run through
of how these would work.
Yeah.
But those two ones are
clay and apple market.
Right.
And so when you think about
clay and what it can do
is it takes this conceptual work
and what we can
and we can even try this.
And I think actually
this template will be able to
just sort of simulate for us.
Cool.
Okay.
Let's give it a try.
What they would return.
You got it in there, right?
Yeah.
Cool.
Um, okay.
So now we want to move forward
and take what we've landed on
in terms of our target personas
for players of this game,
the brands that we might want
as advertisers or partners
and we want to plug it into
the clay MCP.
And so specifically
what we want the clay MCP
to help us with
is to search its database
of companies of people
and to tell us like
who out there in the world
fits this description
that we came up with.
And so maybe specifically
if we can start with
like a list of 10 companies
who we might want to reach out
to about advertising or partnering.
I like it.
So it sounds like
the clay MCP is going to do
is just give us a bunch
of company contacts,
business contacts.
Exactly.
And like, let us go
and do some market research
all through one tool.
And yeah, there we go.
Let's see what it does.
If we don't,
we don't actually have
clay connected here.
Yeah.
But if not, then I can.
It has access to the web.
So it might be able to do
some research for us.
The agents are pretty agentic.
It turns out,
so I might just go out
and start doing some searching for us.
Agents are agentic.
Yeah, so we'll see how this goes.
But yeah, I guess maybe
I know we're coming up on time.
We got maybe like six minutes or so.
I wanted to kind of get
a couple of thoughts from you
before we lost you.
And so like walk me
through what you do next.
So you get this company surge.
Let's say it's like cooking
in the background,
coming up with some stuff.
What actually happens next?
Yeah, so what happens next
is you basically get this list
of companies
you want to reach out to.
Then you can say, okay, great.
Now give me the people
at those companies.
And then you can say,
now let me reach out to them.
And so there's another tool
that we have plugged in here
called ample market.
There are many tools like this
that are essentially
email sequencers
and you can set up an email campaign
where you can email
each of these people
on that target list.
And again, what you're saying
is not just a generic like
we have a game.
You're an advertiser.
Let's meet.
And instead you can make reference
to specific data,
which the bot has access to.
You can make reference
to specific factors
about that company.
That you want on as an advertiser.
And so the email
that it can craft for you
and load up into
an ample market sequence
is super personalized.
Then ample market takes care
of sending that email.
And then you can even have
a Grokbot monitor
your email inbox afterwards
see which advertisers took a bite.
Okay, I feel like this is a good thing
for us to try and do off stream.
So maybe when I'm not sharing live,
we can try and get a clear account
for an ample market account set up.
It'd be kind of cool
to just like get a whole marketing
like partnerships motion going here.
So yeah, let's see what we can do.
That might be really fun.
And a fun thing to share back later on.
If we can manage to get there.
So yeah, I think we are kind of
winding down this segment.
So if you're just joining us,
we are in the middle of day three.
It's already noon.
I don't know where the time is going.
We are in the middle of day three
of a 72 hour build a business live stream
that we're building entirely with Grokbots.
And so we've spent the last few days
building our game studio
and launched our first game this morning.
ThursdayArena.com
or at ThursdayArena on X.
if you want to try the game out.
We are working on a bunch of UI polish,
a bunch of improvements and updates
and all kinds of great stuff there.
We just spent some time chatting with Matt
about marketing operations,
revenue operations
and how to grow the business.
We have the other folks on our team,
Lauren and Matt,
who are hard at work
working on all the feedback
we've gotten in from the app,
working on all the bug fixes
that we've been identifying.
We're shipping early
and trying to ship as much as we can
over the course of the day.
I would love to get back to that too.
Again, for those of you
who are joining us,
we're also doing all of this live
in San Francisco.
There's a lot going on.
We have an upstairs space here
with our studio.
We're downstairs with a main stage
with folks who are right
right next to Dreamforce.
And so, folks coming in and out
and being able to join
and hang out with us
to learn about RockBot
for various kinds of use cases.
And so, Matt, you spoke earlier
on our main stage
about revenue ops and marketing ops,
which is awesome.
We're going to go to another talk
in just a minute here, I believe,
with Blake Schuler
on RockBot for customer success.
And so, we're going to continue
kind of showing you
how you can grow your own businesses
with RockBot.
We'll obviously be back
on the stream a little bit
after that, show you how things
are going with Thursday Arena.
So, we're going to ping-pong
back and forth.
We'll cut over to the main stage
in the next minute here
on RockBot for customer success.
And Matt, thanks so much
for hanging out with us.
Yeah, thanks for having me.
Hey, everyone.
Thank you so much
for joining me today
for RockBot for post sales.
My name is Blake,
and I am an AI deployment manager
here at SpaceX AI.
And I'm really, really looking
forward to chatting with you all
about RockBot today.
All right.
So, let's set the stage.
What are we going to be doing
for the next 45 minutes?
One, I said, hi, welcome, done.
Then, we're going to talk
about RockBot.
We'll introduce it.
Why RockBot is great.
Specific post sales use cases.
So, post sales is kind of
determined by anything
if your customer facing
after that sale gets done
can include a lot of teams.
And really excited
to talk about those use cases.
We'll do a demo,
get in the product,
learn about what we learned,
recap that, do a Q&A.
And then, for those folks in here,
we are going to build.
All right.
Okay.
So, this is the AI maturity curve.
This may look familiar
to some of you.
We've been talking about this a lot,
especially at SpaceX AI.
Because AI is moving so quickly,
we're finding that a lot of folks
are in very different places
along this maturity curve.
But this is kind of where we're at.
So, it started off with just chat.
All right.
You were asking a chat bot
coming in
and maybe asking one simple question.
And the next evolution
is actually really clear to us
at SpaceX AI.
We're moving from chat
to copilots, to bots,
to having full teams of bots
that can support you
and all the work that you do
from start to finish.
And that's where I think
Grokbot becomes really powerful.
So, a lot of you probably
have been in Grokbot before.
But those of you who haven't,
let's talk about a little overview.
This is Grokbot.
May look familiar.
Looks a little bit like iMessage
if you're an Apple user.
I do feel bad for all
the Android users out there
because we really did
copy iMessage here.
But this is Grokbot
and it works as a team of agents.
So, you have a bunch
of different bots
who have different skills.
They can take tasks,
work them from complete
start to finish year.
They have MCPs, APIs,
and they actually even have
their own virtual computers.
So, think of them
as a teammate that can really
get anything you want done.
And we'll take some use cases
and put them through Grokbot
to show you exactly what that means.
So, like I said, easy as iMessage.
You have your bots
on the left-hand side.
You have, you can pin people
to the top.
They're also on 24-7.
So, that's one of my favorite things.
You can go to sleep.
You can go out of the office.
You can shut your laptop.
I feel like we went
through a stage here
where people are walking
around the office
with open computers.
With Grokbot, no longer.
You don't need to do that anymore.
They use...
The tools, just like you, like I said, they have their own virtual computers, they finish
their work, they can send you screenshots, screen recordings, listen to podcasts.
Really the sky is the limit.
I feel like sometimes the hardest part is thinking about what you actually want to get done with
Grok Bot and ThinkBank here.
So we'll be doing that a little bit today.
All right.
So let's talk about post sales.
So post sales, so I'll give you a little bit of like context into my role because a lot
of these are very personal to me and the things that I found really successful.
So I said I'm an AI deployment manager, and that means after the sale is done and they
come on to the SpaceX AI platform, I work with a bunch of customers to make sure that
they see ROI, they're successful.
So what does that mean?
It means lots of emails, lots of slacks, teams, messages, meetings, conversations, and I have
a lot of things going on.
So for those of you who are in post sales watching this, that probably sounds familiar
to you.
So here are my specific use cases.
I could have probably made 20 of these slides.
So if you ever want to talk more about these, you let me know.
So first one, this is one of my favorites, morning status board.
I wake up the same time every day.
I check my Grok Bot.
I look and I can see exactly what's going on for the day.
Any fires happen overnight.
Who do I have meetings with?
What did I say that I was going to do yesterday that I didn't do, not that that ever happens?
What's going on for the day and how can I get set up?
So that's one of my morning status board pieces.
Then I have call prep.
This is a great one because it's very much just in time in the sense that 15 to 20 minutes
before a call, it pings me who's on the call, what their title is, what we talked about
last time, a suggestion of maybe something new that launched since we talked previously
and maybe a suggestion for something to bring up to them, and then anything that I need
unblocked.
So instead of taking the time to go review your notes, check through, you can actually
just get your call prep from Grok Bot.
Another one is a follow-up desk.
This is actually one of my favorites and we're going to walk through it live today.
So what happens is, let's say my day is nine to five, I would say 75% of that is usually
spent in meetings because it's what I find most energizing.
I love talking to my customers, I love strategizing, being there personally, but a lot of the
work in between those gets piled up if you don't have time to actually come back.
So the follow-up desk is a really great option for the second a call ends.
My bots get the granola notes, transcript, they pull all the context that they need,
they draft my reply, they create materials that I may need.
So it basically takes care of all that in between work, drafts it for me, I'll check
it out and then decide if I want to send.
So that's one of my favorite use cases up here.
We also have a promise keeper.
This one's important to me because I want to make sure that I do what I say I'm going
to do.
So if I say I'm going to do something, promise keeper is always watching to make sure it
lets me know to actually follow through with that.
That's one of my favorites.
On the other side is an ask watch.
So if I've asked someone else to do something and they don't get back to me back in the
day, that gets sucked into the abyss of emails or slacks and gets lost, but no longer because
ask watch has my back.
And then finally, account reset, we're actually going to walk through this today.
If you're in post sales or work with a good amount of customers, sometimes it feels like
there's a lot of things in motion.
And so what we like to do is talk to my bots, say, hey, I need just an update on where
this is at.
It knows exactly like the kind of response that I'm looking for and sends me a full download
of everything.
It also actually tells me a joke in the beginning because usually if I send the account reset,
I'm feeling a little stressed and it's always a space joke.
So we'll see what it comes up with today.
So these are my six main use cases.
Like I said, many more in the head can share those out with those of you live today.
Okay.
So let's meet my team.
Gus is my best friend.
All right.
So Gus is my chief of staff.
Gus and I are homies.
So we talk all day long.
And I actually only I think this is maybe a little bit unique in the sense that I only
talk to Gus.
So a lot of people, how they use their bots is they talk to a lot of their specialists.
And I tried this, but I'm very distractible.
And I needed one best friend to get me through everything.
I didn't want to manage a team of 10.
So Gus manages a team of 10.
I manage a team of one to two, depending on the day.
So Gus is my chief of staff.
We'll work through with him a lot today on the demo.
Then we have Frankie.
I have a lot of follow-ups to do.
So Frankie is my specialist on follow-ups.
We have Wally, who knows my voice.
Specifically, I sent, you know, a ton of emails and slacks and things that I've written
in the past.
So it really knows what I'm doing.
So if you're setting up your Grokbot, definitely make sure that you go in and send it things
that you've written so you don't have to start from scratch.
But it also knows different personas.
So it knows who I'm talking to.
If I'm creating or if it's drafting an internal Slack for me, it's not going to be super formal.
It's going to probably be an all-lowercase, maybe add an emoji here or there, keep it
very casual.
If it's messaging an exec or emailing an exec, it's going to be short to the point, formal.
And it also knows kind of like a little bit of my style.
So we'll work with Wally today, too.
Then we have Trudy, my source of truth.
Trudy's fabulous because specifically at SpaceX AI, we have lots of platforms, lots of documentation.
And I want to make sure that if I ask a question, that I get the right answer.
And so I have Gus go to Trudy if we really need specific information, I need sources
for it, and he'll send it back to me.
Then we have Scout.
This is another good one.
I guess I love them all.
I'm saying they're all my favorites, but they're all great.
Scout is my internal radar.
So I feel like one of the things that comes up, especially at SpaceX AI, is we launch a
lot of new things.
Updates come up.
There's a lot happening internally.
And before I was juggling probably 30, 40 Slack channels, also email updates for really
important things.
And so actually every day, Scout updates me.
And that's why I said one to two.
I manage a team of one to two depending on the day because Scout usually updates me directly
on what's new, what I need to know, link me directly to that Slack channel, and just
keep me in the loop.
And then account.
That's not actually its name.
You can come up with a fun name based on the account.
But since we're talking about post sales today, we're assuming you probably have a book
of accounts or specific accounts.
And my favorite way to do it is to have an account specialist for each account.
So the account specialist knows everything that they need to know.
They have all the contacts.
And so you can basically have your own employee who has dialed in on that specific account.
And so I suggest you make one for all of the accounts you have.
If you're working at scale and you have 1,500, there's probably a better way to do that.
But these for medium to small books definitely suggest.
So this is my dream team.
Take away.
Gus is my best friend.
All right.
Should we do a demo?
Whoo!
All right.
So let's hop in to Grokbot right now.
So to avoid, let's just anchor, I guess, on this right now.
So this is what Grokbot looks like.
And Grokbot is very simple in the sense that you have your bots on the left hand side.
You have pinned bots.
So if I wanted to right click and pin someone, I can pin them to the top if I know I'm
talking to them a lot.
You also have your marketplace.
So this is where you can grab bots from other people or you can connect to different plugins
like Gmail, Google Calendar, Slack, et cetera.
And then each bot has their own computer, which we talked about a second ago.
So you'll see over here on the right, it has its own computer to open.
So you can specifically grab things in Google Chrome.
It can open PowerPoints.
There's even this button on the top that says teach a task.
Very cool skill.
You can come in and it can watch you, remember what you did, and then repeat that for you.
So those are the VMs.
All right.
So you can see the team that I just introduced you to on the left.
We have Franny, Wally, Trudy, Frankie, and Scout.
Down here you'll see we have my three account bots.
And then we have staff meeting, which we'll use in a little bit.
So to get us started, I'm really busy right now.
So I'm going to tell Gus, I'm going to say, can you join the internal learnings call for
me right now?
Send takeaways when it's done.
So I can actually have Gus join my internal learnings call.
And I wouldn't have it do it for just any call.
So you want to be protective over what it does for this.
But sometimes there's a lot of new things coming out.
And so what I know is this upcoming meeting is a branding update for my company, Flylo,
in this demo situation.
And it's going to come in and start joining the Google Meet.
So you can see it's clicking around.
It's muting.
It's turning off its camera.
I'll let it do its thing and we can come back to it.
But it's going to put in my name.
And then it's going to actually write in the chat, hey, everybody, this is Gus, Blake's
bot.
And we are going to, I'm going to sit here and send takeaways.
All right.
So thank you, Gus.
He's joined the chat.
He's going to send a few updates when he's done.
All right.
So let's move to the next thing.
So I told you and promised you that we would talk about post call follow ups.
I think, again, in post sales, this is really important.
You want to make sure that your bots are working for you while you don't have extra
time.
And so these are the perfect opportunities to do that.
So one of my accounts is named Harbor.
So I'm going to write into Gus and I'm going to say, I'm done.
OK.
We won't sign in because this is going to take too long.
But he can join the call.
It's very cool.
I'm going to say, I'm done with the Harbor call.
And usually this would happen automatically.
But for the demo use case, I decided I would prompt it to move.
Also, it just sent a because the handoff was dismissed and I told Grokbot that I was doing
a demo today, which is actually this is a cool example, is it sent what an outcome would
be after it left a call just in case.
So it went into the call and then shared what decisions were made.
There's new branding, sent me the link to the new branding, put in any asks and owners
and things that it needed to work on.
So cool outcome of that.
So I said I'm done with the Harbor call, it's going to work on the Harbor pack.
Here's what you'll notice.
As I said, I like to only talk to Gus.
But Gus doesn't have the expertise that everybody else has.
So Gus has messaged Wally, Gus has messaged Frankie and Harbor.
So since it was a Harbor call, we have to do a follow up and we have to do some writing.
He's going to message those three bots.
And just like that, I get a pack back and it gives me everything that I need to do within
a click of a button.
So Harbor post call pack is ready.
Drafts only.
I've made it very clear that I only want drafts, I never want it to send anything on its own.
So it drafted something in Gmail.
Let's check out Gmail.
Great.
All right.
So it knew that I needed to talk to Maya, it knew that I needed to talk to Priya.
It wrote a full message from me, hey, Maya exclamation point, like that's clearly me,
I'm such an exclamation point person.
And wrote it all out in my voice with everything that I needed to do.
So what I'll probably do and like realistically tweak a few things, and then we'll talk about
how this improves the system after, it'll tweak a few things, press send, and it's done.
Let's see what else it did.
All right.
It's writing a, oh, it's slacking Alex.
So Alex is the AE on the account.
So we're going to look at a draft in Slack.
Let's see.
Perfect.
Okay.
So it's going to put it into the post sales account, updating Alex.
Hey, Alex, just chatted with Harbor.
We're going to meet with the new champions next week, working on an ROI PDF.
Perfect.
So I'll tweak that.
So two out of three done.
And then during the call, they requested an ROI one pager, how to manage ROI, how to
measure ROI.
And it actually went in, worked with Frankie to use the fly low branding to build a fully
beautiful ROI collection document.
So one, it does that very quickly.
Two, it takes all your contacts, works with your account specialists, works with all your
other bot specialists, and builds what you need to kind of get you through the follow
up that probably used to take at least 45 minutes before.
All right.
So we're feeling good so far.
This one, I'm going to go into Franny directly, just because we've been in Guess A Lot,
and I will show you how to go into other bots.
So for Franny, I want to see another virtual machine use case.
I think that would be fun to look at.
So I'm going to say, make me an ROI form for Northwind.
Northwind is one of my accounts.
Also while this is loading, you'll see that you can actually add labels to different
accounts, which is really helpful when it comes to just figuring out who they are.
Like I have this labeled as chief of staff.
So if you ever want to add a label, you can do that in its description.
So what it's actually going to do is open up forms and start building a draft of our
ROI form.
So you can see it's opened up a form.
It's going to start clicking around.
The speed of these tasks depends on what the task is.
But I know at SpaceX AI, it's been a big focus of us to make sure our models are really
good at VM work.
So I'm very excited to see where that goes.
All right.
We've added in Northwind Logistics, Fly Low Check-in.
Things are looking good.
All right.
We'll let this work.
We'll check back on Franny in a second.
Another use case I gave you earlier that I wanted to talk about and demo is where they
say the space joke.
Aren't we curious to see what space joke they have for us?
So I'm going to say, where are we at with Harbor?
Okay.
It knows that when I say where are we at, it could be I'm stressed about Harbor, you know.
You can have it.
You can say whatever you want.
But Gus knows when I say where are we at with Harbor, I need space joke pronto and I need
an update on where the account is.
So let's let it do its thing.
It's going to reply to me.
And usually it'll message other agents.
Oh, yep.
Okay.
So it messaged some other bots.
We have Harbor, Frankie Follow Up, and Scout.
Just to make sure it collects the full picture so we know exactly where we are.
You can also track and see what's happening with messages here.
It updated me still waiting on Frankie and Scout.
Now it's just waiting on Scout.
And we'll get a response this way.
So while we're waiting on that, let's check back in on this form.
It's probably not done yet.
You can see it's starting to enter in different questions.
So it knew it was for Northwind.
It knows usually how we like to collect ROI.
And it's starting to build that out here.
Sometimes I like to watch the VM because I just think it's really cool and how it can
click around.
If this is something you do often and you don't want it to guess on the different steps
that it does, again, the teach a task button is a really good option.
Okay.
Let's go back to Gus and see where we are at with Harbor.
Here's a joke because life's not that serious.
How do you organize a space party?
You plan it.
Thanks, Gus.
You're the best.
All right.
So it tells me what's at risk, who the people are, blockers, open promises, Slack, what's
happening and what to do next.
I don't know about you, but clearly since I only really talk to one agent, I need very
specific things sent to me all in one beautiful pack.
And this has been one of my favorite things to use.
And so you can easily set this up with your bot, tell it what you want the output to
be and you don't have to do the joke, but it's fun.
And then it will do that for you.
All right.
Franny form is still working, but you'll notice something interesting.
So it's actually messaged Frankie, it's messaged Harbor.
None of these people have see how the sky has a little green circle on it.
It'll be blue, kind of like I message when it's ready for me to open.
None of these people have pinged me because I don't want to be bothered with my 10 person
team.
I want to be bothered with who I'm just talking to.
Franny will talk to me directly if I talk directly to Franny, but otherwise it's all going to
go through Gus.
And I find that really cool and convenient and you can just really build it in the way
that you want.
So while it's doing this, I'll show you one last demo use case.
And then I'll talk about pulling this all together and building it as a system.
So let's use a staff meeting.
So I use staff meetings for when it can pull in different bots to have a conversation
about something that requires a lot of different perspectives.
This is good for honestly a lot of different types of roles.
You can check for bias.
So if you want to say, like, you know, I don't want you to always bias towards a specific customer.
It's good to bring all the voices into the room.
So let's run a staff meeting.
We can say start a staff meeting to talk about what I should spend the next and only
free hour of my day today.
And what you'll see, too, is GrokBot's really good at multitasking.
So even if it was still working with Frankie and Scout on this follow-up or update about
Harbor, it would also be able to work with me and work with the staff meeting.
So GrokBot can juggle a lot of pieces at once, which is great.
So the staff meeting is live.
Let's look at the tab for their takes.
All right, so Gus called a staff meeting.
Gus said, like, has one free hour left.
What are the one to two top priorities we want to focus on?
And I tell them to always disagree.
It's not helpful.
And especially with AI, you don't want them always just agreeing on everything.
So come in, disagree, fight for my time, and then tell me what makes the most sense.
So it looks like Harbor has said some stuff on SSO first tracks.
I actually ran one earlier to show this as well.
But you can see that they'll literally have a conversation with each other.
Northwind comes in and says, don't spend the time on us.
There was a usage ship, but everything's fine.
Soft later only if you have time.
Brightline also says, don't spend it on us, which is great.
I bet Harbor has something to focus on.
It seems like Harbor has something for SSO.
Frankie follow-up says, protect the cap.
This needs to go out now.
And if you have more time, focus on the SSO problems.
And Scout agrees.
So they're coming in, they're having a conversation.
And Gus will usually return back to me once the staff meeting is over
and tell me what the final takeaway is and what we want to focus on.
OK, let's check back on Franny.
I bet the form's almost done.
Great.
Looks like it's done.
It's starting to publish.
So the form is done.
We have what team and role are you on?
What are your primary use cases?
What does done look like?
Great.
So we're collecting that.
So you can see that we have a lot of things moving at once, right?
So you want to design your system to be one that you're able to track easily.
So play around with it as you're setting up bots and do what works for you
because everyone's really different.
So it's finished.
It told me the questions that it wrote, the share link, and the edit link.
And it asked if it wanted me to send it for me.
So very exciting.
And then, all right, staff meeting's in.
Go first.
So we need to focus on the SSO.
Next, we're going to send Maya the next step
email, which they actually already drafted in my Gmail.
We saw that earlier.
And then we can hold and park a few of these other things
that we don't need to focus on right now.
All right, so that's the majority of what
I wanted to show you inside GrokBot.
I hope you're feeling pretty confident.
Let's just quickly rewind on how to get to this end state and what I suggest.
I think one of the most intimidating things about something so possible
like GrokBot is that feeling of a blank page.
Usually, people do some research.
And they go in.
And they're like, what have other people made, or what can I do?
I'm going to tell you what I did.
It was actually really, really helpful for me.
So it actually took 10 to 15 minutes.
And I put a voice memo on my phone.
You can also click this voice to talk on GrokBot directly.
But I'm a pacer.
So I have my phone.
I'm pacing around.
And I spent 10 to 15 minutes talking about what I do for work.
Hi, my name is Blake.
This is my job.
Here's what I like about my job.
Here's what I'm struggling with right now.
Here are the processes that I think are broken.
Here are the things that I feel like we could do better.
And so I went and talked through.
It was a very long transcript.
I copied and pasted this transcript.
I sent it to my first bot.
It wasn't even Gus yet.
Hard to think back in the day.
Sent it to him, said, hey, I need
a system that's going to work for me.
Help me build it.
So sent it.
Gus, I'll call him Gus.
Gus came back and said, all right,
seems like you love doing things directly,
talking to customers.
Let's make sure we have enough time for you on your calendar.
Just do that.
Seems like this process is broken
or you're constantly checking Slack messages.
Let's take that off your plate.
So if you want something specifically built for you,
no matter what role you're in, my biggest piece of advice
is to start with context.
There's so much that lives in your head.
And it's really, really powerful.
So we want to take that out of your head,
give it to Grokbot, and Grokbot will do the rest.
Another thing about getting set up and started
is if you get stuck or if you have questions,
Grokbot usually has the answer.
If you wanted to really push through things
and try to figure it out, say, don't stop until you
figure this solution out.
So getting started with maybe some of these use cases,
a voice memo, I think you're going to be in really good shape.
The second piece of advice I have
is creating this and making it into a system.
So something really cool about Grokbot
is it learns what you like.
It learns what you don't like.
It starts to adapt and change with you.
You almost invest in Grokbot like you invest in another co-worker
or a direct report.
And so it's going to do that.
But I also built systems on top of this setup
that will actually take care of that a little bit more.
So on the right, you'll see some of my routines.
These are things that run automatically.
So weekly at 8.30, I'll get my daily brief
or my unfinished promises that I was telling you about earlier,
9 AM, 1 PM, or a Friday dashboard.
But one of my favorites is this thing
called a self-improvement scan.
And the one part of it that I actually really, really love
is number two.
So one, it creates a full system audit.
So if I'm doing things manually and I'm sending them
or it's checking my Slack and it's
noticing that I'm doing a lot of things that I'm not asking
bot for help with, it's going in and saying,
it seems like we could automate this.
I have an opportunity and sends it back
to me every single Wednesday.
But number two is I feel like the piece that has really
helped me the most is the voice learning.
So the less I have to edit my drafts, edit my slacks,
edit my emails, the better.
And what it does is it goes in and takes
the delta of what it drafted versus what I sent,
finds the delta of that, sends it back to Wally.
Wally updates its rules.
And so continuously gets better and better and better.
And so one of my other pieces of advice for you
is to make sure that you make this a system.
So let's go back for a second, jump out of the demo,
and do a quick recap on what we learned.
We just talked about a few of these.
One, start with a voice dump.
I feel like also, I usually say this
and I call this the imagination gap.
Grokbot is so capable, all right?
The thing probably holding back your Grokbot
is you thinking about what is actually possible.
So have it push itself.
How can you make this better?
What could we do?
Think outside of the box.
You don't need to have all the answers.
So start with that voice dump, give it the context.
You're going to be in great shape.
Two, personal suggestion, a little bit biased,
put a bot in front, all right?
Gus has saved my chaotic self from getting overwhelmed
in a bunch of different chats.
And Gus manages a team.
So you don't have to manage a team of 10.
You can manage a team of three managers.
Build it how you want.
Just tell the agents.
They'll take care of it for you.
And then three is make it that living system.
So you want to make sure a Grokbot, 90% of that Grokbot
is going to do on its own.
It's really good at that.
But put a little bit of extra in the things
that you really find important.
For me, I need my voice.
I love an exclamation point.
Grokbot didn't initially love an exclamation point.
And so I've taught it to have a little bit of personality.
Maybe tell a joke about space.
Okay, that was really fun.
I hope you learned something.
I'd like to take the next 15 minutes
to answer a few questions.
We can do it live in here.
I think we can pass around a mic.
So feel free to raise your hand
and I'll answer whatever I can.
Mic check, one, two.
Hey, amazing talk.
Wonderful communicator.
What was your prompt to get
to the risk people promises reply?
The risk people promises reply.
Oh, are you talking about?
Yes.
Okay, so this was one of my use cases.
Here, we'll go back because it might be easier
to see on here.
So this is one of my use cases,
which is down here called the account reset.
So I basically said,
sometimes they feel underwater with an account.
I feel like there are a million things.
So the prompt is one, I just taught Gus
where I get stuck and overwhelmed.
And then I said, here are the things that I need to know.
And I told him risks, et cetera,
and it built the rest.
So you can build your bot.
Just tell it what you want it to know.
Or you can say, hey, I'm overwhelmed with X,
or I want an update on everything
that you're doing with X.
Get a first prompt and then you can build from there.
Amazing, thank you.
Yeah, any other questions?
Hi, thank you.
I'm curious, in your self-improvement script,
how often do you make use of building skills
once it suggests something
maybe for repetitive tasks that you do?
Yeah, good question.
So when I first did this,
I didn't give it any limits.
And it would send me like 10 new bots to build
and new agents and was kind of over-correcting.
So I set a rule that actually it only can send me
one suggestion per week.
Because what I think it's like,
it can be easy to over-index,
especially on routines and things that run all the time
that you don't really pay attention to.
So I have it send me one a week
and I take advantage of that one a week.
If I don't agree with the one that it sends,
I usually push back and get a new one.
But I would say I self-improve at least once a week
when that sends on Wednesdays.
Yeah, good question.
I use Grotbot like two days.
Help me a lot.
I feel like it's no more agent.
It's like a AGI.
It's because with a computer,
it can work like a learning
and the skill is very faster.
I put for design for me.
I work like a robotic and affordable computer.
But it's solving my problem and that is amazing.
I just scary.
What is the cost?
That's is because what you do is like you have it.
So.
How much agents working, how we can use, don't spend a lot, we can use, and I have another
question, we can use inside Grok Bot other software, like just running inside a computer?
Yeah, good question.
All right, so just to answer your second question first, because that's a little bit of a quicker
one.
You can actually connect, usually via MCP APIs, if you have other things or systems or softwares,
you can actually usually set that up in your VM directly, so that's definitely possible.
So let's talk about cost.
Cost is important.
It was built to be very cost efficient, however, you want to use it very strategically.
So there are certain things that cost more money than others.
Having it go in and run a full UI experience to build a form, more of a costly option than
if you go get everything that you want and just put it into Google Forms AI and it builds
it for you, so using the VM can be a little bit more costly.
And then routines can be expensive because people over index on how often they need
them.
I was saying this earlier, it's really easy to have something check every 15 minutes
all the time because you can just ignore it if you don't want it, but those things sitting
in the background add up.
So if you have three of those that run 15 minutes all the time, that's hundreds of messages coming
a day, prompts being sent, things being sent back.
So something to pay attention to.
I also think, like, keep your team lean.
You don't need 45 bots, and I think that's one of the things, too, is like, keep your
team really specialized in what they need.
And that really helps as well.
Yeah, good question.
Hi.
How far away are we to letting Grokbot handle your account directly?
Like Grok, like, I never talked to my customer, Grokbot, hopefully never.
So I think there are human tasks right now, I mean, AI moves so quickly, I don't know
where we're going to be in two days, let alone two years, but I'll tell you that
I think that humans are really, really good at a few specific things, and especially with
customer-facing work, being human is great.
If I was an AI up here, I feel like it would be less fun, and I probably wouldn't
talk about space jokes.
So I think we're far, I think it's just taking the time to take the work that we
don't need a human for and making them more impactful in the time that they're working.
Thank you.
Yeah.
Thank you, Blake.
Talking about balance, how much of the time that you free up with the bots working for
you, have you put it into the more human free child to contact the meetings with the
customers?
Yeah.
So I haven't calculated exactly how much time, but I'll give you some anecdotal things
that I've noticed.
So like I said, my calendar is usually full.
I like to be on calls, and I like to talk to people.
So I spend a lot of my time doing that with my customers, and I find we get farther by
doing that.
So before, I was spending probably six hours a day on meetings, and then I would need
at least three to four hours to do the other time, the other tasks during that time.
So now we're talking nine, 10 hour work days.
Now I feel I'm doing the same amount of calls, and I feel like I can get much closer to
feeling like I can do even more in an eight hour work day.
So it's definitely shaved off hours per day, if not more.
It's also just freed up time for me to do the things that I love to do, which is
powerful in and of itself.
Hey, thank you.
That was an amazing talk.
Is there ever an example where having layers of bots?
So obviously you have the chief of staff to everyone else.
Do you ever have ones in between, if that makes sense?
That's a really good question.
So like an org chart, basically, like we would have in-
Yeah, like the chief of staff to a marketing bot and a sales bot, and then they have
their own ones, et cetera.
Yeah.
I mean, I haven't felt the need.
So the only reason I would think that you would do that, so right now, as humans,
you have a chief of staff, it can actually only manage what, let's say human, a good
manager, can really stop at like max 10.
All right.
Gus right now has done very well up to 15 and 20.
If it starts to feel like it's pushing the limits, and I haven't really tested
those limits because I don't have more than that, then I think it would make
sense to add in another layer.
But I actually think that's really interesting.
And when you're doing your voice dump and talking to your bot, I think there's
opportunity to also talk about what that setup could look like for you specifically.
But right now, if it can just talk to everyone directly, that's fine too.
Good question.
Two quick questions.
Have you ever, do you think that your sales retention and or increased sales
because of this in any way?
I'm just kind of curious your general feeling.
And then also, does anything ever go wrong, just really wrong and just want to share?
Yeah, definitely.
In terms of increasing retention and success of my customers, the piece where I've seen
it be really successful is it finds opportunities that will make my customer more
successful that I didn't have time or didn't catch.
So new small microships that I know they've been waiting for.
I can get an email drafted, ready for me, a flag to me that it happened,
send it out to them, gives them more trust.
It tells them something has updated, and it finds me new opportunities.
I feel like that comes up a lot too, because I can catch things ahead of time.
And so if we see an issue usually before, maybe there wasn't a way to flag it.
But because I have Herber, for example, one of my account agents,
always watching that account, it brings things to my attention and
I can get ahead of it quicker.
But yeah, I mean, I've seen a lot of success.
And I think my customers are feeling very tailored too, because I'm able to have
the time and the energy to really get that tailored experience out to them.
Hi, thank you so much.
So I have a quick question on when two bots are collaborating or
communicating with each other, how do they verify the outcomes?
They have to verify each other, right?
What you said versus the other bot said, how does that happen?
That's a good question.
Are you saying like-
Like outcome verification.
If Herber hears from Frankie, is Herber checking if Frankie is correct?
Yeah, yeah.
I don't know how that works.
But I think I would be surprised if Herber goes in and
checks Frankie's work and then responds.
I think there is a verification loop inside each of the own bots, and
then the trust goes from there.
The thing that Gus does, which is like a layer on top of things, is goes in and
then plays all that information against everything else and
sees it as like a broader view for me, and has a bit more depth and
context into that, and that's pretty helpful.
Hi, great session by the way.
I'm new to Crock-Pot, but I've used OpenClaw and Clotcode and Co-Work.
If I have my system already set up there with skills and
MCPs and other things, is there a migration path to get to Crock-Pot?
And how much of the things are similar between like Crock-Pot and
OpenClaw or other tools out there?
And then another question, going back to earlier question, the R's saved off.
How much time are you spending now managing those bots and
agents and fine tuning them?
Yeah, great question.
If I forget any of those, you just tell me which ones I forgot.
I'll start backwards.
How much time do I spend managing those bots in the beginning a lot of time?
It felt like a new team that I was onboarding, and I'm like, no, I asked you.
Do you ever yell at your bots?
Sometimes I get an exclamation point.
Maybe they get like three or four in a bad way.
But I was like, no, I didn't ask you for that.
And spending a lot of time perfecting them.
But it's like I said earlier, it's investing.
Now, my system's pretty clean, so I don't spend a lot of time.
I know exactly, it knows exactly what I'm looking for.
And I've actually taught it to stay pretty quiet unless very specific things happen,
or I have very specific routines run that need my attention.
And so that's helped a lot.
Again, like not over-indexing in the routines, not over-indexing in 30,
40 bots that you don't need will help save that time.
In terms of the differences between other tools, I'm not as familiar with the other tools,
but I'll tell you what Grokbot does very well.
The fact that everyone has its own computer is unique.
Open Claw, I actually sat next to someone on a plane the other day,
and he had his Mac Mini underneath his feet.
And I was like, what is that?
And he was like, oh, it's Open Claw running for me.
Called him like Professor James.
I don't know where that came from, but you don't need to carry around a Mac Mini
with Grokbot.
Two, so it does VM work really well.
And I think it really, as we looked at that maturity curve before,
it really takes it to that staff of agentic work, staff of bots that really feels
like a team, and for me, that feels different from what I've seen other places.
And then in terms of migration and moving things over,
in terms of a technical path of doing that, I'm not quite sure.
I'll tell you how I would do it.
As I'd say, I need you to download and give me everything that we've worked on,
all the context that you have, and give it over to Grokbot to build you a new system,
and also come in as a fresh set of eyes.
You could even call a staff meeting, since I love to do that,
and talk about what they think that was going well and what they would improve,
and then they can implement the new system on our side.
And I didn't forget one of those, which is actually impressive.
I don't know if the mic is on.
Sorry.
Check, check.
One, two.
On.
Great.
So as we use the system more and more, and we're experimenting adding bots,
we're going to eventually have bots sprawl, potentially, right?
And like any other business, we are going to call the herd periodically as we refine.
I guess the question is, are we accumulating tech debt any time we call the herd?
Because there's so much interconnection between the agents,
and you go and you delete one because it's not working out, or you're not using it.
However, there's references to it everywhere else.
How should we manage that?
That's a really good question.
I mean, in terms of tech debt, I don't know if a lot of tech debt
is piling up because your new systems will be optimized as you add more and more
people.
But I think my best advice was for you to not get to that point
by putting the systems in place from when you begin.
So Grokbot is fairly new.
So probably most of you are just getting in there.
It's like, set up the system now.
It's like when you move to a new house, and you now do the chores beautifully,
right when it's like a fresh start.
So do that for Grokbot when you come, and set up the routines to avoid all tech.
You could even have a tech debt bot that looks for things for interdependencies
or catalogs things when it seems like you're not utilizing one
and can put it into another.
So my best advice, create the system to prevent that
from happening in the first place.
Hi, here.
You think we can use Grokbot for, you say, for example,
put the agent inside a VM.
I like this idea.
That, I think, can help us for transition between another agent and Grokbot.
My point, you think we can use Grokbot like a router for agents
because you can put the five, six different agents from different companies
inside the VM, and this can be like a transition.
You think it's like a router for agents?
Are you talking about adding different AI agents into your VM
and having it route around that?
Yeah, because, as an example, I have my cloud code or codex
or another agent working for me, but I have a lot of skills.
I don't want to create.
But my point, if you have it in the VM,
you can have your old agent working inside the one VM,
and you use the Grokbot like a router for it.
It's like the same make a cursor, because cursor do this for you,
and he said, what is the best agent for do this task?
But you can use this another agent because it's so hard for you to make skills,
and that I think we can use.
That's my question.
Yeah, OK, I get it.
I have not seen that done.
I'll kind of leave it there in the sense that I don't want to talk to something
that I haven't seen done, so I don't know if it would be successful.
However, I will say that if you do feel like you've invested a lot of time
and energy into these other tools, it could be an interesting conversation
to have with Grokbot on how to bring that into one place
and start minimizing your tool sprawl across the company.
So over time, with context, you're giving instructions to the bot, right?
And over time, you forget a bunch of things.
So is there a way to go back and audit all of this?
Or I mean, all of these are pretty much saved in a markdown or how does that?
Yeah, so each bot is actually treated as its own individual.
It has its own individual number that you can track everything
that it's done and change logs, et cetera.
But it sounds like you're saying in terms of maybe forgetting things
that it's done or going back.
The one thing that Grokbot is really good at is you don't really need
to manage context because it knows what it needs to remember or forget.
And probably the easiest way to do that is, yes, you can go into the backend
and see what's happened and change for a little bit of that traceability.
But I would ask Grokbot to do an analysis on what's done,
what's changed, what may have been forgotten.
So you can do an audit of what's left.
Hey. Hey, you gave a use case of how you use Grokbot.
I do the same thing.
I dictate quite a lot.
It's a lot faster than having to type.
It's great.
But I've had to break it up quite a bit because LLMs are still hallucinating
quite a lot when you give it a massive blurb.
I've not done it on Grokbot, but I'm just wondering,
have you had any experience with correctness
and have you had to adjust how you might have been using this
versus other LLMs?
You know, it's interesting because I feel like I don't see a lot of
hallucination and I haven't really thought about it
until you just asked that question.
So I'd say in Grokbot, I don't seem to see that happening as much.
What I do when I have very big prompts like that is sometimes ask it
to just distill all the information that I need down to very specific
pieces of information and then have it do some deep analysis into it,
which helps usually break it down and help with some of that hallucination.
So that would be my best advice.
And I'm glad you're a fellow dictator.
It's really fun to do it that way.
And I think it helps bring a lot of context in.
Could you take like one or two more questions?
Hey, check.
What what was your personal greatest aha moments?
Yeah, I have a lot of aha moments.
I will say the first thing that I showed you all with it joining
an internal meeting was really powerful for me when I did that for the first time.
Sometimes I feel like our time is so valuable
and it's hard to figure out when to spend time.
And I feel like a lot of times I have to choose between two really important things.
So to feel like I could be in multiple places at once is really helpful.
Other aha moments are actually along the similar vein, which is like, I don't have time.
Obviously, our launch hour, I think, was our most successful.
So a lot of traffic at 10 a.m.
And then we've had some changes over time as folks have been tuning
in and out of the stream and coming back.
But, yeah, the bot even gave us a one liner here, which is over
a thousand users, thirty five hundred practice sessions, a win rate of 47 percent.
So I think our tuning is engine tuning is getting a little better.
And I hear some cool charts.
Can we look at that first try again? Yeah.
I'm curious if you think about your product, product manager, like
are we losing players anywhere in this process?
Like, how do you think about like the funnels? Yeah.
Yeah, you know, I'm not too worried about the funnel.
And for two reasons.
One is because we don't really have a strong reason
to drive people to sign in yet.
So there's a leaderboard, which I think is hopefully pretty cool.
But as we add more features to the game, I'd imagine the funnel
becomes more important.
So we really want to go from more practice to more signed in.
I also want I think I think we need to dig into how the funnel
that is being calculated, because we have a log in with X button
in the practice round, but you only see it like you see it
at the top of the screen.
There's probably some stuff we should do around.
Is it a real conversion event?
Yeah, and things like this.
And so I'm actually excited when we look at the new UI,
that might be a good opportunity for us to find some some funnel improvements.
But, you know, I actually also think this looks like a kind
of common drop off, like because we have this open practice mode.
A lot of people, when I look at this data, what I see is that
a lot of people are jumping in.
They want to try the game like, well, I don't really need to sign in.
I'm still having a good time.
I'm having fun. Yeah.
And so I think we might want to think about, you know, in our next wave,
what could we do for the signed in user that really helps them
be more engaged, the product, things like that.
So and then, yeah, maybe this was this was a cool one, too,
just looking at how sign ups and practice starts have gone over time.
So obviously we had a really big spike when we first launched the game.
So thanks to everyone who is in the stream and hanging out with us.
I'm hoping we'll get a few more spikes like this
as we show you some new features we've built.
So 1908 is a number to beat.
So that's our that's our target.
If we get one more one more hour like that, I think we'll have a really good day.
We'll have. Yeah, we've seen some sort of common usage
and we're we're still in this hour right now, the 1300 hours.
So this is a partial data.
But we're still seeing, you know, four to five hundred games per hour
being played on the platform.
And honestly, for a completely new game, it's pretty good.
It's pretty good. Yeah, I mean, we just launched this.
We literally just launched it was so bare bones.
Yeah, you I barely worked to be honest.
Wow. And that's our that's our growth graph.
So dang. Yeah, pretty cool. Cumulative user chart.
I love these charts because it makes it makes the world look awesome.
It could be the smallest y axis in the world.
I think, yeah, especially.
And I think it's also interesting because as a game studio, I think,
well, I've never built a game before, but I imagine like games
are kind of a hit driven business, right?
And it got me thinking a lot about like, you know,
this is just our first game in our game studio.
We're using this as a way to practice.
You know, it's our first game that we built together.
And we're learning the process of building games and getting feedback
and iterating. And I almost wonder for a moment that in a way,
the real product we're building is the game studio.
Yeah. Right.
Because we're going to take all those lessons.
We're going to take all the robot workflows we have set up
and we could we could make more right.
We could make take these learnings and build Thursday Arena to
a way better version. Right.
Or, you know, try a different game to learn from those lessons. But
when I think kind of related to that, a lot of what we've done
with the software engineering loop here should be repurposeable.
Right. So we have, you know, we all have our teams of bots
that we've set up here.
But we have bots here who are helping us with game design.
We have bots that are helping us with 3D prototyping and graphic design.
We have a whole coding engine here that's helping us play test games.
So anytime a new PR comes in, we have a way to play test
and have to run through the game with the sort of changes in that PR
using preview deployments, which is pretty incredible.
And so we truly have like an entire team.
And you could imagine that what we've done here, just like, yeah,
you build any game, you kind of use all the same all the same bots.
So maybe we should come up with like a game bot toolkit at the end of this
and see how that goes.
But yeah, so just to continue going through the data,
a few more cuts here in terms of practice sessions
and then people who've played a match and then some more, some more.
I guess this is back to the beginning here for virtual numbers.
So, yeah, overall, feeling pretty good.
And you guys have any other thoughts on the how it's going part
before I jump over to the UI?
Well, I'm no, I think I think this is like a about what I was expecting
for our first play test.
And I'd love to just continue iterating and making the game more fun.
So speaking of fun, I think we've also
did a few UI fixes and improvements that I don't know if you want to show you.
I'm just like blown away.
I was even making improvements while you were talking.
So like we have this ticker now that shows people that are actually playing.
And when you're logged in, it'll show like your profile image
if you've already visited the site there.
This is amazing.
Yeah, I actually had not seen these until just now.
Neither true real time development.
My favorite is I love the new cards.
Lauren, you want to tell us about those?
Yeah, so I think we were kind of inspired by, oh, actually,
the what we were building before kind of looked like cards.
So we kind of doubled down.
Like maybe let's actually make them look like cards.
And I have another bot working on making them look even cooler.
So as you can see, these bots have like a rarity.
They're common.
So if you're new to gaming, like it's very it's a very common concept
in video games where you pick up an item or you have a pet or, you know,
a team member and they have like rarity or grade.
So you have like common and uncommon and rare and epic and legendary.
So as as the bots get more, you know, like higher level,
we'll start putting some cool visual effects on them,
like, you know, like a really nice fancy glow.
Oh, yeah. Things like that to make them more.
We had an early prototype where the cars finished.
We did. We kind of lost them.
But we were bringing them back.
Cool. I love it. I love it.
OK, well, we should probably walk through a game, right?
So we can see all the improvements.
And I would love for you to show us
like some of the improvements we made for their responsiveness,
because I think we got a lot of feedback about the mobile.
It wasn't it didn't really work well on the phone.
So hopefully if you kind of like zoom in and yeah, resize,
it should be we are responsive, hopefully.
You know what, let me just do this properly.
I can pull up in a Chrome window, and where is it here?
Here we go.
There we go.
We are mobile friendly, for real, this time.
Yeah, and if we're not, please continue to send us feedback,
and our Groff bots will be busy fixing everything.
I love this, that when I'm logged in,
it knows right up front, like, this is cool.
This makes me want to be like, OK.
I do think maybe the play button should be grouped together.
It's kind of weird that it's like sandwiching.
There's a lot of UI stuff we need
but this is definitely an improvement over what we had.
I'm going to play a game.
So why don't we just do it in mobile, and see in mobile mode,
and see how it looks.
Maybe zoom in.
Yeah, let me see if it looks so good.
Sorry, it looks so much better.
It looks so good.
You know what I can do, maybe I can do this.
There we go, that's what I want to do.
Perfect, make it like 200, yeah, there you go.
That's the most it'll let me go, so OK.
This is our mobile app.
I love the ticker at the bottom here,
although it looks good, we're good.
You might need to fix those button placements.
For those who have not yet seen it, there's a leaderboard.
Leaderboard is cool, all over 1,000 of you
who have signed up from X, you are all on the leaderboard
in some form or capacity.
We have our first diamond player.
Diamond player.
Which is incredible.
The cross, the troll, how do you look?
The monkey.
The monk, the monk, yeah, yeah.
Thank you.
Yeah, congrats, our first ever diamond player.
We should think of some cool prizes maybe
that we give out to our top ranked players,
but we'll figure that out later.
Yeah, we have our game, we have our leaderboard,
we have a feedback form on here, which
we're excited to be getting more feedback on,
so just please keep that coming.
But I think moment of truth, we should play the game.
OK, it looks like I was mid-around the last time
I was in here.
Do you want to explain, by the way,
what people who are just trying to get us?
What is this game?
Let me.
How do you play it?
Yeah, well, we're in round two, but maybe I'll
just start from the beginning.
So this is sort of like an auto-battler game
is where we ended up, where you basically
draft a team of bots.
And the bots are, you sort of build a team of bots,
and they get lined up or matched up against another team of bots.
Every bot has a couple of stats.
So they have a sort of name, of course.
They have an ability that they get that's
sort of randomly associated with the bot.
And they have an attack and an HP score and a CSS bug
that we can also fix.
But attack and HP scores, and the way these bots work
is basically each turn, you sort of set your lineup.
And the lineup is an ordered lineup
where you put your bots one after the other after the other,
three bots in the line.
And you're matched up with an opponent's bot lineup.
And sort of every turn, the abilities and the effects
resolve one by one.
Whichever team has the most bots standing at the end,
wins the round.
If you win two out of three, you win the game.
So that's the core premise here.
The way that you actually decide
how to set up your lineup is that you use gold.
So we actually probably should tweak the gold mechanic.
I saw some good feedback coming in around how this works
and if 10 gold is too much, it's a little.
So we should probably ask our game design bot
to help with that a little bit.
But if I just take a look at the current round,
it looks like I can see what I'm about to go up against,
which is a 3.5 and a 3.3.
I have a 2.5, 2.6, and a 3.2.
So I'm going to swap on mobile here.
It looks like that's how I swap.
I can see what my cards do.
So I have a, oh, here's some options
I can buy down here too.
By the way, we have this mechanic.
I think we didn't show this earlier.
But there's this button there called freeze.
And so this is actually a way for you to save a card
that you can't afford yet so that the next round
when you play and you have the gold, you can purchase it.
I like that.
It looks like these all cost three
and we have 10 gold right here, right?
So I think what we can do,
I actually wish I can't see the abilities of these cards.
That might be something we need to fix.
Is that a mobile bug actually?
It might be.
Let me see if I go back to non-responsiveness.
That might just be an overall bug.
Yeah, we'll have to fix that one.
We'll have to fix that.
Okay, well, while we're fixing that, we can just-
Oh, no, well, I think the ability shows up
in the white thing, right?
No, it doesn't?
Okay, we'll have to fix that.
Maybe actually, do you have the new Groff bug voice mode
and you will then wonder if we can just fix it by?
I don't think it's enabled yet.
Okay, well, we can try dictation.
I'm gonna talk to my engineer bot here.
Hey, so it looks like in the latest version of the game,
I can't see the abilities of the bots
that are in my lineup when I'm in the shop interface.
So I can see the bots, I can change the order,
I can drag them around, but I don't know what they do.
Can you open a PR to fix that?
Cool, we'll get an agent on that.
In the meantime, I'm gonna keep playing here.
So I will, well, we'll just go with this lineup for now
just to show how it works.
I'll switch back to mobile mode.
Oh, wait, I gotta keep this, keep the inspector on.
There we go.
And we'll make this big so y'all can see it.
So we'll go ahead and just fight with this lineup
that we have now.
And I actually really love some of these changes.
These animations are really fun.
Yeah, I think we will,
we should go even more ambitious with the visual effects,
maybe, and maybe even add sound effects.
Ooh, yeah.
Could add another layer of,
I mean, it's just more fun.
We did prototype some sound effects last night
towards the end of the day.
So yeah, I think we should bring those back.
Maybe we should just add music to the whole thing too,
even talking about that.
So yeah, we'll do a whole audio engineering pass,
but there's a Notion dock in our Notion team space
where you have a bunch of music we were playing with,
including some cool pseudo battle music.
So we'll see if we can get that all in.
Looks like I won this round and I won it overall too.
So this is cool, let me zoom back in.
Yeah, so I win.
One of the things when you guys were off camera,
I was talking with Vincent,
who works on growth here at SpaceX AI,
and he had a bunch of ton of great ideas
for how we could kind of optimize the growth loop here
and make the game more viral, create more shareability.
And he had a great idea
that we should just let you share your wins.
And so adding a share button here,
I think would be really fun.
So I'm gonna just go ahead
and spin up a feature for that too,
just while we're here, you know?
So let me get a cloud agent going on this.
Hey, can you spin up a cloud agent using potato mode
to make it so that you can share your wins?
So when you finish a game,
you get this win screen that shows your bot team
and the fact that you won.
It'd be awesome if we could make a share button for that,
that lives somewhere on that page
and then has a nice OG image
with maybe your specific bot team,
maybe just a generic win card
that you could use to post your wins on X
or something like that.
Cool, okay, so we'll get another agent going for that.
We have our lineup bot abilities bug fix agent going.
So two guys working right now.
And yeah, once we go home, there we go.
We also need to move the sponsor of the lobby card.
I'm gonna work on that too.
Hey, one more.
So another cloud agent for this using potato mode.
In the home screen, we have a sponsor, the lobby form.
Let's put that behind a button
just like we have the send feedback form.
So when you click send feedback,
you get taken to a feedback page.
That's really cool.
For the sponsor, the lobby,
let's put that behind the form as well
and make sure that form is working.
Sorry, I might have zoned out a bit,
but should we fix that bug with the,
what do you call it, the ticker at the bottom
covering the buttons as well?
Oh, that's a good one too, yeah.
So that one was right here, right?
Where the scrolling.
Yeah, yeah, exactly.
Yeah, let me, for that one,
let me ask you pass a screenshot
because I think it might make it easier
for the bot to understand what's going on.
So I'll play again and then show you.
I actually even wonder if you can ask RockBot
to open the game in its own browser
and turn on the responsive mode and fix it for you.
And this goes back to what I was saying yesterday
where sometimes when I feel like
I'm doing a lot of the work
instead of the bots,
I take a step back and think,
how can I actually hand over this task
to the bot or the agent
so that they can help me and make my life easier?
So it's a very good reminder
as you work with RockBot to just be thinking
every now and then,
maybe actually even set up a bot
that reminds you, right?
Like you can say every day,
like ask Dr. Eggbot to give you some suggestions,
like if am I too much in the loop,
how can I make my workflow more autonomous?
And you can go off and suggest those three.
Yeah, I was just-
What are you prompting?
I'm just prompting here.
I feel like it's kind of blocked by the script.
Yeah, I wanted to-
Oh, there you go.
So we could see the game.
Yeah, so what I'm prompting
is basically what we just talked about,
but I'm gonna do it in this very specific way.
I'm like, hey, this new ticker
covers up some of the shop buttons,
spin up a cloud agent using potato mode,
inspect and fix that issue.
And then one thing I really like to say
is before writing any code, do X.
So here before writing any code,
run the app, thursdayareno.com,
find the exact bug and behavior and then proceed.
And so we will get an agent on that as well.
And so, yeah, again,
if you're not used to writing code with Crock-Bots,
this is definitely a really fun way to do it.
Having one engineer that's sort of your ringleader
can spin up a bunch of cloud agents.
These are cursor cloud agents,
so they work in the cloud,
they have their own virtual machines,
they can reproduce behavior,
they have browsers they can walk through.
So in our case, we're building a web app.
Really great to just be able to walk through
the screens of the web app.
And agents are pretty good at this too,
so they can take screenshots,
they can find an exact bug.
And perhaps most importantly,
they can verify their work.
So if they implement a fix or implement an issue,
they have the option to just go in,
make sure that the fix of the issue
is actually what they thought it would be.
They're not just looking at code tokens,
they're looking at kind of how the fix looks in prod too.
So, all right, so I have a bunch of folks going.
I'm curious, what are your agents doing?
What are your bots doing?
I actually have a project going on,
like a project agent that I got Groutbot to create.
And I am doing a lot of UI polish work
as well as bug fixes.
So, I guess we showed this earlier,
but I can kind of refresh your memory.
So Matt added this really nice user feedback feature
in the game.
So if you click on Thursday Arena
and you go back to the home screen,
you can see there's a send feedback button.
And if you encounter any bugs
or you want to give us feedback, you can do that.
20 character minimum there, Roshan.
We were getting some spam,
so we had to enforce the minimum.
Yeah, so all of this feedback is going into Slack
and we have bots and agents watching that channel
and just automatically reproducing the issue
and confirming that there's a bug.
And then if it does find the bug and confirm it,
it'll try to do a fix
and then automatically merge the fix.
Matt, what is this?
Interesting, what is this phone number?
Okay, we're going to do a live demo because I think my,
do I even have my phone?
I do, I do, I do.
Okay, so I was playing around with some XAI voice agents.
So this is actually an XAI feature
and allows you to create a voice agent very easily.
So if I call this number here that's listed.
Maybe we can get the camera zoomed in on Matt for this.
Yeah, let's get a real good close up of Matt.
Oh my God.
Well, I've been using the tool
and I just want you to tell the team it looks great
and we appreciate you building this on such short notice.
It's awesome to hear, glad it's hitting the spot.
Yeah, I think that's it.
So maybe you could send the feedback through.
Thanks for the kind words.
Your feedback's been noted
and sent straight to the team.
There's your feedback, it's right there.
It's in our Slack channel.
That's amazing, that was like super real time as well.
So yeah, how did you build this?
I'm so curious.
Yeah, well, if we cut over to my screen,
I could give you maybe a walkthrough, we could show you.
So actually using XAI.
So XAI has a, you happen to have to delete the token
on whatever screen I was just on,
but XAI has a voice workflow builder.
And so essentially on their voice side,
you can build a voice agent.
And so this is all in a GUI.
And you can come in, basically build these agents
and deploy them very quickly that answer phone calls,
basically what you just saw.
So I didn't actually write any code
for what I was sharing with you all.
That just went on the XAI side.
And then I have a web hook that basically accepts that
and passes it through to our Slack channel.
So it's all lost and the same productions
and guardrails are on that phone number
that we use for some of the moderation.
So you won't be able to like,
do any funny business through that phone call.
But maybe we could cut off my screen for a second.
No, okay.
I'm looking it up, don't worry.
Yeah, yeah, no worries.
And we can keep talking about what we're building.
Also that token only half the value is shown.
So we shouldn't have to worry about that.
Great.
And I have now deleted that.
So we are good.
Just for complete safety.
I was actually surprised we made it this far.
Good save.
Yeah, no secrets in the chat.
Chat is for games and good vibes only.
No secrets.
But I think that I keep saying this
and I'm kind of like repeating myself a lot.
But I keep going back to this idea of,
Graphbot is such a powerful tool
for really bringing together data from everywhere.
And as you saw Matt just demo,
you can have voice support agents through Grok.
You can have in-app feedback that feeds to a Slack channel.
All of those pieces of feedback can just feed in
and be aggregated into your bots,
into your team of bots.
And they can kick off cloud agent workflows.
They can fix things.
They can report them.
It really empowers even such a small team
to almost operate like a big company, right?
Because you have all these automations
that are just helping you.
So I think the future is very interesting, right?
With Graphbot, I'm wondering if we'll see a lot more
like indie game studios, you know,
like really small teams, very, very nimble,
just using AI to punch above their weight.
100%, I think one of the things I've realized
is that voice agents are actually really good,
specifically Grok and XAI voice agents are really good.
And so even on that customer service thing,
would I feel comfortable having a voice agent
call people on my behalf?
Probably not.
I still think it's nice to have a human touch
and I get a little annoyed candidly when I call places
and there are voice agents on the other side.
If I'm trying to get help immediately,
that can be frustrating.
So I think you wanna think through
when it makes sense for your users
to encounter a voice agent.
But for things like submitting information
or getting tasks done,
you can basically give those XAI Grok voice agents tools.
So like I could have equipped it with
a Notion tool or a Slack tool
or built my own custom tool through a web hook.
So say we wanted users to be able to delete
their accounts over the phone.
Someone calls in, we give it a tool delete account.
This might be something you don't want users to do,
right, but maybe something simpler like update,
address, update name, et cetera.
Then the agent can take action on the user's behalf
that saves the human's time
or maybe perhaps there's like a escalate issue tool,
right, you can imagine for your restaurant,
you call in and you have a voice agent
and the user says, what are your hours?
The voice agent can deliver the hours
and the user says, hey, can you help me place an order?
You could have like an escalate tool
that then forwards that call to the actual business.
And so now we're building in some of these
automation workflows that aren't necessarily
Grok bot specific, but they are Grok specific.
And that's kind of part of the suite of tools
that we have on the XAI side
to allow you to kind of get some more stuff done.
So built in all of our feedback flows
and we have a very active customer feedback channel
at this point.
So now we just need to start actioning on that feedback.
And I think we're making progress though.
So lots of stuff in flight.
Yeah, while you were talking,
one of my cloud agents that was working on
getting the cards, our lineup to show their abilities
looks like it has a good draft PR
but it's not like a perfect look yet.
I kind of want some more detail in the card itself.
And so now she's going to give it some feedback
on that while we're going here.
Open cursor.
What should I call this channel?
Metrics.
Oh, we have a metrics channel now?
Yeah, I was just thinking it'd be really cool to have a,
so I guess, you know, like we have a channel now
that feeds in feedback for us,
but I think it's also important,
you know, as a game studio to celebrate our wins.
So I think it'd be nice to have a metrics channel
where we can like, you know, whenever we hit milestones.
Nice.
And I just created it.
So maybe we can show my screen really quick
just for like a minute.
We just enabled a Vercel analytics on thursdayarena.com.
A very nice graph.
We went up from zero to,
well, I think we have 1,400 people on the page right now.
So, you know, again, like getting all this data
is super, super valuable.
We can see where people are coming from.
We can try to optimize, you know, like our outreach
or, you know, something like that.
We can get a sense of like,
how many people are on mobile?
How many people are on desktop?
In fact, we have more mobile players
than we have desktop.
So that's really good input for prioritization.
44% are on iOS as well.
So yeah, I think that's all I wanted to show.
But it's good to have these numbers
because Grofbot has all these connectors.
We have a Vercel plugin in Grofbot.
So Grofbot can pull this information as well
and help you put together plans,
help you put together, you know, whatever you want.
Yeah, and actually as you were doing that,
I just realized I have my data scientist bot
that's been generating all my charts.
And so I literally just prompted it like,
hey, we just turned on Vercel analytics.
Please factor those into your regular routines.
And I already have Vercel connected to my Grofbot setup.
And so the plugin's already there,
really easy to just be able to say like,
cool, like pull those numbers in
and add it to your data store.
And I think that's a really like,
just on-demand data science.
I can't get enough.
It's awesome.
Cool.
Over here, I have my play tester bot also playing.
We still need to fix this one.
I guess we haven't fixed it yet.
The banner, the ticker, still covering the buttons.
Ooh, yeah, I have a PR for that being worked on.
It looks like it's actually testing its changes right now.
Yeah.
It's going through a bunch of computer use, I can see.
Yeah, I think verification is so important
because, you know, you need your bots
to be able to actually run the code,
take screenshots, and it gives you so much more confidence
that it actually understands the problem.
So, very glad that we built that early on.
Yeah, I think that was really, actually really helpful.
One of the things that Lauren has set up
for our internal products as well within SpaceX AI
is sort of these verified skills.
And so the idea here is you teach the bot once
how it can test your product.
And once you do that once,
you can have a skill that you continue to update
and kind of use that to, you know,
make that part of your workflow.
So, yeah, verification.
And I'm just looking at our leaderboard.
We have a second diamond player,
Dev Arminess, congratulations.
Ari the Monk.
Ari the Monk, so holding strong at number one.
But I think, oh yeah, you know another feature we should add
is it would be really cool to click on the player
and watch, like, if we could see their game history
and we can see and we can learn.
Yeah. Learn from how they play.
Like, how are these players so much better
than everybody else?
Is our game history working?
Because I know we had a past games feature.
I don't know if that works.
I'm just going to have to go and test it.
Hey, so in our home page.
So, hello, I am recording our past matches.
Oh, that's cool.
Okay, so you can see, and as you can see who we play.
Yeah, look, Matt, I actually played against you when I won.
How do you feel about that?
I think that might be incorrect data.
No, no, this is definitely incorrect.
I think you might have ran an insert on a database.
No, no, no, no, this is real, real data.
I don't remember that.
I don't recall that as that match.
Yeah, well, we should make the leaderboards
clickable somehow.
Yeah, I'll get a bot right now.
Okay, okay, cool, cool, cool, sounds good.
I think I have some updates on lineup bot abilities
and shops, that's really cool.
Let's see here.
We make user, they call it user names clickable.
Cool.
We got a bunch of stuff going on
just to do a quick reset.
If you're just joining us, we are on day three
of building our game studio and launched on our first game.
We launched around 10 a.m. this morning,
ThursdayArena.com, at ThursdayArena on X.
We're walking through some UI updates we just made.
We just went through and tested the experience together
and every time we find something we wanna fix,
we're feeding it into a grok bot
whose job it is to spin up some agents to go and fix it.
And I'm really liking how these cards
are coming together.
Yeah, I have some even cooler updates.
Yeah, so again, I really like this.
I love the CSS library.
So it's a, I'm not a big Pokemon card fan,
but I have a lot of friends who are.
And I happen to find a site where it's by Simon Goldner.
Sorry if I'm mispronouncing your name.
I just followed him.
Oh, nice.
But yeah, you've got these like really cool effects
for these cards and I thought it would look so good
on ThursdayArena.
If you scroll down, they get even cooler.
There's like these extra special
like chevron glowy things going on.
Yeah, where are they?
It's like...
Oh yeah, well, these look, this looks amazing.
Yeah, right, like that kind of thing.
I wonder how that'll work on mobile.
Wow, I love the effects.
They look so good.
We should definitely get some of these in there.
Yeah, yeah.
So shiny, all of those.
We're gonna use that library, thank you, open source
and kind of bring them in.
And something cool, I guess, about these cards
is that they were all designed by Grok Imagine.
So we took all of the GrokBots that we have
on the bot marketplace and we randomly assigned rarities.
We gave them fun skills.
We also have, of course, the author name.
So maybe it actually another fun thing we could think of
is how do we get chat to be able to create their own bots
that show up in our game?
That could be another driver of some growth for our app.
I think it'd be really cool.
I mean, one way we could do that is anyone can share a bot
from GrokBot today.
So if you have a bot that you really like working with,
there's a share icon in the top right.
And if you click that, you can share a bot.
Do you wanna show how you can share a bot?
Yeah, actually, why don't we switch to my screen for a second
and I can kind of show you how that works.
So if you have a favorite bot that you've been working with
or just a bot that you wanna create
and kind of share with your friends,
any one of these bots, you can go over to it
and just click this and click share as template.
I'll do it with, well, let's do it with our game designer
and click share as template.
And actually, it's really fun.
This just does it in the chat.
So you prompt the bot to create a template
and these bots know how to templatize themselves.
And under the hood, a couple of cool things happen here
is like GrokBot strips out all the sensitive information
that might be associated with this particular bot.
So you don't have to worry about any of that
getting sort of like shared outside of your workspace.
But the core ideas, right?
The core memories about this build,
the core ideas, we're on a team account here.
And so you could actually make it shareable only as a team
but I'll go ahead and make this public.
And so at the end of this process,
you actually get a shareable link.
And for those of you who were watching earlier,
we showed you how you'd install one of those bots.
I installed Cerebro for Matt on our go-to-market team.
Sorry, not this Matt, not me.
Other Matt.
But yeah, you can share these templates
and we could probably make it really easy
to just import one of your own bots into the game.
Maybe you could build your own team of bots
and go and do cool things with them.
That's a good feature.
Cool, all right, so what's working?
Oh, actually, while you're talking,
do you want to bring up the leaderboard again?
Sure, just something changed.
As we were talking, our bots just shipped the PR
to revamp the leaderboard.
It's a little bit more user-friendly now.
You can find yourself in the leaderboard.
We have a special, much nicer-looking design.
This is totally new.
Yeah, so Ari, the monkey, still number one.
I like how it just tells me
that I am falling further and further
every time I log in.
Yeah, I'm ranked 247 now.
Oh man, as long as I'm beating potato.
Oh my gosh, yeah.
I'd have to be last on the board.
This is great, I actually really like this.
And so we have the one, two, three,
the podium at the top.
Really awesome, really awesome.
And we have pagination now, which is nice.
Okay, just to orient us,
I'm getting a note from production over here.
It looks like we are going to have another segment
at 2 p.m. Pacific in just about four minutes.
And so we'll try and get to a good stopping point here.
Maybe what we can summarize for the group
is what is everyone going to be working on
for the next few minutes.
We'll kind of come back on maybe at 2.15, 2.30
and show what we've made since then.
I have a few agents working on some UI polish.
Oh, there's our bot template by the way
that we just published, that's awesome.
UI polish, I have some agents working on
fixing those bugs that we talked about.
I see a bunch of other PRs landing here though.
You know, what I would really love is if we could...
So yeah, we have bugs and UI polish that are going on.
But I'd love for chat to be able to submit bots as well.
So maybe we can do that
and hopefully, like maybe kick that off now.
Like add a really small feature.
Maybe like, let's just keep it extremely simple.
Just like an input box, like share a link
to the bot that you've created.
And maybe for now we can just dump it into Slack
and then we can look through and pick a few
to actually turn into real bot templates
or sorry, bots in our game.
And then we'll make them and hopefully
you'll be able to play with your own bot in Thursday arena.
And then I think we have some other stuff cooking, Matt.
What are we cooking on?
What are you working on?
I got a bunch of stuff landing.
So I'm making some improvements to the home screen
if you wanna cut to my screen.
So a few things, first,
making some improvements to the home screen.
I've been kind of chilling in cursor for a little while.
Simultaneously, just trying to link to our X account.
And then in this sort of agent here,
I was working on a nice little,
seems like the cloud agent might be,
might need to restart the dev server,
but I'm working on having just a link to the live stream.
So it shows on the homepage that should be in imminently.
And then also setting up our agent environment,
our cloud agent environment.
So I wanna make it as easy as possible
to spin up cloud agents
that have the environment pre-configured.
And the way that we do that
is by giving it access to the same,
like similar preview API keys and credentials
so that our agent can pull in our dev environment
basically and start it the same way a human would.
So it goes back to what Lauren's been talking about a lot,
which is kind of like feedback loops
and things of that nature.
And then also I started off
this exploratory base UI migration
because I'm starting to get tired
of like all these like buttons and stuff
all over the place.
So yeah, I need to like start thinking
through this a little bit.
I kicked off basically a planning agent.
And I mean, this is a really great way,
at least for me to kind of like
work through a technology that I don't use all the time.
It's like elicitation of like,
oh, hey, we need a UI improvements.
You ask me what you need from my input
and we're gonna work through this together
and we're gonna get that implemented.
It also just kind of helps to know
what base UI or Radix or some of these other things are,
which are just like essentially systems
for building component libraries
and design and implementing standardized user interfaces.
So yeah, a lot of stuff cooking.
I feel like once you get the basics,
you can just start kicking off cloud agents
to handle many of these things now.
And actually speaking of cloud agents,
my agent that was working on fixing the shop interface
where you can see the full card now is good.
I got a good PR.
So I'm gonna go ahead and merge that.
So we have one bug that we just fixed live on the stream.
Nice, cool.
With that, I think we're gonna transition
to a quick video to warm up for our next guest.
So whenever we're ready, let's go ahead
and cut over to that and we will be back
with a bunch more updates really, really soon.
We're gonna build a company.
We got 72 hours.
We haven't done anything.
I mean, we just spent the last 20 minutes
of yapping, we shouldn't be able to do that.
So the goal is to have an idea in day one.
Maybe it's a good time to talk about like exactly
what we mean when we say that we're in built-in.
Yeah, I don't know.
I kind of go back to the build something people want.
functionality, right?
Maybe something we use ourselves.
That's where we're gonna try to build
with a human touch.
Yeah.
Most importantly, that's something we're gonna try
to build this week.
And then, you know, what I think might be fun to do
is just kind of look through all the great feedback
we've gotten.
So, what we're working on is a restaurant pop-up. So we're going to do a pop-up in person in San Francisco.
We're building a company. Not everything is working perfectly. We are building it as we go.
I love it. You see, we've played three things. This is the merch, the ticketing,
we'd like to solve the case, and then it's finding a venue.
Yeah, you know what? Let's do what every startup has always pitched to every VC ever.
Guys, we're going to start small. The addressable market is everybody.
We're going continuously live from 8.30 to like 6.00, 6.30. Tune in here any time.
Really? I don't get the moods yet, but I want one.
We need to improve it. It's kind of...
Love it. Love it. Well, hey, welcome back, everyone. Welcome back. Hopefully you enjoyed
that recap of the past two days. We are joined by a new guest. We'll introduce Dan very shortly
here, but just find it helpful for folks who are just tuning in to kind of share where we are.
So, we are on day three of building a game used, or really building a business with Grok Bot.
We kicked off two days ago. We started off by exploring a bunch of ideas. The goal was to ship
something by Thursday. We have done that. We launched our game this morning. We are building a
game studio. That's our business. We launched our first game. It is ThursdayArena.com or
at ThursdayArena on X if you want to stay up to date on what's going on. We just made a bunch
of UI improvements that I think are pretty exciting. And we've had a bunch of really
great guests who've been joining us throughout the day, actually throughout the week, to chat
with us about how we can turn this business and make it a really, really business. So,
really excited for Dan Hill to be joining us from the Stripe team. Dan,
welcome. You want to introduce yourself, say a little bit about what you work on.
Yeah, great to be here. It's been fascinating watching the live stream the last few days.
Like, I've seen the game just as I was on the way over here, and I'm like,
I just need to, you know, want to play this game. But yeah, I'm down to work at Stripe
on Link. So, if you go into Grok Bot today, one of the connectors you'll see is Link.
We also have a bunch of Stripe stuff. But the Link one basically lets your agent
buy stuff on the internet. So, you know, in this game example, actually, I've personally
built a few games with Grok Bot over the last couple of weeks. Often I need to buy, like,
texture packs. And, like, I need, like, just, like, oh, I need a set of trees that can go,
like, you know, in my game or whatever I need to do. So, yeah, Link basically creates one-time
use cards that the agent can go off on the internet and buy stuff. There's a really nice
UI in the Grok Bot where basically you approve the spend. So, it's, okay, I need $10 to buy this,
you know, this tree pack for my game. And you see, great, approved. And then the
agent can go off and safely go buy stuff. Yeah. I'm trying to log into my Link account
behind the scenes here so we can try to do some, try to do a live purchase on stream,
maybe. I feel like that could be really cool. But I guess where I wanted to start, so you,
sounds like you have a sense of the game and kind of what we're trying to do. Obviously,
Stripe works on payments. This is sort of like the lifeblood of the business in some ways,
I'm guessing. Can you talk a little bit about sort of what you're seeing with AI agents and
payments? Like clearly a bunch of cool stuff, at least from what I'm seeing on X and things
like this, and obviously some stuff we've worked on together. But we'd just love to get your take
on like, what's new with agents and payments? I mean, this is not new to anyone right here,
but like the explosion of just like AI capabilities in the last, I don't know,
like it feels like two weeks, but like call it a month has been, has been incredible obviously,
you know, and Grok's been a huge part of that. Like, and for some reason, it's just like at
the end of so many of our sort of things we're building or doing end up with, and I need some
money to go buy that thing or to complete that task, I need some, some money. So we've been
seeing a huge range of use cases on Grok and others with payments. There's a whole category
of stuff, which is like, you probably see on X, a whole bunch of like, I have a parking ticket.
Yeah, I literally can't be bothered to go through this, like, what a great use case.
I just don't want to go through this whole, you know, flow that's janky and hard. I'm
just going to have, you know, Grok go pay that for me. A lot of people are doing like, you know,
restaurant reservations, flight booking. I have Grok hooked up to my inbox. You know, I always
get in like, I need to pay this bill or I need to like do this thing for my kids school and Grok
can just be like, yeah, I can go do that for you. I can, I can make that, that go.
If you want to cut to my screen for a second, I'll pull up the parking ticket example, because
I just love, I love that one. I thought it was awesome. Not just as someone who works on
Grokbot, but it's like such a cool use case as a human. I just want help doing the stuff
that I don't have to do every day. I mean, there's like this, this is huge sort of, you know,
one set of people using I think these AI tools like Grokbot are just like, people with busy lives,
stuff to get done. They just want to get like, to your point, they just like, here's a whole bunch
of tasks. Can I just fire off, you know, a couple of agents to do that? I mean, the other is like,
I guess kind of to the game you're building here, it's like, sort of entrepreneurs,
solo printers. I myself literally have like 17 half baked projects at home. I actually build a game
and I go off like 3GS boot up thing and I like spend an evening just like building a game and that's
super fun. The next day I have an idea for like some new thing I want to make. And yeah, a ton
of those end up with like payments, you know, you want a provision of a cell account or you want to
provision, you know, you need some email service that you want to pay for, some AWS bill you want
to pay for. So yes, you tell people they're needing payments to go kind of like spin up
the things they need on this stack. Yeah, we did it all manually. So I sat down for like an hour
and logged into like 10 different services, put in our credit card numbers, and we got the whole
like infra set up. Yeah, that was fun. At Stripe, we have a thing called Stripe projects,
basically, which is integrated into grok. And basically, stripes just partnered with a ton
of these infra providers, I think you've got a projects.dev. Yep. If you scroll down there,
you'll see, these are kind of all the companies that are just like natively integrated. And so
basically, you connect the stripe account once. And then you can just provision those. Oh,
straight from winning. Yeah, exactly. Like, hey, grok, I need like, you know, I need database,
I need email sending thing, I need a hosting provider, maybe I need a domain name. Great.
You can see it there. It'll just Yeah, that would have been so good. Because I think,
even on like day one, I think our audience also saw us like, we were kind of like,
all over the place, China, you know, get all these services. Yeah, we were really struggling.
So this, this is like a really, really good product. We kind of have this like,
not like running joke, but like, so many of us, like you guys, and the team at Stripe are like,
we're always like hacking on something, building something on the weekends. And it's like, you have
the idea. And then you've got your agent spun up. And then to your point, you hit that point of
like, oh, and now I need to go do like manual tasks, and that kind of kills it. But yeah,
but yeah, it's like when the agent gets blocked on you, it's when the fun kind of goes on.
Exactly. You want you to be in self driving mode. And so yeah, exactly. So on the project,
we can use that you can spin up all those providers just right there from Grotbot. And yeah, get going.
That's awesome. That's awesome. So it sounds like a lot of cool stuff going on with link a lot of
cool ways to buy things, maybe we'll see if I can get that working, we could try to buy something
together. What I'd love to spend a few minutes on though. So, you know, obviously, you know,
you know, payments incredibly well, you're also a product person, right? You think a lot about
product, but you're not not afraid of codes, like kind of the perfect person we need for this
phase of the business. You know, we said when we started off this work that we'd be building a
business in three days, we've launched our first product, we're operating in classic San Francisco
startup fashion, which is like, let's go get users and we'll figure out how to monetize it.
So what I want to do that might be a fun exercise together, is maybe just work through
how you'd suggest we monetize the product. So we don't really have a strong plan here,
we've thought about some ads, we've thought about some merch sales and things like this,
but we'd love to kind of just go through the game in case you hadn't seen it yet.
Walk through how it works, and then maybe just like riff a little bit on air.
Let's do it.
Let's do it. Yeah.
Okay, so this is Thursday Arena. There's a practice mode, there's a play mode. You can see we have
these cute little cards. All these cards are actually different crockbots from our crockbot
marketplace. So yeah, if you just go to x.ai slash bot slash marketplace, you can see
all those bots, we imported them, they are now characters in a game. So thanks for all
the folks who are in the marketplace.
This brings me back to my Magic the Gathering days.
Yes, that was 20 years ago.
That was how we drew some inspiration from Magic and new video cards and all those. And so
essentially the way this works is you buy and draft a lineup, and I love that animation,
whoever worked on that. And you order this lineup with all their abilities, and you hit fight,
and you're paired up with a teammate or I guess an opponent in this case.
Things happen, abilities get played, and that's the game. So it looks like I won the first
round. There's a phase in between rounds here where I'm spending some of this gold that I've
earned, which we should rename to tokens. We keep waiting to do that. I'm spending some of my tokens
and basically continue this game until we win. That's the game. So yeah, I'm curious. You
thought a lot about great products, you thought a lot about payments. What comes to mind for
you here when you think about some of the...
Yeah, so to monetize, I guess a couple of paths kind of seem obvious first. One path
is definitely ads. Totally works. Generally, you need a lot of eyeballs to get that to work,
but really does really great at supporting a free product. If you want people to play the game,
ads can work great. I feel like with these kind of games,
and there's a couple of games that are similar. My kids really like playing.
Avatar World is one of them. But have you thought about allowing people to pay for upgrades or
better cards, better characters that they can unlock if they pay?
We thought about that. We keep going back and forth on it. I think we decided we did not want
to let you pay for power because those types of games just sort of prey on your ability to pay,
sort of pay to win. So definitely an option. I guess if we really needed to make a bunch of
money, you wanted to create that system, I think we could. But we're trying to think of ways...
I just lost this one. Trying to think of ways where we could try to find revenue streams,
partnership streams or something like that, that would let us keep the game sort of the same.
I mean, other ideas, this might be a bit of a crazy one, but you could kind of go with
sponsored characters. I like that.
So you've got your Grok characters here, but there's actually...
I mean, this is, for a startup, maybe a little harder, but you've got your Pokemon tie-in,
you've got some... Bring in some Disney characters, and just like, could you get
brands excited about like, oh, if this game has got a ton of traction, then like, you know,
custom cards, kind of like, you know, snaps done with like custom filters that you can like,
you know, brands can create for the game too, maybe.
I really like that. I'm actually, we have a bot here that's recording a bunch of
go-to-market monetization ideas. So I'm going to just feed that into the bot while you're
talking so we can capture all that. Something like, actually, it was just dictated.
Yeah, that's just dictated.
So we just had a great idea from Dan Hill here. Could we try or log this idea that we could have
sponsored cards? So rather than making the game pay to win, which we don't want to do,
we could maybe go find partners to help us sponsor cards and pay to be like,
featured on a particular card without changing the behavior of the card. I really like that.
Another interesting idea is like, I feel like bot templates are really powerful because...
So actually, our game's database is powered by PlanetScale. And one of our friends at
PlanetScale sent me a PlanetScale bot that helped me with all of the database administration.
And he got me thinking a lot about, it would be really interesting if companies and brands have
not just plugins that you install into tools like Graphbot or to cursor, but you actually
release a bot that almost encapsulates all the skills that you need to spin up.
For example, imagine we had a Stripe Link bot that helps you integrate, set your cards up,
things like that. So it got me thinking, it would be interesting to have those kind of
company-built bots as well as part of the featured feature bots.
Having them kind of pay for that?
Maybe something like that, I think would be interesting.
Okay. Well, we have...
I like what you said. We don't want to have to pay to win.
Right. Yeah. Yeah.
And there definitely is space for those games, just not our favorite. So we're like,
it's our game. We're not going to make it pay to win.
Curious Dan, what else is running around your head right now as you kind of think through
what you're seeing?
Just as an aside, before you get to that part, the voice dictation stuff is like...
Oh, yeah.
It's my favorite.
It's just so good.
Like, if I was writing code like two years ago, I would type code.
Oh, yeah.
A year ago, I would type prompts.
And now I'm just like, yeah, I just got my phone out and I just start talking to
Grok or whatever. It's insane.
Yeah. And if you haven't seen it, we actually added more to this.
Hey, what's on deck for today?
Hey, main item for today is finalizing a proposal for partner.
Great. Can you start drafting a proposal and send me a notion link?
Oh, and I need some coffee.
I don't know if folks can hear this.
On it. Want your usual oat milk cappuccino?
Yeah, that sounds great.
Okay. We don't have to listen to the whole thing.
Yeah.
We literally just announced this an hour ago. And so I think actually,
voice a way to interact with agents is going to be so cool. We're going to hopefully be able
to show this a little bit later in the stream. It is rolling out over the next few days.
So if you're using Grokbot, a really cool way to maybe even interact in a completely new way too.
Yeah. It's a really fun way to like, you know, if you're maybe not driving, but you know,
like you're walking, walking to work, you know, you're like on a subway or something.
And it's a bit awkward to get your phone out and start prompting.
You can actually just chat with it like, like a, like a friend.
I did a couple of days ago, I was, I was, I was out, I was walking somewhere between places
and it's my anniversary weekend coming up. And so I got on my Grok in my, on my phone,
pop an anniversary bot. I was dictating, Hey, this is my anniversary. These are the things we like.
These are the places we're trying to go. Just like, okay, just, can you build an
itinerary and go like figure all that out for me? And just like, yeah, just dictating just
like in five minutes, a task that I would otherwise had been putting off for ages.
Like it was great.
I love that too. Because I feel like there's a dictating code and we're,
we've been doing this sort of all, all week, right? Like, Hey, can you build this feature?
Hey, here's what I'm thinking. I love dictating the knowledge work stuff. It's like,
I need you to coordinate these things. Send this email. Also do that. Like get me the coffee.
My wife's birthday is this weekend. And so I've been doing that. This is the exact same thing
of like, Hey, here's like the 10 things in my head. I'm not quite sure what,
which exact combination of them I want, but let's try and make something of it.
And I find the agents are just so good at, I mean, they're good at text, right? They're,
they're language models. And so you can just feed it a bunch of text. And one trick
that Lauren's been sort of showing us throughout the stream as well is asking the agent to restate
the plan in its own words, which is so cool. Cause then I kind of, you make sure that it
understands you. It's almost like this intern or colleague that you're teaching and make you feel
like, did you get that before you go live? So yeah. This, this tip was really kind of inspired
by the fact that, you know, like models are getting so capable that, that they're almost
like these magical input boxes. You just type something in there and it just does it. It's,
it's pretty incredible. But it got me thinking a lot about like, you know,
uh, the bottle, the, I guess the bottleneck is you being able to get your idea across well.
And so I love the stream of consciousness thing, because sometimes you just have this
very abstract picture of what you want and you don't know what exactly it is. So just like,
just yap for five minutes and then tell it to restate in its own words. And then you
get a sense of, did it actually understand? Totally. Um, so if your game, if you guys
considered, um, any kind of like straightforward, you know, freemium model, like play hand games
for free, then you have to pay, you know, a $2 a month subscription to keep playing or like
gating certain features behind. Cause right now it's just like one team versus another team.
Right? Yeah, totally. I actually was there'd be a world where it was like, Oh,
and if you pay X, you can have like multiple five team games or like run your own league.
Maybe like, could you do something like that? Or like, Oh, if you want to be like, like a
organized with your friends, you can like set up a league that you, I like that sort of like taking
calling back to the old like in person trading card game days and having a league. I really
liked the subscription idea. Cause I think that's really durable revenue for our business. And
especially where a brand new game studio, like durability would be awesome, right? So we can
fund our next game. Right. Um, and obviously I don't know if we, yeah, that would be a really
interesting business model where I wonder actually, what if we had a, well, I guess I don't,
we don't actually have a company name for our game studio. We should, maybe,
maybe just incorporate it. Maybe our company is just Thursday and maybe we could have a
Thursday subscription where you can play all our games for a monthly fee. So you get more of the
value of the subscription goes up over time as we make more games. And that, if you have a
subscriber base, they're going to be the great early adopters of new games you want to put in.
Cause they're already sort of putting, they're already paying, they're already invested. So like,
Oh, you have a new game come out. They'll be the first ones to get in and give feedback,
play, you know, kind of make the game better. I love that. Yeah. And for those who are watching
me just click around idly while we talk, you can see the UI is literally changing by the minute.
This home screen now looks totally different than it did when Dan first got on the set.
So the, the factory is going, this is the coding factory that Lauren is established.
That's like, I'm not typing right now. It's just, it's just doing one.
I, this is my favorite bot too. I have this bot bake who's our engineer and we're at 235
plus PRs already since we build this idea in earnest. We'll have more, we'll have more,
but it's like having an event stream of all the things that are happening.
You can see on my, my slot here. Yeah. Hopefully not mostly as well.
Yeah. Dan, I wanted to go back to the subscription idea. Obviously like this is a thing.
Maybe just to chat about like what trends are you seeing? Because I think one of the things
that we've kind of a lot of the folks who are tuning into chat and are, have been coming in
and questions on is, you know, like the, the world looks different, business models might be
changing. Obviously this open router thing is kind of interesting. Just curious what you're
seeing. Obviously I'm sure link is playing a big part of that in terms of the consumer
side of things, but yeah, how would you describe like Stripe's view on the world as AI businesses
and AI powered businesses start to exist more? Yeah. I mean, let me answer that both on the
consumer side and the business side. Obviously at Stripe we have, you know, huge conviction in,
in, in, you know, AI and a genetic and where that world is going and the capabilities unlocking,
you know, both for us as like employees and engineers and product people who are building
each day, you know, like we're all in these tools all day building, but also in the, you know,
the users and the consumers we partner with. So on the consumer side it's a really interesting
sort of thing we've been observing the last few months. If you look at like consumer spending
on AI subscriptions, you know, spending on like Grotbot or on, you know, OpenAI or on,
you know, Muse or whatever, it's been increasing steadily over the last few years.
Started this year, the number of people paying more than a hundred dollars a month
for AI products has grown like 5X. Really? Okay. I think there was just like so much consumer
demand for this kind of thing where like people can just like, they can build things, they can
create things. They don't have to be super like deep in engine, you know, engineering and sort of
knowing how to, how to, how to do that. So like, I think on the consumer side, there's this huge
growth of like people who are just like really interested in creating these kinds of games and
building. You know, on the business side, of course, you know, an explosion of both startups
and of course, on the big labs and like you guys doing doing really great stuff. Obviously, you
know, we stripe, you know, start collaborating with Metronome much recently. So like a lot more
AI companies, I think, you know, looking at like usage based billing as a model. I think it'll
be really interesting to see if that plays into a consumer world too. You know, personally,
I have my subscriptions and I always have a little thing where I can buy extra credits if I
need it to finish the task. So I think, you know, we'll see a lot more on UVB. You know,
one of the things that Stripe is doing a lot on right now is like helping AI companies think about
risk and fraud. Okay. So as you're growing massive user bases, you know, a lot of stuff
we're trying to do is like, how do we help make sure that the people who are, you know,
subscribing to your products are good and how do we, how do we lower that fraud and things too?
Awesome, awesome. Yeah, these are all these are all great. And I guess one thing that maybe we
can try and do if we get some time this afternoon is build a quick strike of integration and figure
out how we try out some of these monetization ideas. Yeah, I'm pretty sure with your existing
Grok connector on Stripe, oh, yeah, if you connect it up, you should be able to get going on one.
Yeah, we do. Okay, so yeah, I haven't added it yet. But you see here, you've got like,
Stripe best practices, that'll get you integration going, we've got Stripe directories,
that'll help you find businesses to buy from Stripe projects. So that's what will help you
provision services. Exactly. Yeah. So yeah, you should be able to connect the Stripe connector
here. And like, just go ahead and add it in case we decide we want to do this. Yeah. And then we
definitely need to make money at some point. Yeah, yeah, point, point, point one of your
Grok bots at getting a subscription set up and it should, it should get it done.
I think that's a good stretch goal for the afternoon. You get our first dollar.
Get your first dollar. That would be amazing. That would be really cool. That would be a real
games video. Yeah, exactly. A revenue creating games. Yeah, I don't know if we'll get a whole
business incorporated by then, but we'll see. We'll see what we can do. Exactly. Yeah, yeah.
Okay, awesome. Well, it sounds like we have a bunch of really good ideas. I guess, Dan,
I'm curious, maybe as we wind down here about five or 10 minutes left, you, you talked a little
bit about what link is doing for making it easy to buy things with agents. And I've seen a bunch
of buzz on the internet about link lately. And obviously you can, you can do that with Grok
bots. So if we can hide my screen for a second, I want to see if I can get link working
without giving away my credit card numbers or personal information. We could just go to the
wide angle camera shot, please, when you get a second for the production team.
But in the meantime, while we do that, I'm curious, like, what's next for link? How are you guys
thinking about the future? Because I know stripes probably is on the frontier of a lot of this stuff.
Like, where do you see this whole thing going? Yeah. So we got, we got a bunch of stuff coming
on link. So the stuff we're doing right now is really around helping agents buy things that they
need, whether that's personal stuff, whether it's to build a business, go buy things. So a lot
of stuff we've been working on there is like, how do you help agents understand how to use checkout
forms? How do you help them buy, especially from striped merchants without any friction,
so they can just, you know, buy what they need. We'll be expanding into more geographies soon.
So start off US only, but we have other countries coming. The next one that I'm really excited about
and folks are actually using with Grok bot is what we call financial insights. So this is
allowing Grok to basically import your, you know, credit card data, your bank data,
and do all kinds of personal finance stuff. Or if you're building a business, right? Like,
why not connect your business accounts in and then have it be able to kind of, you know, oh,
I see your credit card limits coming up, you know, here's how we can optimize your business for you.
So we have a lot coming around, sort of personal financial insights and connecting your bank
accounts and credit cards with link. As a personal finance, sort of like have my
spreadsheets and trial the apps person. I think this will have been pretty cool about that.
I use it all the time. It's just like so great to have like, I, one of my Grok
agents is just a personal finance thing. And it's just like, you know,
you always forget to pay that bill, or you forget that there's that, you know,
tax thing going to happen or something like the agents, because it's just data,
the agents can set up routines, maybe they remind you on the schedule. So Grok bot could just give
you a routine and say like, Hey, once a week, give me my balance, that kind of stuff. Yeah,
people do really fun stuff, really creative stuff with it too. Like, you know, if I spend more
than x dollars on eating out this month, I want you to like tell me so that I can like
try and you know, keep to my budget, or like, you know, this is really fun. So if this then that
stuff, I've done some stuff where like, I if I don't work out, like enough times in the week,
yeah, I'd make I have link just go like make a donation to charity on my behalf, which is,
I don't know which one I prefer, like not working out or just it's fine to get the charity,
but like, so it's a really fun stuff you can kind of give yourself a moral gray area.
Yeah, is there a most unusual use case that you've seen someone you know, link for?
That's a good question. Well, we saw the we heard about the parking ticket line. Yeah.
I'm wondering if there are like, I guess, other more.
I mean, I've been I've been I've been sort of amazed at like, how quickly people will have
embraced putting like pretty, pretty meaningful purchases through like grokbot and others like
flight bookings, you know, things that like, if you'd asked me, you know, a few months ago,
I would have been like, yeah, people are going to be pretty hesitant with that. But like,
just seeing how great the tools are, like the approval steps inside like grokbot and things,
just like how well the agent can use browsers and just like, get the right answer. I think
people have like, I've been amazed people are just like, happily booking flights travel,
like really important things. Yeah, actually, now that they were talking about I feel like I
saw this on x, that someone use bling to actually pre order a Tesla. Yeah. Oh, wow. Yeah,
that was such a cool use case. Yeah, that's really cool. Oh, man. Yeah, well, I guess there's
a ton of cool stuff we could buy. I just tried this backstage. I think I realized that I think
my past key might not be set up on this computer yet, or like not in the profile that I've set up.
But if we want to quickly show my screen, I think it's pretty cool. Like I just pulled up if
we could raise if we could link donate $1 to Stripe climate, we can just try this again,
actually cancel that. Buy some shoes from Nike. In fact, as a small fun fact, these shoes I'm
wearing. Oh, yeah, I bought with grokbot. No way. No way. Because on our production team. Yeah.
Did you want to make a quick cameo? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. That shoe was also bought by grokbot.
Love it. I just took a picture of my shoe and said grokbot find me a new pair of these
in size 12, please. Thank you. That's that's Yeah, if we had this set up for that. Oh,
that would be so cool. I did almost that I was like, I just want to, like, have stuff buy things.
I need some new shoes. I was like, whatever popular men's shoes are size 12. Go buy them
you pick. Yeah, I don't care. The box arrived like three days later at my house. And I was like,
I don't even think I even know what these shoes are. But like, I've loved them. So yeah,
that's awesome. I feel like there's a really fun product to be built here. Maybe if like,
surprise me with a purchase every week. And like, hey, you got 100 bucks, like, get your agents to
buy you gifts. Maybe there's some really cool stuff there. Well, one of my co workers actually
we're just talking earlier, he's put all of his family's birthdays in. Yeah, just like hey, I've
like, you know, my siblings, my parents, whatever, two weeks before their birthdays, I want you to
just like, suggest some gifts for me and then just go buy them. And it's just like, up comes
a few options, preferences, like great link. Go buy it. Yeah. And I feel like it's just
so interesting when you think about just like, so much of what we do, we buy is on the internet,
like, let's say I want to send a card or send a package, and just being able to have a really
easy way to do that, I think is really, really great. And, you know, just working on the GrokBot
team, we've also heard a ton of great feedback on how, you know, how nice it is just to be able
to buy things from the bot, like this bot is managing your life, it's managing your finances,
it's managing, you know, your tasks, your emails, and just like connecting that payments piece to
it, I think is really awesome. So one, one really fun use case, I just I just remember
there's a company, it's called postal form. Okay. And it's basically a way that agents can send
physical mail. Okay. And so I've had, you know, bots in the past, like, they will make like a dad
joke for my daughter, they'll like write out a joke, turn it to a PDF, like pay the dollar in
postage, and like, my kids just get random mail each day, which is like a letter from me, you
know, so like, I have some really fun stuff. That's really, really fun. We had a few days
earlier, a creator on the on the stream, who basically has built all of these really cool
grok bot physical in person use cases, and has built a daily newsletter where she wakes up,
well, she doesn't really do this, but she's a printer in a room every morning, she gets a
physical newspaper. Yeah, just really incredible. Just like taking agents, making them do something
for you in the real world, which is which is super cool. So in my house, I have a sort of 32
inch, you know, display on the wall. Yeah. I've previously just had to like write some custom
codes to like have it display some for each day. And I'm now when I get home from from this,
I'm going to have like, my bots just basically like, whatever they want to put on my wall,
they can just put up there, you know, reminders, jokes, news of the day, something. Yeah,
I love it. It's gonna be great. I'll put one next time I do it.
Tell them the surprise. Yeah, please do. Yeah, we love to see it. And actually, you know,
I forgot we didn't get a chance to ask you this yet. But I think, you know, as our last question,
what are some of your favorite grok bot use cases? What does your grok bot team look like?
What are you offloading to bot or using a bot? Obviously, you're buying stuff.
Yep.
Makes sense for the link person to be buying stuff. But aside from aside from buying things.
I have a couple of categories. So I have a bunch of personal stuff. So I have a shopper bot that does
like, literally, I'm just like, I need shoes, I need t shirts, just like go do that. I hate
shopping. So it does that for me. I have the finance one. So I have it just like,
kind of keeping an eye on my finances. Am I spending right where I want to spend there?
I have a special one for the anniversary weekend. I'm just like having it trying to figure out the
anniversary for me. And then just kind of spin them up as I'm thinking of like personal projects.
Like I love just like, like you guys are just building stuff. So like, I've got one that's
building a game in 3GS, just like kind of like how do you make an infinite scrollable world that
you can kind of move around in. I had this idea actually last night that I have one working on,
which is like, I want a mobile app, where it's like a, it's an AI agent, but it only does
find date night spots. So basically, I want it to be able to go off on the internet,
find all the like recommendations of like cool restaurants and stuff I don't know about.
And just like every day, just give me a feed of like, this week's date night, you should do
this restaurant. So yeah, I've got one going on that. It's kind of so like, I find it just so
easy to be able to kind of like think of a task in life or like a thing and then be like,
okay, I'll just spin up a bot to go. Like, be good at doing that thing that I keep having to
do over and over again. Yeah, definitely. It's so freeing to just like, offload a task through
GrokBot, right? And you don't have to think about it anyway. Yeah, definitely. I think we've heard
this week too, sort of, you know, the best way to get started with GrokBot, think of something
you're doing that you don't want to do or that you want to do faster or that you want to do
better and just ask GrokBot. It turns out these bots can do quite a bit. So with that, Dan,
thanks so much for joining us. Thanks for being a GrokBot user. We're excited to maybe see some
of these bots.
And if you need someone to publish that 3JS game that you just described,
I might know a game studio.
We might have a game studio.
Yeah, a special model.
Yeah, awesome. Call us.
All right, well, that was Dan.
And his Twitter, or sorry, xHandle is up on the screen.
So Dan Hill Tech, it looks like, if you want to follow him.
Yep.
And we are going to now cut to our main stage,
back to our main stage here, right next to Dreamforce,
where Josh Kim is going to walk us through Grok Bot for marketing.
So we'll cut over to Josh, learn about Grok Bot for marketing,
and then we'll come back on for more build time.
Thanks so much.
All right.
Hello, hello.
Hi, everyone.
My name is Josh Kim, and I am so thankful for all of you for joining us here.
And I'm excited to share how we on the SpaceX AI team use Grok Bot for marketing.
Here's our run of show for today.
I'll be sharing what Grok Bot is, how we use it internally to market and grow the products,
and most importantly, how you all can start using Grok Bot within your teams.
Let's jump in.
So let's start with the context.
The way we all started using AI was pretty simple.
Many of you may still be using AI today, just like this.
And I certainly was in this camp before I started on the SpaceX AI team.
The typical pattern is that you have one or two AI chat bots
that you really use and leverage as your thought partner,
meaning you chat with them, you ask questions, you spar on strategy,
maybe you edit copy, but they're really there as your thought partner
and not a doing partner.
As AI has started advancing, there's been this rise of generalized
and specialized agents that can start to do tasks with you.
We refer to these internally as co-pilots,
because while they can get those tasks done with you,
they still typically require you to babysit them, push them along,
particularly for those complex tasks,
rather than truly being able to delegate your work.
And that's the reason why we're so excited about Grok Bot.
With Grok Bot, marketing teams can now actually start
to automate away true pieces of their work.
You can think of Grok Bot as always on asynchronous AI teammates
that actually do and finish the work on your behalf.
And most importantly, they'll do it the way that you do it.
And today, I'm excited to demo how on the SpaceX AI marketing team,
we not only use bots to automate jobs and tasks,
but we actually use them to staff up functions
and create teams of bots to actually do the work for you.
But first, let's do a quick intro of the product.
For those of you who haven't tried it out yet, this is Grok Bot.
And now some of you may be wondering,
how is Grok Bot different from all the other AI tools
and chat bots that I might use today?
What's different about Grok Bot is that rather than working
with one agent or one chat with multi-threaded conversations,
you create individual bots for each job.
And what that means is that you think of one bot
to be a singular teammate that you then delegate away
a single task or a set of related tasks.
What this also means is that you can actually message your bots
and talk to them just like you would Slack
or message someone on Teams.
And to take this up further, bots can start to talk to each other
and actually collaborate with each other within group chats as well.
And as you continue to work with your bots,
they'll learn how you work, they'll learn your preferences,
they'll learn your memory, and they'll get smarter and smarter
and get closer to the way that you actually do the job yourself.
So, similar to someone on your team
or someone that you collaborate with,
the more feedback you give and the more you invest in your bots,
the more they'll be able to do for you in the long term.
And what makes bot especially unique
is that while it can hook up to all the MCPs and APIs
that you're currently using today,
it also has its own computer.
And that's a bit of a novel paradigm shift
from how you might be using other AI tools today.
And what it simply means is that because it has access
to its own browser and its own computer,
so long as you give it access to tools that you use,
it can actually use those tools just like you would.
So, what does this all mean for marketers?
If we talk about how it can use tools just like you,
that means that your bot,
you can teach it specific ways that you like to optimize
your bidding strategy in ad platforms,
or the nuances and how you put together a campaign brief,
or maybe just how you like to manage your computer.
But ultimately, what's really unique and valuable about bot
is that it becomes customized and flexible
to the way that you work.
And with bot, you'll also find that you're no longer
having to babysit and push along
and really remind the bot to keep working.
And rather, Grokbot is extremely ambitious
and it's also very proactive.
And so now you'll be working with a team of bots
that actually want and will finish the work for you.
And that's quite different from other tools
you might be using.
Because bot is hosted in the cloud,
that also means that they're running 24-7,
no more keeping your laptop open
or needing a Mac mini setup.
And for marketers, that means if you have reporting
or metrics that you're looking at on a regular basis,
you can trust that Grokbot will be able
to pull those down for you.
And the best of all, as you might have noticed,
it's really simple to use.
This UI is as familiar and intuitive as iMessage,
which really lowers the barrier to entry
for any marketer, no matter what their specialization is,
to weave agents into their daily workflows.
Okay, so let's actually dive into what we're going to do today
during the demo.
What we're going to do together
is actually launch a marketing campaign from scratch,
from end to end.
Meaning we're going to start from the first task
that we typically take on,
which is market research analysis.
We're going to go all the way through
to ideating, embedding on positioning,
updating a landing page,
starting to build and monitor ad campaigns,
draw that analysis,
and then actually end with automation.
Now, this is a lot of work.
There's a lot of things that happen behind the scenes.
For all of us in the room, as marketers,
you know that this slide might look simple,
but it actually spans across many different teams,
functions, disciplines within a typical marketing org.
Meaning the person who conducts market research
is having to work with a product marketer
to identify about the positioning,
who then has to pass off a task to the web team,
and so on and so forth.
And for anyone who's done marketing before,
that context management,
the coordination, the orchestration of a campaign like this,
that's truly where the craft of the work happens
because it's the crux of our job.
So today, I'm going to introduce you
to my marketing team of bots.
And I would be remiss to say that I built all these.
I was crowdsourcing these across the entire SpaceX AI team,
which is a feature I'll talk about.
But I'm excited to show you how you can
orchestrate an entire campaign build
across the entire flow.
So you can say hi to our market researcher,
our product marketer,
our website ops, performance marketer, marketing analyst,
and lastly, our project manager.
So with that, let's dive into our demo.
Now, for the sake of our demo,
we have launched a brand new product,
and it is called Xair.
So this is an airline product
that we built as something that we can use
to build a net new campaign for.
And you'll see that this landing page is set up.
It's our home page.
People can do some airline route searches,
look for fares, and then we have some positioning
and value propositions currently in place.
So I'm going to navigate to my Grokbot instance.
And just to walk through what you see on the screen,
on the left side, sidebar, that's where the bots live.
I've pinned them to the top,
similar to what you might do in iMessage.
And I'll be flipping through each bot,
and I'll explain what I'm doing as I'm going through it.
But let's get started with the market research bot.
So what I'll say first is, hey, market researcher,
what I'd like you to do is study the Xair website,
get a deeper understanding of what the product is,
what market we're operating in.
And now I want you to go do a competitive analysis,
identify and deeply understand our competitors,
look at their marketing websites,
understand their positioning,
and then importantly,
identify the gaps and opportunities that we have
to actually strategically competitively position
against them within our marketing strategy.
So just dictate our prompts.
I'm going to set this off.
Now the market researcher bot is actually going to go
and scrape the website.
It's going to understand the product.
And then it's actually going to go find the competitors,
their landing pages,
and start performing this analysis.
So while that's running,
let me just do a quick walkthrough
of the additional bots that we have.
We have our product marketer bot, website ops,
performance marketer, marketing analyst,
and our project manager.
And importantly,
what I'm about to show is that as this works,
you can actually kick off jobs asynchronously,
meaning you might have one bot that you work with
as your main point of contact,
but you can actually kick off work in parallel
across a team of bots.
And that means that orchestration is happening
in the background because the product is always on.
So market researcher is saying
it's pulled xair.
The competitive asset is being identified.
It's going to show us a screenshot first of the website
and then go through gaps in positioning.
Great.
So it has its first output of an analysis.
It's talking about the product.
It's talking about the market.
It has identified key competitors.
These are all airlines that we're all familiar with.
I think most importantly,
it's identifying the gaps and where to lean in.
So similar to how you might work
with a market researcher, you ask,
hey, I'm launching this new feature.
I'm going to have this new exciting campaign launch.
Help me understand what's currently in market.
So we are optimizing for breaking through the noise
and actually landing and resonating
with our target audience.
So I think the most important note here
is these gaps around useful time,
day design, long hauls,
and then really leading every message with useful time,
which is something I think is resonating,
at least with me.
And it's also shown me that it's pulled up the website,
and this is actually a view of its browser
that it has access to and that it controls.
And it's showing me progress updates
of it working in the background
and being able to actually go to the website itself,
pull it out on a screenshot,
and show to me how it's progressing.
Now, market researcher has done one task,
and that's great.
What I could do is actually kick off another one,
but what I'm going to do instead
is actually go to the next spot,
and that's the product marketer.
And I'm going to have the product marketer
actually do a handoff of that work
that the researcher just did
and take that into their work.
Okay, product marketer, what I'd like you to do
is now go to the market researcher bot,
do a handoff of the analysis that just performed,
and I want you to draw up a draft of a positioning brief
where you identify how we should go to market,
what our one-liners are,
our positioning and packaging,
some value statements,
and then also show me some examples
of how this should come to life
across two or three different marketing services.
So as this is running,
what you'll see is in the chat,
the product marketer bot
is starting to kick off this work.
I told it to actually go and speak to
the market researcher
and actually grab that context and information.
As it's working,
you'll see there's a visual indicators,
it's doing things,
it's running in the background,
and then it'll actually show you,
hey, I exchanged a few messages
with the market researcher bot,
and that's showing that
they're starting to collaborate,
and that's something that
you can tell it to do in the beginning,
but over time,
it gets smarter and smarter and smarter,
and it will actually do it proactively,
meaning you have to be less involved
in doing the orchestration
of context and knowledge between your bots,
and rather,
they actually start to work
with each other organically.
So it's telling me
it's grabbed the market researcher analysis,
it's drafting the positioning brief,
it's created a Google Doc
where it's actually starting
to draft that position of brief,
which we'll jump into,
and inside, it's telling me
what exactly it did.
So let's bring this up,
and if we go through this,
this is looking like a solid first draft.
I think what I will do
is start to read through this,
it has a research handoff
that it got from the market researcher,
is identify the target audience,
long-haul travelers
who want useful time back,
I'm going to leave a comment and say,
this is great,
lean into this in our messaging.
It's talking about positioning and packaging,
and how we should be thinking
about our marketing strategy
and the way we go out with messaging,
and it's also left some notes
on how to go to market,
some additional one-liners
by different types
and angles to lean into,
and then some value statements
and examples of how it shows up.
So there's a paid landing page here
that is drafted.
I think what we'll do for our campaign
is actually take this page,
shove it up into the website,
launch the landing page,
and actually start directing
and building an ads campaign
to do a messaging test
to see what's landing the most
and what's resonating.
So I'm going to close this,
and what I'm actually going to do
is tell it,
hey, product marketer,
I've just left some comments
inside of the Google Doc.
What I want you to do now
is go through the Google Doc,
take the comments and the feedback,
incorporate it into an updated draft,
and while you're at it,
I also want you to build out
a full outline of the landing page,
and then I also want you
to ideate and draft
some Google search campaigns
to do variant testing
between the copy angles
that you drafted.
Now again,
this is all happening
within one bot right now,
but what it's doing
is flipping it back and forth
between market researcher bots
to make sure
that it has the right context.
It's going into the Google Docs
which I've connected through the MCP
to be able to actually
look at the comments,
look at the feedback,
and incorporate into a new draft.
So it's telling me,
okay, I'm reading your comments now,
I'm going to update the brief,
expand the landing page outline,
and then start drafting
search ad variants
inside the sheet,
which is great
because that's typically
how performance marketers work.
Now, while this is happening,
it's redrafting the file,
I'm actually going to flip over
to my performance marketer.
I'm going to say,
hey, performance marketer,
I would like you
to start creating a shell campaign
inside of Google Ads,
and what I want you to do
is build it
so that it's optimizing for clicks
because we're going to do
some copy and messaging testing
that's being drafted
by the product marketer right now.
So before this demo,
I actually hooked up
this bot
into our Google Ads account.
What's happening
is it now has access to it,
and when I kick this off,
it'll actually go into it
and you'll be able to see
because I'll show screenshots
of how it's starting that build.
And it'll be able to actually
do the clicks for me
and start the shell campaign
that can start trafficking
that copy into.
So let's flip back
to product marketer.
There's an updated brief.
We can open it.
Comments are resolved.
Looks like it's in a good state.
It has a fuller landing page outline
that we can implement.
It also has more built-out
campaign variants,
which I believe are also
inside the sheet
where it has variant name,
hypothesis, ad group name, etc.,
as well as a URL.
And then it's also built
some additional copy variants here.
So all this is happening in background.
I've kicked off two
or three jobs in parallel,
but the best part
is that they're all sharing
contacts with each other
while not tripping over themselves
to get their work done.
Okay, this is feeling pretty good.
What I'm going to do now
is I'm going to go to website ops
and I'm going to tell them,
okay, so landing page outline
is drafted.
What I want you to do now
is take the landing page
from the latest brief
that the product marketer just drafted
and spin up a PR
to actually push that
as a new landing page
into the website
and send me screenshots
as you're working
so I can keep monitoring your progress.
On the back end, again,
this bot is hooked up into our repo.
It has access, right access
to our landing page
and our marketing site.
So it's not able to actually
leverage what's under the hood
is cursor to be able
to go write the code,
look at the copy,
get the handoff
from the product marketer
and actually ship a new landing page
to the marketing site.
So it's going to pull down
the latest product marketer brief.
It's going to open the PR.
It's also going to show me
progress screenshots as it works.
Meanwhile, if we go back
to performance marketer,
it's successfully gone
and found the copy
that was drafted.
It has shown me some screenshots
of it actually starting to build
the campaign
inside of the platform,
and we'll let this keep running
as we finish up the landing page.
Okay, so you can see how
it's working through.
It is going to take a landing page.
It's going to update it
with the latest full
paid landing page outline
that was passed off
in the product marketer,
and we'll actually be able
to ship this
and ship it to production
and see the updates come to life.
Okay, so while this is running,
I would like to show
a feature that I think
is really special.
It's quite unique from the way
that you might be using
other AI agents now,
which is our sharing feature.
So something really unique
about GrokBot is that
while you can create
these really robust,
powerful bots within your workflow
that are customized
the way you work,
you can continue to feed
a context and memory
and build routines.
You can also turn those
into templates,
and this is where
I'll show you.
You share as a template.
You're prompting it to say,
hey, I want you to create
a template of yourself
that I can then share
with someone else.
And the implications of that
are pretty powerful
because that means you can
not only take a snapshot
of your bot in time
and turn that into
a duplicatable
bot and agent
that you can share
with your team,
but also people externally.
And what that means
is for the receiver,
they then have access
to literally the way you work.
Because you've injected
all this context,
your expertise,
your specialization
directly into the spot,
and they can easily take it,
copy and paste it
directly into their GrokBot instance
and then start using it
exactly the way you would.
All right, so
looks like it is working
on getting this page up.
It's still writing the page
in the PR,
and it'll show me
when the preview's up.
So, while that's working,
what we've done so far,
just as a quick recap,
we started with the market researcher.
We asked it to do an audit
of our product page,
understand the product,
identify competitors,
and then give us strategic guidance
on the gaps and opportunities.
That was passed off
to the product marketer
to then draft up a positioning brief,
which it did in Google Docs.
I was then able to go
into that document,
leave comments and feedback,
and then go back to the bot
and say, hey, fix this
the same way that you might
give feedback to someone on your team
when they're drafting a document.
It's done that rev,
and come back and said,
great, I did that.
I also created an outline
for a paid landing page,
and I'm also drafted this copy
that you can then traffic into your ads.
That outline is now being worked on
by the website ops,
which I'll give it.
It's currently working through this,
and that is going to be turned
into a landing page update
that'll push up
and we'll be able to host
on the main site.
Performance marketer has started
to build the campaigns,
built the shell,
and that copy is being fed into
the way that the campaign
will be structured
so that we're getting
that message and test live.
And as this is running,
rather than needing to actually
push the campaign live here,
because that would require,
obviously,
some additional guidance
on spending the budget
and hooking up a credit card,
I've actually already launched
a campaign this week.
And so what I'm going to do
is actually tell my marketing analyst,
hey, you're already hooked up
to my Google Ads account.
I want you to actually pull down
that data and give me insight
and analysis into how
the test performed.
Hey, marketing analyst,
what I want you to do now
is go into Google Ads.
I want you to pull down
the data from our last experiment
on messaging, analyze it,
tell me the TLDR of the insights,
and then give me recommendations
on how we should incorporate it
into our marketing strategy
as well as update
the other assets that you've seen.
Okay, so what this is doing now,
it's actually going into
the Google Ads platform.
It has access to that through the API.
It's going to pull down the information,
pull down the data,
and it'll be able to structure
it into an analysis
that's all going to be living
within this chat here.
So it gives me the TLDR.
It's pulled this copy test
down from the Google Ads.
It has a clear winner
that's analyzed across
the different variants of brand,
customer promise, hours in between,
cheap that cost a day, et cetera.
It has key metrics,
spend, CTR, CVR, et cetera,
all the things that we care about.
I think most importantly,
what it's done is
it's actually made recommendations.
And this is obviously where
there's some debate of how much
liberty do you give your agent
to actually make those decisions for you.
But I think in this case,
it's making recommendations
that can then intake,
discuss with the team,
but also guide it
to actually make decisions
on my behalf.
But it's made that entire process
smooth and without
any dependencies
that you might otherwise have
in a traditional org.
Okay, so now we've finally
gone through every single piece.
Research, positioning, landing page,
which I will nudge one more time.
Push the page to prod.
Building the campaign inside a bot
that has access into your account
from the Grokbot instance.
We've run the analysis
and it's pulled that down.
And you might have noticed
that during this entire demo,
I have to be the one
actually orchestrating.
And to go back to my earlier point,
that's really where the tax is, right?
It's a context switching.
It's having to know the players,
understand who's good at what
and sort of like trafficking
and managing that entire process
across the entire workflow.
And that is actually something else
that you can dedicate
or delegate to Grokbot.
So now with my next and final bot,
which is the project manager,
what I'm going to tell it is to do
is actually study
the entire orchestration flow
that we just went through
and then automate it
so that I don't have to be managing
the context, information,
and communication
between all the different bots
all the time.
Hey, project manager,
I want you to now study
and talk to each of the bots
in my team
and understand what each of their roles is
in bringing a campaign to life.
I want you to also look
at our conversations
and look at where I had to interject
or give guidance
or give feedback
and weave that into the way
that you work with them.
And I want you to also now
kick this off
and automate completely
with three new campaigns.
Send me screenshots
and progress updates
that can stay in the loop.
And most importantly,
I want you to now be
my point of contact,
meaning I don't want to talk
to any other bots.
I only want to talk to you
to save myself
the context switching.
So I've now delegated away
the entire process
of a campaign build.
And throughout that identified,
okay, there's like tax
and additional work needed
to actually make a campaign happen
from start to end.
And the final piece
is actually taking another step back
and saying,
I'm just going to have RockBot do that
and play the role
of project manager,
coordinator, handoffs,
sharing the context,
pushing the team along.
And I think most importantly,
what's most valuable
is the fact that
you no longer have to contact switch
and be bombarded
with five different messages
from different individuals
or bots on your team.
And that gives you the clarity
to be able to zoom back out
and really start to direct
and direct your energy and time
towards where the most leverage is.
So you'll be able to see
it's saying that it's the only...
This bot is now the only point
of contact here.
It's starting the five specialists
and it's going to create
and kick off three net new campaigns
that it'll then show me screenshots of.
So it's identified these are campaigns.
We're going to do research.
Positioning, landing page build,
et cetera.
That's all queued up.
And it will continue to keep me
in the loop
so that I can continue to monitor
but I don't have to be directly involved
in every step of the process.
All right.
And finally, we have websites
that we built up and running.
It's shown that it's actually
pushed it to prod.
And if I ask it,
give me the URL,
it'll also give me the URL
that we can open C.
And so this is the URL
that we drafted,
went through positioning, et cetera,
and actually pushed up to prod
all from the one place
where all the work is happening,
the Grokbot workspace.
Okay.
And that's it.
That's our demo.
So just to wrap that up,
what have we learned
by going through an entire campaign build
from start to end?
The first point is,
what's really important
when you're starting off with Grokbot
is to ensure
that you're scoping your bots properly.
And the way that I like
to think about this,
is that when you identify a bot
or a job that needs to be done,
it's almost like crafting
a job description,
meaning you're identifying
a new teammate
that you need help from.
You understand the swim lanes
and roles and responsibilities,
and you're ensuring
that it's scoped tightly
to ensure that they are specialized
and they're able to get
that specific piece of work done
because that's the way
you squeeze the most efficiency
out of your team of bots.
Second, you want to trust your bots.
As you might have seen,
these teammates are ambitious.
They're proactive.
They're hungry.
They want to do your work.
And that starts with giving them
the access they need,
meaning one of the first steps
you might take is hooking them up
into your Slack instance,
your email,
and actually maybe asking it like,
hey, go study all the context,
all the messages,
all of my organizational history,
and tell me what you can do for me
and take a job off my plate.
But I think if you do that,
you give them the access,
you throw ambitious tasks against them,
you'll be surprised
by what they're capable of.
And finally, I've said this over and over,
but you want to invest in your bots.
They really get better
and better over time.
You know, the point of collaboration
between bot to bot
is something that gets more organic,
especially as you prompt it.
But they also improve steadily
as you start to feed it
more feedback, more context,
more memory,
similar to how you might work
or manage a teammate
where the more feedback you give them,
the more time you invest into them,
the more the compound and value
and be able to take more
and more off your plate.
Lastly, here's a plug. This QR code goes to our bot marketplace. And the
marketplace is actually where we take the very best bot templates, like the ones
that I shared, and host them, meaning you might be able to create your own bots and
prompt them and build up, you know, really rich context and memory, but you can also
just copy others. And that's what I did, is when building out this demo, I
crowdsourced across the entire team. I said, hey, who has the best positioning
bot, who has the best ads bot, etc. And you can find all of those on our
marketplace. So I encourage you to go here and be able to copy them down. And with
that, that's it for me. Thank you so much for your time. And I believe we have
some time for questions. Thank you. I'm just curious, the marketing bots that they
were showing, are those available in the marketplace? I was like looking on
there, I didn't see them. I was refining them, but they will be. Yeah. So I
basically went to the marketplace, and I like scraped up all the different bots
that sort of like amount got consolidated into these, along with some internal ones.
But we'll push them into the marketplace. They'll be available. John, thanks for the
great presentation. So my question is like, are there any areas that you
would, you know, not allow them to do it autonomously? Because I do find myself
sort of waking up and approving the task. So it does feels like there is
still a lot of tasks that are human in the loop. So what would you advise? Would
you advise me to like completely automate those tasks and just let it run
by itself? Or yeah, where are the limitations and constraints when it comes
to human loop? Yeah, yeah. Great question. And it's something that's come up in a
lot of customer conversations. I think what I lean back on here is really
like the analogy of treating a bot like a teammate. And so similar to how
you might, you know, onboard, you know, someone that's just started their
personal, their professional career, you're not going to give them the
keys, the kingdom, like immediately, you're going to give them quick
context, you're going to train them up on board them. Obviously, that
happens much faster with the rate at which these improve. But I'd start
gradually, you know, you want to give them a simple task, maybe you hook
them up to one or two tools where they'll get the most context quickly,
you want to see that they're actually delivering value, and they're
getting better and better over time. And I think what you'll see as is
as you continue to prompt it, give it feedback, sort of curate it to
the way that you work and what you care about, it'll be able to take
more of those tasks off your plate and be truly automated. There's also
some additional features and settings where you can actually like
prompted to just be like, hey, you asked me for permission to do these
things just like always allow if you wanted to like go more, be more
liberal with that. But I think a good like end state is we have
engineers that work at SpaceX AI that have entire like armies of
bots that are working. And they're actually pushing code to prod. And
so I think obviously, like, the way you get there is by creating
really great, rich, prompting and memory and context. But you got
to start small. And so I'd start with something simple, low
risk, and then go gradual from there.
Hey, I'm wondering, what do you think is the biggest blocker for
marketers in using this technology?
Good question.
I think something really common that I see when I talk to new users
is they might come into the product, and they don't have a
clear understanding of like, what's actually capable, right? And
so that's why I spent a lot of the time in the front saying,
hey, this is different. Like, you kind of need to like shift
your mental model away from thinking it's just something
that's like a Google search or, you know, AI search or another
LLM, where you just ask questions and get answers back.
That's not the way this works. The way it works is you have to
trust it to actually like do things for you. Meaning
something that's really common in our team is you hook it up
into Slack, you know, you get bombarded with different
questions, maybe in Slack and DMs, emails, etc. And it is
like the first line of defense, it becomes your triage of
like, hey, I'm receiving this, I'm going to triage it message
Josh when something's important or urgent, but
actually message back to the person that's responding to you.
And so I think to answer your question directly, it
won't be valuable if you come into it and just treat it as
like another LLM. It'll be extremely valuable. If you
come into it and say, okay, you can do things for me, I'm
going to test it. I'm going to throw some tasks at you,
I'm going to give you some context and actually see what
you're capable of. Thanks.
I was wondering that when you use Grokbot, do you
always assign it roles like company roles or do you also
group it by like initiatives or other things that you're
working on? Yeah, good question. You can do
initiatives. I think the way that I would think about
it is like, initiatives always have like a start and
stop, right? It's sort of like a campaign. These are
more always on. So you want to treat them more like,
okay, this is now like an individual or teammate
that's going to continue to get better and better
over time. And if I would think about the
initiative level versus the individual level, there are
groups of individuals that work on an initiative and
you want to be able to identify like the swim lanes
of each of those individuals and you can group
them together into chats where they then work on
projects together. And so similar to like what I
had, you could then take those and say like, hey,
you are now a Tiger team. You work on improving,
you know, the positioning of our website and the
initiative you all work on in a group chat is,
you know, website conversion maybe. So that's
sort of how I think about the mental model of
like initiative versus actual role.
Hi. Is it me? Oh, it's me. Okay, good. Hi. I've
got an agent on Open Claw and one of the things
I love about her, her name is Ariel by the way,
is that she's got her own personality and she
can be snarky and fun and consistent across the
board. Now I know Grok can be snarky because
I've tested that. How do we make Grokbot
somehow fun and snarky and a consistent
personality over time? Is there a way for that?
Yeah. Yeah. Good question. So something fun
that you can do actually is what was the name
of the agent? Ariel. Ariel. Hey, I want you to
update the avatars and animate them based on
one word. Ariel. It's spelled A-I-R-E-A-L.
A-R-A-I-R-E-A-L. Cool. So something really
easy you can do is actually have it go and
update the avatars. Like obviously that's not
personality and I'll get to that. But if you
talk about customization and personalization,
like here's a really easy way to make the
product feel like yours, similar to the way
that you refer to this agent on Open Claw
is like, this is mine. I've curated it. I've
personalized it. The other way is that each
bot has its own context and memory, meaning
you could easily tell the project manager,
like, I want you to talk to me as if, you
know, you're Harry Potter and like you need to
call me a wizard every time you talk to me,
you know. So all that customization is
possible. And so just the way, like exactly
the way that you've built this agent for
yourself, you could easily also point a
GrokBot at your agent and say, go replicate
that for me and pull it down and then turn
into something that looks here. And do you
have a way that they can communicate
together? So Open Claw and GrokBot somehow?
Not natively right now, but we do have
import templates, which we can talk about
afterwards. Yeah, one final question. Can
you get GrokBot on the Tesla soon, please?
We'll see.
Thank you for the presentation. Yeah. Is
there a way to connect a GrokBot to the
Grok CLI and the information that we
have in the Grok website, or is just
everything independently?
Yeah, I haven't done that myself. But,
wait, sorry, the Grok build CLI?
Yes.
Yes. Yeah. Yeah. So just the way that I
was doing the landing page build, like
that's actually hooked up a cursor on
the back end. Okay. And so it's using
Cloud agents to actually kick off the
job and actually push the PR. So you can
do the same thing with any other
coding tool they use.
Okay, so it means that all the
developments that I have done with the
Grok CLI will be part of the context in
GrokBot. Yeah, that's cool.
Yeah, exactly. So you don't have to
like rebuild that context. You can just
say like, hey, GrokBot pointed at my
existing work and be able to like,
basically treat it as a harness for your
work there.
So it is possible to connect the
GrokBot directly there via their own
computer to the Grok CLI. So that,
yeah, okay, that's cool.
Yeah, the next question. One of the
main issues that I see, because I
work at a company in Germany, is the
rules and regulations that we have.
And one of the main issues that I
see for this product to get into the
market in the B2B business in Europe
is how do you ensure companies that
the alpha is not going out, or that
the information that they're putting
into GrokBot is not used for training?
Yeah, so we have data privacy modes
that you can opt in or out of to
ensure that you can choose whether
or not you want the data to be used
for training. But in terms of like
actual security, we do it on a case
by case basis. And so we have a
team, I believe they're in the
back, they can speak with and say
like, hey, like, I want to use
this, I use it personally, how do I
make sure that we're, you know,
standing by and within the
guidelines that my company has to
use it safely?
Okay, cool.
How do these feel? Are these
aerial? Is that okay?
Well, I just wanted to show you
that like you can create
personalization. Everyone has their
own way of doing this, like mine
were Machimaro theme for a while
I switched them over like a week
ago. But the best part is that you
can do it completely custom and
animate it to make it fun and
feel personalized to you.
Hello. Yeah, that's crazy. I
didn't know you could do stuff
with the avatars like that. So
that's pretty cool. But my
question, you said like when you
created new bots, you like did a
combination of a bunch of bots
together. I actually haven't
heard that like being done for
I want to know how did you do
that? Because normally I'd just
be like, find the best one on
marketplace and use that, right?
So just curious, like, yeah,
like, you know something? Yeah.
Yeah. So this is mostly a product
of me being lazy, or not
having much time. But what I
did, for example, I think for my
product positioning bot, I had
it do a few things. So I
obviously get it gave it it's
like an initial set of
prompting from me, just
dictated into it for like a
couple minutes on like, how I
want to think about it, I had
it pull down tone and voice
from the current existing
website. I then actually went
into the marketplace. And I
said, Hey, here, like two or
three bots that I like, based
off of what I'm seeing, I then
pointed it at those URLs and
said, like, go scrape up all
that context and memory and
actually replicate it into the
way that you work. So sort of
sort of like, you know, went
and absorbed all that, you
know, the work that had been
put into those templates and
fed it into itself. And the
last thing I did was, I
actually had it make a
connection to super me, if
you're familiar with it, it's
a marketplace of experts,
where like, you know, industry
experts on product
positioning, packaging are
like available there, we
actually have a plugin. And
I said, Great, in lieu of
doing like scale, qualitative
research, go and vet
everything you do with
experts on the marketplace.
And so it'll start speaking
directly to super me without
meaning to like go into a
website and like prompted and
set up an account and all
that. And so that's just like
a few different ways that I
sort of like took different
sources of data to make it
happen. Yeah. Okay, I think
that's my time. And for the
digital audience that's
joining us, we'll be going
back to the studio.
That was Josh Kim, doing
Grokbot for marketing. Hope
y'all have been enjoying the
day so far. We're joined by
a new guest who will
introduce in just a second.
Eric, welcome. Welcome to
the studio. Thank you so
much. Why don't we introduce
you now? Cool. Let's do
it. Hey, everyone. I'm Eric.
I'm on the SpaceX AI
team. I do a little bit of
everything. And today I'm
here to help out finish the
product and ship it. We're
thirsty. It's Thursday.
Yeah. This is the final
stretch, I think, too,
right? Yeah, we have a few
hours to get the last bit
of polish in. The last time
we saw you all, we were
working on implementing a
ton of new features. And I
think with Eric's help now
we're going to 5X our team's
velocity. So no, no
pressure, no pressure. For
those of you who are just
tuning in, we are towards the
tail end here of a three
day live stream where we're
building a new business over
72 hours. Our business is a
game studio and we launched
our first game this
morning called Thursday
Arena, Thursday Arena dot
com, where you can follow
us on X at Thursday Arena.
Those are our two official
sources. So just keep an
eye on those. Anything you
see that comes from other
counts, not us. We're just
at Thursday Arena and
Thursday Arena dot com.
Tons of really cool
improvements we've made to
the website and the game.
So we're going to walk
you through some of
those. We're going to
just work on and work on
adding some new features
and coding together and
probably do some of that in
the next few hours and
hopefully end up with a
really cool product. I
think that's going to
work on some ads and some
some revenue so we can
take all those lessons we
learn from the day and
kind of build it into
something and build it into
the product. So yeah, we
had a really fun fun week
so far. A lot of really
great guests that have
come onto the stream,
learned a lot about
marketing, great
businesses, the things
that businesses care about
obviously taking a little
bit about revenue. We
spent some time today on
growth and have a growth
playbook that we're
working on implementing. We
have a bunch of people
playing the game. And so
maybe just to see how
things are going, I'll
kick over to my screen. We
can get my screen up for a
second. So what we've been
doing today, and this is
something that I really
like doing just working
on products at SpaceX AI
is having a Grokbot whose
job it is to help keep an
eye on our launches. And
so we have our data bot
here. This is my data
scientist among the many,
many other bots we've
created over the course
of these streams. And
what I have my data
scientists doing here is
every 15 minutes or so
I'm getting a update of
how our launch is going.
So we're getting live
real time dashboards every
15 minutes connected to
our production data
stores. We have two sets
of data right now. We
have our Vercel
analytics, which are just
giving us stats on page
views and referral links.
And it looks like we
have well around 17,000
page views since we
turned on analytics about
midway through the day.
Yeah, not bad at all.
And we also have a ton
of great usage data. So
I thought I could spend
a few minutes walking
through that. So what do
you guys think we've
hit exactly 4,500
practices rounds or
practice games, close to
2000 X logins. We got to
get that number up, right?
I think we can hit 5,000
in the next few hours.
No way.
Yeah, I don't know. Maybe
with Eric's help.
Maybe with Eric's help.
Yeah, we'll pick
something together.
Yeah, okay.
Yeah, a ton of people
who will go through a
practice round about 8%
of our users who go
through our practice
round, then sign up and
sign in with X so they
can get onto our leader
board, which is great.
So you can see our
customer funnel here,
which is super cool
around, like I said, a
4,500 practice rounds,
total of close to 5,000
battles. And then here's
what our traffic has
looked like over the
course of the day. So a
really exciting bump
this morning to get a few
folks right when we
launched the product. So
thanks to everyone who
jumped in really early
on. We have feedback in
the app that is coming
into a Slack channel. And
we have agents looking at
those Slack channels,
humans looking at that
Slack channel, trying to
get all that feedback
incorporated into the
product as much as we
can. We have some really
cool data where it looks
like we're still seeing,
you know, every time we
come back on stream, I
think that's what these
peaks are over here.
Yeah, it's just like 1.30
looks, can we replicate
that now?
Yeah, right. How do we
bring back that 1.30
energy? That's what we
need. That's how we got
to end this. So bring
back the 1.30 energy or
the 1.45, 2 p.m.
energy. Oh yeah, we're
at what? Three. So
afternoon, afternoon
bump, hopefully. Yeah,
thanks for continuing to
sign in and keep the
game going. And this is
one of my favorites,
cumulative graphs. We
talked earlier about how
much we love cumulative
graphs because they
always go up to the
right. So yeah, the games
are growing. The page
views are growing. Wow,
looks like we're still
pretty 5050 mobile versus
web. That's pretty cool.
And yeah, some of the
most common websites
looks like people are
signing in, have folks
checking out the
sponsor page, a few
people checking out the
feedback page, which
has been great. Yeah, a
bunch of a bunch of
cool referrals. Most of
our traffic is coming
from X and X links. A
few people direct as well.
So eight, eight people
who found us from Bing.
So I don't know who you
are, who those eight
Bing people are. Shut
up, Bing. Thanks,
Bing. And then it looks
like a few people coming
in from the Android app
as well. So yeah, very,
very cool stats. You
know, earlier today, we
announced actually that we
just launched today, voice
mode for Grokbot. And so
if you haven't seen that
announcement yet, let's
see if I can pull it up
here. Oop, that's the
wrong one, x.com slash
bot. So yeah, Grokbot can
talk now. It has a voice.
It can, you know, talk
with you. And so we
thought actually, maybe
we kick off this by just
demoing the feature and
seeing if we can check
in on how things are
going. So production, do
we have a mic that we
can pull in? Grokbot's
voice needs to be heard.
So this is Blake. Sorry,
Blake is my founding
engineer that I've been
sending a bunch of
feature requests to. So
I'm going to see if
this voice chat works.
Hey, how's it going?
You've been watching a
bunch of PRs for me. Can
you give me a sense of
what of my PRs are open
and if they're blocked at
all? Two of yours are in
play. The reroll softlock
fix 269 is open with CI
green. That one's clear.
Can you merge that one?
220 is still sitting as
a draft with merge
conflicts. Nothing's
moved in since I last
checked. Okay. Hold the
conflict details or leave
it parked. Can you just
get an agent to fix 220
so we can fix those
merge conflicts? I think
that would be really
helpful. And then that
first PR you mentioned,
can you just go ahead
and merge that? On it.
Agent for the 220
conflicts and I'll land
269. Awesome. Cool. I'll
check in back with you in
a few minutes. Sounds
good. I'll have updates
on both by then. Catch
you then. Cool. Well,
that was easy. So just
huddle our bots. It's
like huddling a teammate,
I guess, and getting
them on the horn. That
was great. So, okay,
we'll get some PRs merge.
Maybe we can all try
and voice chat with our
guys a little bit here
and there. Yeah, that was
really cool. So really
fun way to work with
Crockbot. Obviously,
that's just launched
today. It's rolling out
over the next few days.
So if you're excited
to voice chat with your
agents, stay tuned for
that to make its way
to your account and a
shout out to the team at
SpaceX AI that got that
ready to go for us to
try out today. So thanks
guys. Around the horn.
What's everyone working
on? I'm continuing to
ship UI polish things
that I'm finding and
bugs. So we have a lot
of bugs being recorded
to Slack and I have my
bots, bot factory going
on just reproducing,
fixing, merging.
Awesome. Yeah, I've
been working on some ad
stuff. So we're getting
an ad marketplace spun
up. And in order to do
that, there's some like
blob storage for cell
integration work to be
done. So right now I'm
just working environment
variable and everybody
loves blobs. At least
on the Crockbot team.
Eric, you on noted.
Try to get up to speed
with the with the code
base and the product and
ever how everything
works. I think we've got
it going now. So I'm
going to focus on
polishing the like the
fighting experience and
making it look like I
needed realize like, you
know, card game and like
the animations and making
it flash in a way. We
desperately need help with
that. But yeah, let me
know whatever I should
work on. I'm here to
help. But yeah, looks
good so far. I'm excited
to see. I think you
should really ship that
thing where you can
actually pay to become
top of the leaderboard.
Okay. Yeah. Well, I
just like not pay to
play, but just pay to, I
don't know what you
call that cloud pay for
clout. Yeah. Pay for
clout is a great
automatic like posting
to Twitter as well. Oh
yeah. Speaking of posting
to Twitter. So I did work
on this. I'm going to see
if this works. Let me
just speed through a
battle here. We'll skip
a win. I think. Yep. We
added this new share
feature so you can
share your share your
post. It looks like it's
prompting the Mac OS
system that happens. So
that's going to show my
recent contacts. I'm not
going to show that on
stream, but there is a
share card. We'll get
that working and you
can now very soon share
your own wins or your
losses if you want. You
can share your losses too.
You know, nothing wrong
with defeat once in a
while. You can share
share on X or wherever
you'd like to post links
on the internet. So set
up for that. Nice.
Let's take a look at
the leaderboard. Okay.
I've dropped to 51st
place. We have about
we're still holding
strong at five diamond
players. So we have an
elo system here that's
giving everyone a player
rating based on how
they're doing. And it
looks like we have our
top three, the podium
here. A lot of folks
who've played over 40
games almost and a lot
were really good. So very
high win loss ratio on
these guys. Do you have
an OJ image for sharing
the link to the
leaderboard? I think that
I think the app is
generating one. Nice.
But yeah, actually, we
need to improve that. I
don't have anything
generating the leaderboard.
That would be really
cool. So I just made one
earlier. I tried this
before and this is what
I think should be
happening. If you guys
can see this in slack,
there should look
something like this, but
maybe we could come up
with it. Oh, you meant
the leaderboard. Sorry.
Yeah, it's pretty nice. We
can have like the top
three leaders on the
right side with their
names. I did something
similar before, but you
get like showing the top
10 or top five.
Currently, our OJ
image service uses
Takumi, which is one of
my favorite. It's like
it's similar to Satori
if you're familiar, but
it's written in rust.
Exactly like Satori.
Actually, it's great.
It's actually, I think
Takumi, I love this
open source library. Very
good. OJ image
generation service. How do
I spell it? T-A-K-U-M-I
and then type in OG
image after that. Takumi.
Yeah, it's actually if
you go back the second
link there is like the
lander. Yeah, so JSX
two images also look at
I mean Fuma Nama
getting a huge shout
out there Fuma docs,
another one of my
favorite open source
repositories. So yeah,
love it. Good folks.
I started Grokbot for
trying out new like
libraries and stuff
that you're finding.
Yeah. Did you find
these and like the
Grokbot like build
something? I've
actually been using
these for a while. So I
think I on all every
project I make it's like
I'm going to use Takumi
to generate the OG images
and they're almost
always dynamic. So yeah,
I've used it for a
bunch of stuff.
Nice. Awesome. Yeah, we
should try to hear and
see how it works. Guys,
I just made a bot called
Grind and the bot is
going to log in for me
on Thursday Arena and
play the game. So if
you see me climbing the
leaderboard, you know
why.
We've got to get so
much leaderboard spam.
Yeah, we've got to make
it like Grokbot
compatible so they can
actually play against
etc. So my bot,
like an NCP or
something. Exactly.
Exactly. Not the scope
creep, but you know,
cut a bunch of PRs
going here. So where's
the Kanban board?
That's the only piece
I'm missing. We don't
project manage, we
just ship to production.
Really? Yeah. Wow.
We had a Kanban board.
Nice.
I think it kind of
devolved. Yeah, let me
see if I can pull it up.
I'm looking for the
sticky sticky notes,
the Sharpies, you know,
I mean, that's part of
the fun of a startup.
You know, it's like,
it's just chaos.
It's chaos.
You just can't just
ship, break stuff and
ship and move really,
really fast.
Yeah, we've been we
told our our bots to
create a to-do list
tracker and turn out to
just be a very long
list here. A lot of
AI notes.
Not sure how helpful
this is at the moment.
But we we should have
it somewhere.
They're very diligent
about taking notes.
Our our bot.
There we go.
Oh, wow.
This we do have a
Kanban board.
It is very long.
I'm glad it's in the
Don Paul.
We got we got to fill
up the the up next.
Yeah, if you if you
have a Kanban board,
I guess good to have
everything and done.
Yeah, yeah.
True, true.
Cool. We got some bugs
that are being
picked up here.
Hopefully, too.
That's great.
Another leaderboard we
haven't shown is the
contributor graph.
Hmm, that's a good one.
Yeah, like who's got
the most commit?
It's 100% you.
Yeah, I have 157.
Wow.
Not bad, not bad.
How was our total PR
count right now?
I think we're at 433.
Wow.
Pull this up.
So is PR?
Yep.
From 1 to 73.
Yeah, we're going to
definitely clear 300, I
think.
Yeah, one bug that I'm
trying to try to fix
that a lot of people have
been reporting is you
keep getting matched with
AI players.
And that's a really
important one.
So I have my my bots
prioritizing that that fix.
Yeah, I saw the slack
channel for user
feedback, which is really
nice.
Did you see that from
there?
Yeah.
Awesome.
I have some bots that
are just watching that
slack channel and then
they're aggregating all
the feedback.
And I'm just automatically
reproducing and fixing
and verifying.
Nice.
How much of like how you
build Grokbot, how much
inspiration do you take
from that to like apply
to this?
A lot.
I think with like
building Grokbot, my
setup is like more
rigorous, I guess, here
because we're in the
interest of time, not
be that rigorous.
So I'm like merging
things a lot faster than
I would be.
But in the Grokbot
code base, for example,
I also spend a lot of time
actually reading the code.
For Thursday arena, I've
not read any code, to be
honest.
Yeah.
But I read the code and
I try to really deep
dive into the PRs and
look at like anti-patterns
that agents are writing.
And then I add the rules
to check, you know, like
one, the classic
example is like agents
just love leaving
comments.
Right.
And when you think about
like comments, why are
they bad?
But what I found was that
agents were using
comments as a way to just
justify some work around
or a hack, like a
band-aid.
And they never really
fix the root cause.
And I think over time,
you just end up with
these files that are
just full of band-aids
and it becomes very,
very brittle.
So I banned them in the
Grokbot code base.
Here I haven't.
Although potato mode
does come with some
skills.
There's a skill called
no comments.
And that spawns this
really fun agent called
the comments sicko
who like says,
yes, ha ha ha.
Yes.
And then goes off and
deletes a bunch of comments.
So I think we're
actually pretty good
with the no comments
in our code base.
But yeah, that's
kind of my work.
That's really interesting,
like how like by
removing the band-aids,
like you're forcing
them all not to get a
wound and like actually
do it right the first
time or like you're
going to punish it
in some way like or
reward it by like
doing the right thing.
Yeah, I haven't really
looked at a code here
yet, but I'm kind of
curious to see like
I don't know.
Big pile of slob.
I'm curious, I guess,
Eric, in your own
development,
what is your work
for like, do you use
gawk for coding much?
I do.
It's so interesting.
Like I thought about
this the other day,
like before I joined
cursor, I wrote this
article, like how I'm
using cursor and the
main piece was like
how I'm using tab
and like the
composer mode in the
old cursor and this is
like pre-agent and
like going from that
to agent and then like
abstracting all the
like the prompting
myself to now like
using rock part.
So like I started in
rock part all the time
and then I try to like
scope out the project
and like get all the
context and like align
on what we're going
to do and then I'll
just have it send a
bunch of cloud agents
to build a thing and
eventually like I might
want to look at the
code. So I pull it
locally and then I
open cursor and go
through go through it
all. See how it works.
And if I'm fine, I
just like go back to
rock part and just like
keep prompting from
there.
So it's like very much abstracted compared to what it used to be and like relying heavily on like
reproducing things and computer use and like just doing all the hard work and like ironing out all
the bugs before I'm taking a look at it so I don't really need to spend that much time to look at the
code and just like I only want to look at the code if it actually works the way I want. But it's nice.
It's I guess we're all like trial and erroring. I remember when Grok Bot came out I had like one bot
and then like all of a sudden oh I want this use case too so it's like you create another bot
and then you just like keep on going like that and that's eventually like how I discovered that
I built this project manager bot to like create separate rooms and channels for different projects
I have and like spawn ephemeral bots for the specific use case. Maybe it's like a researcher
or coder or whatever it might be and it's actually using a Kanban board which makes
it easy for me to go into Notion and I can see like the status on different tasks and different
projects and like usually when it's blocked it's because of a human somewhere and I can have like
the bots you know like check if we're unlocked or if there's anything else we can do like in the meantime.
That's awesome. If you want this bot that Eric just described it is in our marketplace you can
just go to this URL grab the bot hit import it'll bring your bring you a copy of it.
That should ask you to do some setup and it should be good to go.
You know it's cool every single one of the bots in Thursday Arena is actually built from that
marketplace so we probably there's your bot. Hey look at that. In game form.
It's uncommon too. Yeah yeah good role. Nice. Gives the front most friend plus two attack.
Not bad. I'll take it. How do I play with it? How do I actually use it? Do I need to buy it?
No so if you play a game basically you get like so you when you start you get this you're here
you're like building your deck and then you have a shop where you can buy cards and so then it's
like random randomly selected from our available cards then you build your deck by buying them.
So if you scroll up Roshan you'll notice the yellow button is now tokens. We call it tokens
now so you get 10 tokens each bot costs like three tokens for the common common ones and
basically that like like what Roshan did he just built his deck and then you move your your cards
around based on the effect they have and the stats they have and so you can sort of strategize
like for example this is super strong right because I would get this would turn into a three
seven at the beginning of combat yeah and then you have like office ops desk bot which whenever
it's hurt from the front I guess it restores one health which is really powerful so yeah maybe you
want to put that at the front but the strategy comes from yeah like picking the order you know
choosing the cards which cards you sell you know so get power ups like there's an apple that you
can buy yeah I believe I actually added a potato special I saw the potato yeah really good that
gives your that kind of powers up your bot and then you use your deck to fight fight around
and then we fix the AI issue that's great now I'm longer seeing that it's AI
excellent it's like one of the the most reported bugs okay so now I'm in round two so here okay
now you're getting the unlock cards you can get Eric's card though I love the shiny uh deal three
damage to the last living enemy you deal one damage to the last living enemy shout out Lenny
or Chinsky over there cool card I kind of like this three damage to the last living
enemies a lot if I start him in the back so I'm gonna get rid of this guy oh and you can drag them
into the slots that's so nice yeah I just added that that's a great feature and then you know I
can afford an apple right yeah I have seven tokens left so I'm gonna actually how much are these four
so if I sell this for the sell cost is one right yeah you get one back okay so if I sell this
I'll be at eight so I think I should do that I'm gonna sell this guy grab this swap these
oh that's cool I can sell now too and then I'm gonna get an apple plus one attack and plus one
health four six okay I like this lineup a lot one thing I think is good to kind of remind chat is that
like when we first launched third arena it was so bad it's not perfect now but it was really bad
the UI was horrible I think we sort of almost intentionally wanted to ship like well I didn't
I don't I don't think you want to ship bugs but we did want it to ship really fast and I think
the the cool thing about building a game studio I think is is the iteration loop so
setting up our factory with grothbot really helps us iterate fast and you know get to like a really
good game and then maybe we can take our learnings and build more games yeah in the future much
faster and much higher quality so I'm gonna win this one guys yeah yeah that's the cool part like
everything is like prompted which means we have all the transcripts of all the agents like human
prompts and agent responses and we have the game data so we could like theoretically just look at
all the prompts and like replicate this into like a game studio bot and that would like help us
create more games based on the learnings we've made like creating all the websites and the
brands and the product decisions what works what doesn't and the style of game yep oh yeah
wow you're ranking nice good climbing I'm climbing 39 although I think there might be a bug here
where it says four wins zero losses but then if I go into my bass games did you hard code that
what's that did you hard code like zero losses well I mean you can't lose it might be good to
use a voice mode to file that bug and fix it let's try let's try so I'm gonna go into grothbot
where's my engineer all right can we get the production mic again please we're going live
we're gonna huddle our bot thank you hey you there yes hey are you there did you mute your sound
we'll try it again I think we confused hey bake are you there here cupcake bug fixes sticking by
what's on your mind hey so I think I found a new bug on the leaderboard when I look at a player's
win loss numbers in the bottom right of their card it doesn't match what you see when you
click in so if you look at me on the leaderboard roshan underscore s roshan underscore s
when you click when you see the leaderboard it says four wins and zero losses but when you click into
my name it shows um actually one loss can you spin up a cloud agent using potato mode to investigate
and fix that issue also by the way can you can you tell us that's roshan underscore s
I don't know if you heard my colleague over here but could you also tell us a joke
sure a sequel query walks into a bar walks up to two tables and asks can I join you
oh that's terrible no more jokes from you we need to work on that one
that's how you know these bots are serious thank you teach um yeah okay so we got we got our voice
chats make and there you go and yeah we didn't show this before but you can actually dig in here and
see a transcript of um of the voice chat um joke was all right but call was a plus and
this actually goes back to our team so uh we'll see what they do with that one
okay fix it bugs got agents running all right my cheater bot is is uh grinding for me
okay we'll see if it's actually making a difference on the leaderboard
three loads of one point yeah I went at one point I'm doing really bad my rank is one three two two
out of 1800 oh that's rough yeah yeah not even I couldn't command that well it doesn't work
yeah I'm not even I'm not even on the front page so we have 1,819 players though that's pretty cool
I set it up so my cheater bot will actually learn from the game as it plays and uh we'll see how it
does maybe I can climb the leaderboard let's see we'll see what's your name for the for your bot
oh it's just my it's just my account oh yeah of course I could create an account for it but
I'm trying to make myself look good you know that's fair all right Matt you got to tell us
about this this ad bidding thing going on here yeah so this is I'm working on fixing some some errors
and actually simplifying this uh but you know for this is a business we have to monetize it somehow
so we're going to do that through ads because everybody loves ads we all need more ads in our
life um yeah exactly you know sometimes I'll just uh I'll open Spotify just to hear the ads oh
yeah like I don't even listen to music who hurt you that's a great question actually uh but uh
so we're gonna allow our users to buy ads uh we have like a bidding marketplace which is currently
broken so if you try to submit this nothing will happen but uh once I merge a PR that is
currently in flight you'll be able to bid ads uh on ads for the platform um where do you think
you will show that we can put them wherever you want haven't figured that out yet interesting
maybe like the ticker an ad ticker would be good uh and then also working on Eric's sort of like
pay to be at the top of the leaderboard idea nice all right I got another idea for you yeah what
if you can submit a prompt and you pay for that and that will like make its way into the product
so you can like purchase a picture yeah my mind automatically goes to like some sort of prompts
I'm already heavily moderating all user inputs to this so our feedback submissions
I think we can moderate that pretty easily so yeah I'm down for it one thing I was thinking
of when you mentioned the ticker is we have this ticker you could pay to be like a special like a
blue color yeah I like that now it's all kind of generic so we could add some visual pop there
that could be kind of fun I think this is actually one of my favorite features though is seeing the
ticker down here and just being able to to to see who's doing what yeah that's a good ad spot
yeah we could do that by ads in the ticker nice cnbc style yeah I should have this this pr to fix
the ads and in a second so you can walk me through the the phone number that's on the screen
yeah like how does that work so it uses an xai voice agent so I actually you know I hadn't played
around with this at all but it's very easy there's like a custom voice agent builder on the on xai
and so all I did was hook up a couple tools so like it can search the web technically but it's
more just feedback and then you slap on a bunch of guardrails like hey if the person starts trying
to like you know get weird like like do any sort of prompting stuff just hang up if they
start getting angry like hang up um and you can kind of see some people are submitting
phone calls there nice and it flows through to our feedback channel here's some
changing okay it looks like people are there's a lot of feedback on the elo system yeah we need
to fix that one um you know one thing I think I think our agents are connected to slack and so
one of the cool things about this we could just ask our guy here actually so I can show something
on this if you want to cut over to uh to Matt's screen on the production side I've uh basically
this is something Lauren was doing as well so I told uh my chief of staff bot here um make a cup
cupcake feedback fixer so our original um our original like code name was cupcake right but now
it's listening to the cupcake feedback channel so we have our slack channel where feedback's coming
through and so as this comes in um this bot is just spinning up fixes so Lauren just called
it the elo feet feet like AI matchmaking rated play so it opened a cursor cloud agent that is
now addressing that fix um so that I can come through here and start reviewing some of these
prs as they get spun up nice so pure unreviewed just uh uses submitted fixes going in full send
full set can I say full set so you're using uh the cursor projects here yeah I am using projects
and this was um something Lauren recommended because I hadn't used them before now so I was
like oh like this is probably a good time for me to try it out uh and you can kind of think about
projects for at least I do similar to the way that um you know you can have like a chief of
staff grok bot where you just like drop a bunch of stuff in here and so projects are basically
like long-lived ways uh for organizing work so if I was like working on something specific maybe
I was doing like a UI refresh um I could make a new project and the project is like a master
chat so you can see here I was chatting about this ads product and the project basically
kicks out separate work as sub-agents and then you can have this like durable long-lived session
where you're just chatting about like one topic or many topics actually and using sub-agents
to fix those so like at a meta point the same way I would be like oh I'm going to create a new
sub-agent here on this project to address an issue now you can just chat with a project
that's able to kick off those sub-agents that are working on things for you um so yeah that's
how I've been using it and you know the projects team if you're thinking oh well like how much stuff
could I chat with at the same time before the model gets degraded the projects team has assured us
that you can have thousands of chats over months uh we have some magic going on under the hood to
maintain this uh maintain this context I've really only heard good things and I've yet to try it out
so that's that's where I'm using it now do you use projects Eric um I dabbled briefly uh I remember
like three four weeks ago when we like barely shipped like an internal alpha okay that's when
I use it uh latest but I kind of am moving to rock for coding honestly okay um just like
consolidating all the cloud agents in a single uh yeah in a single like bot is kind of nice
yeah I do that do that as well like I don't have one here but I'll have like a loop spot which is
essentially my like engineering bot um and I'll kick out tasks um to that here I've just been
using Lauren's pattern of like chief of staff to engineering bots that then uh can delegate
themselves so sweet I also have my like uh my grind bot here that I have to set up so I'm
behind Lauren on the grind so it's your looped like your loop spot is it instructed to like
verify the work it's doing as well and like kicking off the cloud agents and yeah so it
uses a mix of like the um of uh potato mode and then uh and verification stuff so it's like
every time I send through things I want to see it verified I use the same pattern for the um
basically I shared uh this would be cool uh I guess the I shared this a couple days ago on twitter I
think honestly since I've been in the streaming booth time is like it's like oh there it is um but
yeah I shared this this flow which finds cool demos um and then builds them and kicks off a
cloud flow or preview deploy and those get screenshotted for me as well uh so you can
really use the rock bot like screenshot functionality and cursor cloud agent screenshot
functionality they like prototype some really cool stuff and like verify work and that's part
of a good loop is verification right something Lauren's been talking about a lot so honestly you
should create a new bot that just posts all these explorations that is there with the screenshots
videos on twitter yeah I feel like uh I'm a little I'm a little apprehensive to have anything
like go on twitter without me that is fair that is fair nice awesome pay for cloud PR is up
how does that how does that work a weekly ads auction for a pin paid row on uh on the leaderboard
oh merged already I just merged it's very preview I guess we can see live you can see it live in
about two minutes oh we have a new first place player on the leaderboard not a bot is at the
top of our leaderboard now 29 wins three losses congratulations all right let's see maybe we have
the uh our cloud uh our cloud so leaderboard that's my tools I don't know what happened to my bidding
well while matt debugs that i'll just do a quick reset so we can catch up to to where we are we've
been kind of hanging out for the last man it feels like 30 minutes 45 minutes now um we are on
day three of our live stream 72 our live stream here of building a business with rock bot we are
building a game studio we have launched our first game it is called thursday arena you can check
it out at thursday arena.com and find us on x at at thursday arena and you're kind of seeing
matt walk through some changes he's making for the website in real time you're seeing me break
our website in real time uh which is which is awesome uh we are joined by eric who's on the
space xai team for this last three hours the stream we're all working on some features some
polish improvements we have man i don't know how many grok bots now i think we had a grok
bot overlay i don't know where that went but we have something like 40 50 60 something like
that grok bots that we're using across across all of us to get all this work done we've made over 200
prs i just opened one and it's pr number 274 i think so we're going to cross the 300 number
pretty soon we have a leaderboard we're adding features we're adding modernization
a lot of good stuff going on we're going to try to sort of get to a really good point
that we feel great about the project on and hopefully like an hour or so if not less
just to ornate you if you've been tuning in throughout the three days we're live here
in san francisco right next to dream force uh spending some time cutting between talks
on the main stage right downstairs us up here in the studio booth and hopefully you've enjoyed
hanging out um we are going to cut to a 10 minute break uh just to kind of do a quick be
right back and get give us a chance to take a little second so we will cut to a 10 minute
break see you guys in 10 and finish up welcome back everyone to the grok bot galaxy live stream
we are on day three the final hours the final minutes some might say of building a business
from scratch with grok bots for those of you who have been with us this entire journey thank
you so much it's been a ton of fun we are uh kind of trying to get to a point where we wrap up and
you know finish really strong in the next few minutes here but i think are we doing a promo
first is that is that what i heard we're doing a promo first okay give me a second here let me
get this going on my screen we know a lot of you have been patiently hanging out with us all day
and so uh if we can get my screen up on the screen this is for the real ones for the real
real one for the homies for the homies going out to you yes you're still watching the stream
this day on day three at four p.m pst we appreciate what do you get what do the homies get
well i'm i'm just reading off uh the thing here right so uh within the next five minutes if the
homies post credits in the chat that's not a twitter comment this is specifically the chat
for the live stream that's not like a it's not an ex post it's a chat in the live stream you post
credits in the live stream chat you receive grokbar credits by the end of the day two hundred dollars in
value amazing did i say that right is that am i am i coherent here i think that's what it says
right we post credits in the in the chat live stream chat two hundred dollars of grokbar credits
by the end of the day limited time offer five minutes so if you want if you want credits now
is your chance get it while it's hot get it while it's hot okay recommend i recommend and then really
if you haven't tried out crockpot by now
I mean, we don't know what you're doing here.
Give it a shot, like, you can actually build a company
with this thing.
It's crazy.
Yeah.
Cool.
Thanks to all the real ones.
Dang, the chat is blowing up right now.
This is nice.
Nice.
OK, we can kill my screen for a bit
so I can switch over to some more serious stuff.
But this has been great.
Credits are great.
I think it might help maybe.
Like, let's do a quick check-in of what
everyone's been working on.
We just took a quick 10-minute break.
I saw a lot of agents and bots hanging out in the background.
Anyone have anything fun they want to share?
A lot of agents.
So I've been working on more animations
for the actual car defining scene.
I chose Matt just now.
I don't have a screen connection,
but I'll put up a PR, and you can judge for yourself
to see if it's actually an improvement.
If not, don't revert it, please.
Just keep it.
We can get to my screen in the meantime.
And then when Eric gets his PR up, we can run through it.
And I can show you what I got cooking here.
So my screen, when production gets a moment,
I've been iterating on the flow I built in Grokbot.
So earlier, we talked about how we'd set up a feedback slack
channel.
And so now we have all this feedback coming in,
bug or bad design like that.
That's just like a little nag for us live.
And so we're getting all of this feedback.
And what I did was I built a Grokbot that
watches the feedback channel, and then basically
dedupes the feedback.
So we come down here.
It's noticing duplicates and then kicking off
cursor cloud agents to start fixing the feedback.
So this is part of Lauren's factory that she built here.
So you can see here, recent ones are not updating or showing
when the user views past matches.
Past matches look static.
Match history UI appears stale.
And so there's a repro, which we have because Lauren set up
some cool repro skills and a goal.
And so we also have related inflate work.
And you can see, it appears to have fixed the issue
with some tests that are confirmed.
And I have this just set to YOLO.
So it's just merging stuff in.
So we have our little user feedback software factory.
I guess I should close my PR that's doing the same thing.
So good to know, good to know.
Already merging.
And then concurrently, I'm also just like our ads bid stuff
is completely broken.
So I'm working on some fixes to that with some new ad
placements as well.
I have honestly no idea where these ads are going to go.
They could just be all over the same.
But it's something we can figure out in a little bit.
I love that.
But the idea is that you'll be able to buy an ad.
And you can see the auction is currently broken,
which we need to work on.
And eventually, that ad will live in either ticker
or you'll be able to buy your way to the top of the leader
board here.
You can see I'm in the bottom 5% of players.
P99.
P95.
We're down there.
Hey, at least you got it ranked.
I know.
You're in the arena.
So now we have our bid for the bottom spot.
I actually don't know if this works.
So I actually placed a bid.
I placed a $1 bid.
And now, I think maybe there's a, I don't know.
I actually don't know exactly how this works.
But we should have that bid and show
at the top of the leader board.
And I think we might want to have like three places here.
Take the top spot.
All right.
So we'll get on that one.
If we cut over to my screen real quick,
I've also been playing with different card designs.
So hopefully a little bit more visual.
I kind of like number three.
I was a bit pixelated.
But number three looks pretty good.
It's like more full screen, I guess, within the card.
Yeah.
A little bit easier to read.
We got a few card templates generated.
But I think so far, number three is my favorite.
I can imagine some nice holo effects on this,
like on hover.
And then I also have my chief of staff, Steve.
And I basically told it to, as we're wrapping up the day,
go watch our live stream.
Look for clips.
Look for tweets, interesting ones.
And just draw like a recap poster in TL Draw.
So it's still working on it.
It's got three boxes so far.
I'm curious what it will come up with.
But yeah, one nice thing about GrotBot
is you can jump in, look at the browser,
see what your bots are doing.
And then, of course, I have my cheater bot,
who is somehow making my score go down instead of up.
When it started, what was it at when you started?
When I started, I think we were at 986.
I was at 986.
And now I am at 956.
I'd actually like to just point out that you're below me.
I'm a leader.
So this bot needs some, what do you call it, discipline
from Dr. Eggbot.
I did actually add a rules endpoint.
So if you go to Thursday Arena.com slash rules,
maybe you tell your bot to look at the rules.
I just saw that.
And I was like, wow, we made it to the end of the stream.
And we finally have a tutorial for how to play.
It only took us until 4 PM on the third day.
Also, what you might notice if you open that on the stream,
it's now agent friendly.
So I guess the agent has to be auth, but rules.md renders.
And we have a LLMs text.
So oh yeah, if you want to pull up, there we go.
There we go, friendly.
And if you search, if you go into Google
and you search Thursday Arena, yeah,
I mean, you could also do Thursday Space Arena.
We are now the first results on Google.
We have our AMO SEO.
You didn't pay any money to do that.
So we're running a business.
Wow, whoever did the SEO, free browser auto battle
was pretty good.
I mean, it was cursor auto battle.
I'm going to teach my bot.
And if you're tuning in, we have some free credits
to give out.
Just type credits in the x chat.
Is that over already?
Actually, it ended one minute ago.
Dang.
If you got it, then give it a real one.
I'm kidding in your bot.
And I'm saying, read this and learn how to win.
Because I finally got my first PR.
All right.
I think, I think.
It's going to be a mega PR.
Let me tell you about that.
Let's see here.
Most likely going to be submerged context too.
I mean, I've just merged like six PRs.
Are you just force pushing?
No, I set up the auto bug fixer to use Lauren's EOLO mode
or whatever.
Just EOLOing.
You had to say slash potato mode full autopilot.
Yeah, full autopilot.
OK, these are just merging and disappearing.
So I guess it's working.
How's your bot doing with our three day recap?
The drawings.
Not that great.
Yeah, I don't think we should see that.
13 PRs, no ICP.
It's kind of roasting us right now.
So I guess it's, well, day one, I think
we were trying to think about like a real person in an IRL
business.
And we, after interviewing some of our guests,
we realized how difficult that endeavor would be.
So we pivoted on the second day to working on a game studio
instead.
And then on the third day, we actually shipped it.
And look, 4.5K games.
So Groff was actually doing all the research.
I didn't really tell any of these numbers.
I just told it, go look us up on X and figure out the details.
And it's drawing pictures for me on TL Draw.
Pretty fun.
That's cool.
So OK, we have a core game.
I think we have a bunch of polish going into it.
We have a billboard ad slot.
We have a leaderboard ad slot.
So I feel we've got a couple of monetization opportunities
for folks to kind of get their brand out there,
get their name out there, which is really great.
We fixed some bugs.
So we had some bugs around win loss ratios.
Those are now fixed, should be fixed.
We have a whole system that's taking feedback that's
coming in through the app.
We have phone feedback.
We have text feedback.
I'm trying to think of what else we
want to do to sort of feel like we've
gotten to a good spot today.
I have not had a good win streak lately.
Yeah, me neither.
I'm ranked 82nd.
OK, I feel like if I end the day in the top 100,
we're literally at the bottom 5% of players, so.
Yeah, we need to learn how to play our own game.
Cool, cool, cool.
We do have now, it looks like we're
down to three diamond players, although we have had
some feedback around Elo.
And so we'll double check on the Elo logic.
I think there might be something going on there,
or at least some, hopefully some, maybe a quick fix.
There we go, three diamond players.
Ari, the monk, has been leading all day.
Looks like we've got a couple of fixes coming in,
checking on bots here.
I got to get a right access to repository.
You had Eric on right access.
I think I asked, I guess.
Eric has to make PRs.
The rest of us don't.
The hand-writh and code.
Yeah, let me log in on GitHub here.
Let's not show my screen if you come up.
Do you need my username?
You got it?
I'll send you a Slack message.
Yeah, sounds good.
Let's do that.
OK.
OK, so we have Eric Bush permissions.
It's going to be good.
collaborators and teams.
I love that you've set up the Slack channels,
like the marketing, the socials, the metrics, the bug
reports, ad bids.
Yeah, once we have the ad bids live,
they should come through in there.
But it's currently not doing so.
Nice.
I think one thing I am sort of reflecting on,
as we built this our very first game,
is there's so many different aspects
of running iGame Studio.
Or I guess if we're even generalizing,
running a business, starting a startup,
takes really a lot of effort.
You have to spend a lot of time
building the product, doing engineering work.
You have to think about, you have
to validate your ideas.
You have to do GTM, go to market.
You have to think about monetization.
There's all these different things
that you have to consider for building a product.
And not just that, but also all the work
that goes into maintaining a product,
like getting feedback and whatnot.
So I think I'm curious what you all think about this.
Right now, we have a game studio.
But if we were to start a new business,
how would you think about approaching it differently
or whatever, based on what we learned during this experience?
Yeah, so I think my learnings off the top were,
number one, once we aligned on an idea
that we're all excited about,
and just started shipping an MVP,
things started moving a lot faster.
They were kind of like deliberating an idea.
And candidly, right, we had distribution
because we had a lot of people watching our stream.
So it was easy to get people to try our product.
I think the hardest part is really getting people to care
or building something that people care about.
For example, would anyone have played this game
had we not been on a live stream?
I do not think so.
I don't think so.
So the hardest part is getting people to care,
aligning on an idea that resonates with people.
And I really do think it is kind of like the idea,
like when we announced we were doing this live stream,
we got such a magnetic, such a compounding response.
It's kind of like, if you get an idea
that gets people really excited,
then you have the beginnings of something
that you can then create a business from, I think.
Yeah.
And I think what was interesting to me
is we had a bunch of talks throughout the last few days
where we heard from people who are using GrokBox.
SpaceX and our employees were using GrokBox in really fun ways.
And at first, I kind of thought a lot of that stuff
wouldn't generalize to what we did.
There's a lot of, well, working at a big company,
but it turns out a lot of the stuff was pretty relevant.
So the chats we had earlier today, chatting with Matt,
who works on our revenue operations team
about how you go build a growth playbook,
we came up with a pretty good plan
with some really good ideas, right?
Like anytime someone follows us on X,
we can send them a DM
and let them know they should try the game.
You know, there's a lot of like really rich ideas here,
then some partnership models where we could go talk
to companies that host games or distributors of games
so that we could get featured on those lists
or in those places.
I think it's kind of a standard business playbook
in a lot of ways, right?
Like you sort of can run a general business playbook.
You need sales, you need partnerships,
you need, you know, revenue operations.
And that probably looks and feels different
when you're a small zero to one company.
Like maybe that's all one role
instead of like three different roles.
But one thing that I really appreciated is that
there's a lot more work that goes into this
than you might expect.
And there's a lot of like small things to get right.
And, you know, I think, yeah,
just kind of learning those lessons
and being able to experience them was really cool.
Yeah, it's kind of interesting.
Like you have to go out as a human
and like discover all the problems organically.
And once you like figured out how to solve them,
you can actually like turn them into a bot
and just like keep them running forever.
And eventually like that's,
those bots are gonna grow by a lot.
But yeah, it's still,
it's an interesting like paradigm
to create a company with rock bots.
Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, Adam, go ahead.
Sorry, can we, a production team,
can we take my screen off?
Yeah, I think the thing I'm also reflecting on
is like, you know, the,
for me, the process of building a game and a game studio.
A lot of the, you know,
even though our first product,
our first game isn't really that good.
I still keep coming back to this idea that
optimizing and thinking about your workflow, right?
Like how you actually get work done
is so powerful when you have growth bot by your side
and automating and doing things.
Because, you know, we can again,
take the learnings you reiterate fast
and ship the next, ship a next game
or ship the next application.
I think a lot about building products
is not just the initial splashy launch,
but also how you keep improving it as you...
Getting the flywheels in.
Getting the flywheel.
Right.
And also exercising some restraint, right?
Like with AI, you can literally build anything you want.
So you can have products that just have a million features
and they're not any good, right?
And so there's this,
there's almost like this discipline
that we now have to have, right?
When there's an abundance of intelligence
and ability to build to do that.
So...
Yeah.
One of the things we talk a lot about internally is
what are we going to unshift
and just having this meant constant mentality
that there's stuff you should remove from the product
to simplify it, make it easier.
And I think we did a decent job of that, right?
We didn't feature bloat.
We came in with a lot of feature ideas.
I'm thinking back to yesterday
when we had our initial whiteboard,
we had these really complicated stat blocks
for each character.
We had a whole plan to add different battlefields.
And I think what really,
at least let us get this out today
was making sure we pared that down a little bit
and really just focused on the core loop.
And that went through its own iterations,
but I think that actually made a really big difference
to getting something launched.
And then, you know, also something that we think
ended up looking pretty good in the end.
So, yeah.
One final question.
Like if you, if someone were to ask you like,
I want to build a company with Crockbot,
what are like the top three things you would tell them?
Ooh.
It helps to like know exactly what you're doing before.
Like, okay, so here's a good example.
We talked to a guest yesterday.
I can't remember exactly which guest.
So maybe one of you can help me.
And they were like,
oh, you guys want to do an event pop-up?
And then they just rattled off like 10 things
that I'd never thought about doing an event pop-up before.
Like permitting, catering,
what it means to serve hot food versus cold food
if you need a kitchen.
And I was just like, oh, like that's all stuff
I've never thought about
because I've never actually done it.
And so a large part of like,
as it turns out, like doing something is actually
maybe unintuitively actually just doing it
and then figuring out like,
oh, I'm not good at this thing
and I need to learn these things.
That's like what makes a professional
and someone that like does a business well
is like, you know exactly what you're doing.
So if you're going to build a business with Crockbot,
like build a business around something
you already know how to do well.
And then that makes it a lot easier
versus someone that comes in and says,
oh, I'm just going to like make a bunch of money.
And as it turns out,
you don't just like make a bunch of money
without doing anything.
You're telling me you can prompt the models
to like make a billion dollars, make a mistake.
No mistakes.
I have an age of running when we started the stream
and I still have zero dollars.
That was our backup plan.
Like in case it's all crash converted.
I guess one thing that I would say to your question is
I think there's just a lot of wisdom in the world.
Like we're really lucky to have a bunch of guests
as Matt called out that kind of helped steer us
throughout these three days.
But a lot of the bots we created to go learn things
like we have game designer bots
who learned how to do game design
by just learning from the best games.
And one of the things that maybe I undervalued
before this was you can give the bots lots of context,
you can sort of teach them all the things they need to know.
We had someone earlier on the stream talking about how
whenever they're entering into a new discipline,
they tell the bot to go take a bunch of courses
on the internet.
And I never really thought, I never thought of that idea.
But you sort of think of these bots
because they sort of learn and evolve over time,
you can kind of encourage them to learn
the things you want them to learn.
And so maybe another angle to what Matt said
is create bots that help cover the things you don't know.
So if you don't really know how
maybe hot food versus cold food works,
or if we'd stuck with that idea,
we could have probably tried to get a bunch of bots
learning as much as they could about that
and maybe giving us some advice.
And so I think my big thing would be
don't be afraid to assemble a really varied team of bots
and kind of think of them the way you'd think of
like hiring a group of employees.
I think for me, actually,
obviously this is a brought bot live stream,
but actually the thing I think is even more valuable
in the era of agents is actually the people
that you work with, right?
And I actually saw this tweet on our post on X recently.
I can't recall exactly what the post was,
but it was something along the lines of,
every team needs basically two different types of people.
One is someone who has a clear vision,
a clear understanding of what it is that you want to build
and a lot of good taste and good judgment
of what should go into the product.
And then the other person you need
is someone who is relentless at making things happen
and even better when you can find someone who can do both.
And I think that's a distinctly human role
that we'll continue to play
even as models get more and more capable.
And yeah, I think it's been a real blast
working with all of you
and kind of learning this stuff.
Yeah, I agree.
All right, let's bring it over to my screen
and try to see if we can bring this all home.
So what I'd like to do is two things.
One is I want to go over our final metrics.
It's not the end of the day
until we've seen how we did on the numbers.
So I just asked Data, our data bot here
to pull our metrics as to where we are.
It's as of just halfway past 4 p.m. on Thursday.
It looks like we have crossed the 4,000 game threshold
after we crossed the over 6,000 game public match threshold.
This chart is the one, there we go.
We got our 4 p.m. bump that we're hoping for.
X signups will continue to come in throughout the day
but looks like we got a nice little bump
in the afternoon here.
So thank you all who are signing up.
It looks like still people coming in and joining.
Tons of players on the stream too.
Our cumulative user graph,
we will probably cross 2,000 I hope
right before we wrap up here in the next few minutes.
I actually, I brought that on prod.
So we're working on this.
Classic.
It has to be done.
I'm over here talking about signups.
You're up.
Lauren's talking about restraint
as I have a software factory
that just totally brought down prod
with a bad SQL query.
So we're working on that one.
Okay, so we will have signups open again soon.
We may not hit 2,000 in the next little while.
We've had, man, like close to 30,000 page views
on the website.
We're ranking number one on Google.
We have a bunch of different websites
that are bringing us traffic.
Yeah, overall, I just think we're having a good time.
I asked my bot to put together a plan.
Oh, much better than mine.
Over the last three days.
So we'll see which plan we like better.
But you know, at the end of the day,
I think this was never really about building a game.
It wasn't even about building a game studio,
although yeah, that's what we were doing.
We really just wanted to bring away to show you all
how you could use Grokbot
for all the stuff that you do.
And that could be in your personal life.
We heard from shopping with agents and buying shoes
to running your own creative projects
to everything in between,
but also for all the things that you do at work
every single day, right?
All of us are diehard Grokbot users.
We're in the app every day.
We're hourly active users in our jobs.
And we know many of you are,
many people we work with are too.
And so really just wanted to show if we start from scratch
how you can just build and bring a team of bots
to kind of help you accelerate your own work.
So hopefully there are some useful tidbits.
We'll probably share out some clips and all that
from the stuff we found most useful after the fact.
So stay tuned and follow at bot
to see some of those at Grok, of course,
and then maybe keep an eye on our X page too.
Maybe see some updates to the app,
but let's do a quick recap.
So we started out building a marketplace for bot templates.
We've talked about the X.ai slash bot slash
marketplace template.
We want to do something with those bots
and bring some joy into those bots
besides just the templates they are.
We started out with an auto battler concept.
We had all these ideas for, well, we'll volunteer later.
We won't do cosmetics.
You might have some ads in the stadiums.
We'll add some replay mechanics.
It turned out as we pared down our idea more and more.
We picked some of those that we wanted to keep
like the ads.
We threw away some of the other ones like the cosmetics.
We aligned on a core game mechanic.
We got rid of this mechanic,
which was this rock, paper, scissors idea we had.
We pared it down even more
to focus on a pure auto battle mechanic.
And we really came to build a really great edge factory.
And I think this was maybe the defining feature,
I think, of our last 24 hours
where we have chief bots looping in a team of other bots,
play testing, fixing PRs, auto approving PRs
once bugs are fixed and then landing to mash main.
Fun joke.
Lauren, do you want to explain this one?
I actually don't, I don't know how this happened,
but like I had, I think what happened is
I told Dr. Eggbot, who was my bot for creating bots,
to come up with like food theme names
and like specifically potato theme names.
And somehow one of them snuck in, I think into notion,
a task that every merge of a pull request
should be called a mash.
So that's the fun trivia.
And it is happening to this day.
There are, if you look at this screen here,
there are pushes and there are mashes.
My chief now only believes in mashing PRs.
So yeah, you can have fun with it too, right?
You can invent your own language,
you can give your bots your own language.
You have to mash PRs and squash potatoes.
Yeah, very cool, yeah, love it.
We've been cooking, as they would say.
Yeah, so I guess, yeah, over the course of three days,
did a ton of stuff.
You can see some examples of that here.
But we didn't just build features, right?
We also started to think about
what it would take to build a business.
And so we integrated with a ton of tools.
Thank you to all the tools that exist in the world.
Like Lawrence said earlier,
we're kind of standing on the shoulders
of incredible engineering teams,
from planet scale for our database,
to Clerk for authentication,
and Vercel for deployments,
and Stripe for payments,
and all sorts of other things.
It's been really cool
just to be able to glue all these things together
to build something.
And obviously there's a lot more we could do with this,
right?
So a game studio being built,
sort of one of many games that could come.
And yeah, I guess I would just say,
I think we ended up
with a pretty successful three days.
Hopefully, if you're tuning in,
you managed to pick up some credits along the way too.
We're unfortunately out of getaways for the day,
but we have done a few of those as well.
So hopefully that kept y'all engaged
and gave you a chance to hang out with us.
Any parting thoughts from the group
before we call it a day and call it a week?
Thanks for having me.
And I'm getting the PR merged.
All right, he's getting the PR merged.
Maine is proud to back up,
so we have fixed that.
Yeah, we're so back.
I think ads might work.
I don't know that we have time
to actually do a walkthrough of ads.
Well, actually we can try.
Why not?
So if we want to cut over to Matt's screen here,
potentially.
Okay, cool.
Number one, I wanted this to show,
we have like our take the top spot bid here.
So now I'm leading the bid.
I wanted this to show at the top,
so we still need to work on getting
like my sort of sponsored bid at the top.
But now, maybe final check,
we can test our monetization factor.
So we need an advertiser name.
So we have our preview here,
which is again, very vibe coded.
It's a logo,
which I don't know if that's optional or not.
Dex.com, let's try bidding.
It needs SVG logo.
Okay, SVG logo dummy.
Logo Ipsum, there we go.
Actually do that.
Yeah, there you go.
Okay, cool.
Oh, these are quite cool.
We're figuring stuff out every day.
Okay, so choose file,
we'll go with our logo Ipsum.
Okay.
Oh, wow, I like it.
Oh, wait, it doesn't have a reload if it fails.
Okay, wait, we'll try one more time.
Cool, we got a logo, got a URL.
Okay, bid, uploading logo.
Placing your bid.
Placing your bid, did we make a dollar?
It's also just a heads up.
It's like moderating a lot of the user submitted content
and moderation is broken.
So I know we tried, we almost got there.
I'll take the ownership of this one.
But we made our first theoretical sponsorship dollar, right?
Theoretically.
We have theoretical leadership dollars
and theoretical sponsorship dollars.
And I think that's a great way to end it.
All right, cool.
Lauren, any parting thoughts?
Have fun using Grockbot and follow us on X.
Follow us on X, yeah.
Oh, and eat more potatoes.
Yeah, not very useful advice for me.
Mash more PRs.
There you go.
There we have it, amazing.
Thanks you all for watching.
Thank you. Have a good one.
See ya, bye.